<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<streamprofile_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Stream Profile Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Stream Profile Settings</titleTxt>
		<sizename6Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(partial)</sizename6Txt>
		<sizename7Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(partial; full speed)</sizename7Txt>
		<sizename8Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(16:9)</sizename8Txt>
		<sizename1Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(VGA)</sizename1Txt>
		<sizename2Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(CIF)</sizename2Txt>
		<sizename3Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(quarter VGA)</sizename3Txt>
		<sizename4Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(QCIF)</sizename4Txt>
		<sizename5Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(1/8 VGA)</sizename5Txt>
		<pixTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">pixels</pixTxt>
		<introTxt type="text" minor="0">Here you can add a new stream profile or change an existing profile.</introTxt>
		<intro1Txt type="text" minor="0">Enter a unique descriptive name for the profile.</intro1Txt>
		<intro2Txt type="text" minor="0">Enter a description. This can be a short description of the settings for future use.</intro2Txt>
		<intro3Txt type="text" minor="0">Choose the form of Video encoding you wish to use from the drop-down list:</intro3Txt>
		<intro33Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;H.264&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Also known as &#x3C;b&#x3E;MPEG-4 Part 10&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, this function offers higher video resolution than Motion JPEG or MPEG-4 at the same bit rate and bandwidth, or the same quality video at a lower bit rate.</intro33Txt>
		<intro32Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;MPEG-4&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Video quality is comparable to Motion JPEG, but requires much less bandwidth.</intro32Txt>
		<intro31Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Motion JPEG&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Delivers a high quality video stream, from which individual images can be extracted and saved.</intro31Txt>
		<saveTxt type="text" minor="0">Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;OK&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to save your settings, or click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Cancel&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to return to the previous settings.</saveTxt>
		<descTxt type="text" minor="0">All checked settings are included in the new or modified stream profile. When chosen from the drop-down list in Live View or in individual event configurations, the stream profile will override current settings.</descTxt>
		<subTitle_tabs_Txt type="text" minor="0">Tabs</subTitle_tabs_Txt>
		<tabinfoTxt type="text" minor="0">The settings are separated into different tabs:</tabinfoTxt>
		<tabGenTxt type="text" minor="0">Image</tabGenTxt>
    <tabDirTxt type="text" minor="0">Direction</tabDirTxt>
		<tabAudioTxt type="text" minor="0">Audio</tabAudioTxt>
		<tabMjpegTxt type="text" minor="0">MJPEG</tabMjpegTxt>
		<validitynoteTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Settings under the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; tab apply to both  Motion JPEG and H.264/MPEG-4 video formats.</validitynoteTxt1>
		<validitynoteTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Settings under the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; tab apply to both  Motion JPEG and H.264 video formats.</validitynoteTxt2>
		<validitynoteTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Settings under the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; tab apply to both  Motion JPEG and MPEG-4 video formats.</validitynoteTxt3>
		<subTitle_preview_Txt type="text" minor="0">Preview</subTitle_preview_Txt>
		<prevVirTxt type="text" minor="0">To view the image while configuring the settings, choose a &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video encoding&#x3C;/b&#x3E; under Stream profile, a View Area from the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Source&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Show&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</prevVirTxt>
    <prevVirTxt6 type="text" minor="0">To view the image while configuring the settings, choose a &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video encoding&#x3C;/b&#x3E; under Stream profile and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Show&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</prevVirTxt6>
		<prevVirTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Video channel &#x3C;/b&#x3E;</prevVirTxt1>
		<prevVirTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Video format &#x3C;/b&#x3E;</prevVirTxt2>
		<prevVirTxt3 type="text" minor="0">and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Open&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</prevVirTxt3>
		<prevVirTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Pixel Counter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The pixel counter is useful in situations where there is a requirement that the image is  a certain size, for example face recognition. Note that, Pixel counter is available once you click open.</prevVirTxt4>
		<prevVirTxt5 type="text" minor="0">To set the size of the rectangle enter the number of pixels to show and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Apply&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Check &#x3C;b&#x3E;Show pixel counter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to enable the box in the image.</prevVirTxt5>
		<prevBTxt type="text" minor="0">To view the image while configuring the settings, choose a &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video encoding&#x3C;/b&#x3E; under Stream profile and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Show&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</prevBTxt>
		<subTitle_default_Txt type="text" minor="0">Restore Profile</subTitle_default_Txt>
		<defTxt type="text" minor="0">To restore original settings for this profile, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Restore&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. This option is available for pre-programmed Stream Profiles and not for profiles that have been created.</defTxt>
		<tabimage_Txt type="text" minor="0">Image</tabimage_Txt>
		<tab_info1 type="text" minor="0">Check the boxes of the settings you wish to include in the profile.</tab_info1>
		<subTitle_appearance_Txt type="text" minor="0">Image Appearance</subTitle_appearance_Txt>
		<sqpixTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Aspect ratio correction&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Checking this box improves the appearance of images from analog video sources when displayed on digital screens (i.e. computer monitors). The pixels comprising the image are rearranged so as to provide a more accurate representation of the image.</sqpixTxt>
+		<res1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Resolution&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the resolution to use for the image. The options are:</res1Txt>
		<res1Txt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Resolution&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Listed are the resolutions supported by the Axis product. Select the resolution to use for the image from the drop-down list.</res1Txt-1>
		<noteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Notes:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</noteTxt>
		<aspectStretchTxt type="text" minor="0">Image sizes in the 4x3 format (640x480 etc.) are rescaled from the image sensor's natural 5x4 aspect ratio. This requires a slight vertical compression of the image, but also gives the maximum vertical viewing angle.</aspectStretchTxt>
		<widescreenTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;16x9&#x3C;/b&#x3E; aspect ratio is for wide screen.</widescreenTxt>
		<partialTxt type="text" minor="0">Partial scan presents an image taken from the center region (measuring 1024x768 pixels) of the sensor, for optimal frame rate in Motion JPEG/MPEG-4.</partialTxt>
		<fullspeedTxt type="text" minor="0">Full speed takes a partial scan from the center region (measuring 900x675 pixels) of the sensor and then scales it down to present an image of 640x480, or 800x600, at full frame rate in Motion JPEG.</fullspeedTxt>
		<privacyMaskTxt type="text" minor="0">Privacy masks should be set in full resolution to ensure proper area coverage under all resolutions.</privacyMaskTxt>
		<resVSTxt type="text" minor="0">When using the &#x3C;b&#x3E;2CIF&#x3C;/b&#x3E; resolution, images are originally sent in the resolution 704x240 / 704x288 (NTSC/PAL) and then rescaled by the client to 704x480 / 704x576 (NTSC/PAL). This results in savings on bandwidth and eliminates problems concerning image interlacing.</resVSTxt>
		<resVS1Txt type="text" minor="0">The resolution &#x3C;b&#x3E;2CIF Expanded&#x3C;/b&#x3E; rescales the image on the server instead, which is more efficient than client-side rescaling.</resVS1Txt>
		<resVS2Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Snapshots &#x3C;/b&#x3E;saved in 2CIF will be saved at the original resolution, but snapshots in 2CIF Expanded are rescaled to the 4CIF resolution.</resVS2Txt>
		<compr1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Compression&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Changing the compression level affects the amount of bandwidth required. Lower compression improves image quality, but uses more bandwidth.</compr1Txt>
		<comprMP4Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: When using bit rate control for H.264/MPEG-4, this setting will define the minimum compression level. The compression level will temporarily increase as and when required.</comprMP4Txt1>
		<comprMP4Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: When using bit rate control for MPEG-4, this setting will define the minimum compression level. The compression level will temporarily increase as and when required.</comprMP4Txt2>
		<comprMP4Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: When using bit rate control for H.264, this setting will define the minimum compression level. The compression level will temporarily increase as and when required.</comprMP4Txt3>
		<compr2Txt type="text" minor="0">The compression level also affects file sizes when saving images. The graph below provides approximate file sizes when saving Motion JPEG images in the</compr2Txt>
		<compr3Txt type="text" minor="0">resolution 320x240.</compr3Txt>
		<compr4Txt type="text" minor="0">CIF resolution (352x240).</compr4Txt>
		<colorEnbTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Color setting -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Select either &#x3C;b&#x3E;Color&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Black &#x26; White&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Black &#x26; White uses less bandwidth than Color.</colorEnbTxt>
		<colorNoteCam type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Depending on the camera or source configuration, the video stream may appear black &#x26; white even if color is enabled. See the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Camera Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</colorNoteCam>
		<mirror_man_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Mirror image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this option to mirror the image in Live View or in event configurations.</mirror_man_Txt>
		<palette_man_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Palette&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the palette to use for the image.</palette_man_Txt>
		<subTitle_stream_Txt type="text" minor="0">Video Stream</subTitle_stream_Txt>
		<lmtFPSTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Maximum frame rate -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; To avoid bandwidth problems on the network, the frame rate allowed to each viewer can be limited to a fixed amount. Alternatively, the frame rate can be set as &#x3C;i&#x3E;unlimited&#x3C;/i&#x3E;, which means the Axis product always delivers the highest frame rate possible under the current conditions.</lmtFPSTxt>
		<lmtFPSTxt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Maximum frame rate -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; To avoid bandwidth problems on the network, the frame rate allowed to each viewer can be limited to a fixed number of frames per second. Alternatively, the frame rate can be set as &#x3C;b&#x3E;Unlimited&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, which means the Axis product always delivers the highest frame rate possible under the current conditions.</lmtFPSTxt-1>
		<rotTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Rotate image - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;The image can be rotated to suit requirements, by selecting any of the available values.</rotTxt>
		<rotQTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E; that rotating the image 90 or 270 degrees will lower the maximum frame rate.</rotQTxt>
		<subTitle_overlay_Txt type="text" minor="0">Overlay Settings</subTitle_overlay_Txt>
		<ovl1imgTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Text and/or image overlay&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</ovl1imgTxt>
		<ovl2imgTxt type="text" minor="0">Overlays are text and/or static images superimposed over the video image. The following options are available for overlays:</ovl2imgTxt>
		<ovl1noimgTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Text overlay&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</ovl1noimgTxt>
		<ovl2noimgTxt type="text" minor="0">Overlays are text superimposed over the video image. The following options are available for overlays:</ovl2noimgTxt>
		<ovlDTT1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include date&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The format for the date display will be as configured in the &#x3C;a href='date_h.shtml'&#x3E;Date &#x26; Time&#x3C;/a&#x3E; settings in the System Options.</ovlDTT1Txt>
		<ovlDTT2Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include time&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The time format will also be as configured in the Date &#x26; Time settings in the System Options.</ovlDTT2Txt>
		<ovlDTT3Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include text&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter your own text in the field provided.</ovlDTT3Txt>
    <ovlDTT4Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Text color and Text background color&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Set how the text and/or background are displayed. The options for text are black or white only, whereas the background can also be set as semi-transparent or transparent.</ovlDTT4Txt>
		<ovlPlcTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Place text/date/time at&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select placement of these items at the top or bottom of the image.</ovlPlcTxt>
		<ovlImgncTxt_camera type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include image overlay&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - (using default coordinates). Select the overlay image in the main &#x3C;b&#x3E;Camera Config&#x3C;/b&#x3E; settings.</ovlImgncTxt_camera>
		<ovlImgvsTxt_other type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include image overlay&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - (using default coordinates). Select the overlay image in the main &#x3C;b&#x3E;Source Config&#x3C;/b&#x3E; settings.</ovlImgvsTxt_other>
		<ovlImgnc_hiati_Txt_camera type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include image overlay&#x3C;/b&#x3E;  (using default image and coordinates)- Check this option to include the image and coordinates as set up under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Overlay Image Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</ovlImgnc_hiati_Txt_camera>
		<overlay_img_enabledTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Current overlay image setting&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Shows if overlay image settings are enabled or disabled. To edit settings go to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Overlay Image Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</overlay_img_enabledTxt>
		<tabaudio_Txt type="text" minor="0">Audio</tabaudio_Txt>
		<tab_info2a type="text" minor="0">Check the box to activate the settings in the profile you are creating.</tab_info2a>
		<tab_info2b type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Audio support must be also enabled under &#x3C;b&#x3E;System Options&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Security&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio Support&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</tab_info2b>
		<subTitle_audioenb_Txt type="text" minor="0">Enable Audio</subTitle_audioenb_Txt>
		<audioTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable audio&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to enable audio functionality.</audioTxt>
		<audioEncTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Current Audio Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The settings you have chosen under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Audio&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; will be shown here.</audioEncTxt>
		<tab_info3 type="text" minor="0">Check the boxes to activate the settings in the profile you are creating.</tab_info3>
		<subTitle_govsettings_Txt type="text" minor="0">Encoder Settings</subTitle_govsettings_Txt>
		<gOVlength1_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Length&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The GOV structure describes the composition of the H.264/MPEG-4 video stream which consists of 2 image forms, I-images and P-images. An I-image is a complete image, whereas a P-image is only the differences in the image as compared with the previous image.</gOVlength1_Txt1>
		<gOVlength2_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Length&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The GOV structure describes the composition of the H.264 video stream which consists of 2 image forms, I-images and P-images. An I-image is a complete image, whereas a P-image is only the differences in the image as compared with the previous image.</gOVlength2_Txt1>
		<gOVlength3_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Length&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The GOV structure describes the composition of the MPEG-4 video stream which consists of 2 image forms, I-images and P-images. An I-image is a complete image, whereas a P-image is only the differences in the image as compared with the previous image.</gOVlength3_Txt1>
		<gOVlength_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">The GOV length determines how many P-images are sent before the next complete I-image is sent.</gOVlength_Txt2>
		<gOVlength_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">Setting the GOV-length to a higher value saves considerably on bandwidth but if there is congestion on the network, there may be noticeable decay in the video quality. Setting the GOV-length to a lower value increases the video quality, in this case.</gOVlength_Txt3>
		<encoder_settings_H264_profile_help_text1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;H.264 profile&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select one of the sub profiles described below from the drop-down list.</encoder_settings_H264_profile_help_text1>
		<encoder_settings_H264_profile_help_text2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Baseline&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select this option if the client does not support CABAC entropy coding.</encoder_settings_H264_profile_help_text2>
		<encoder_settings_H264_profile_help_text3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Main&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This option uses CABAC and provides a better compression with maintained video quality. It also requires a larger amount of processing power to decode.</encoder_settings_H264_profile_help_text3>
		<encoder_settings_H264_profile_help_text4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;High&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Provides higher compression than both Main and Baseline profiles, but requires more processing power to decode. High profile supports 8x8 blocks which reduce the bitrate further compared to the Main profile.</encoder_settings_H264_profile_help_text4>
		<subTitle_bitratecontrol_Txt type="text" minor="0">Bit Rate Control</subTitle_bitratecontrol_Txt>
		<bitrate_intro_helpTxt type="text" minor="0">Adjusting the maximum bit rate and setting it to variable or constant is a good way of controlling the bandwidth used by the</bitrate_intro_helpTxt>
		<maxbitrate_helpTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Leaving the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Maximum bit rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; as unlimited will provide consistently good image quality, but at the expense of increased bandwidth usage whenever there is more activity in the image.</maxbitrate_helpTxt1>
		<maxbitrate_helpTxt2 type="text" minor="0">Limiting the bit rate to a defined value will prevent excessive bandwidth usage, but images will be lost when the limit is exceeded.</maxbitrate_helpTxt2>
		<maxbitrate_Note2 type="text" minor="0">Note that a maximum bit rate can be used for both variable and constant bit rates.</maxbitrate_Note2>
		<cbr_vbr_helpTxt type="text" minor="0">The bit rate type can be set as &#x3C;b&#x3E;Variable Bit Rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (VBR) or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Constant Bit Rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (CBR). VBR will adjust the bit rate according to the images' complexity, and thus uses a lot of bandwidth for a lot of activity in the image and less when the monitored area is quiet.</cbr_vbr_helpTxt>
		<cbr_helpTxt type="text" minor="0">When using CBR you can set a fixed &#x3C;b&#x3E;Target bit rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, which will ensure that the level of bandwidth consumed is predictable and will not change, whatever happens in the image.</cbr_helpTxt>
    <cbr_helpTxt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Constant bit rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; allows the operator to set the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Target bit rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; value that will be used by the Axis product in calculating the bit rate that should be applied to the video stream. CBR is mostly suitable when bandwidth is limited, since the operator can predict the level of bandwidth consumed. Note that, the bit rate applied to the video stream may be slightly above the set target bit rate depending on the situation the product operates in.</cbr_helpTxt-1>
		<cbr_helpTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Priority&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - As the bit rate would usually need to increase for increased image activity, but cannot when CBR is selected, the frame rate and image quality will both be affected negatively. To go some of the way towards compensating for this, it is possible to prioritize either the frame rate or the image quality whenever the bit rate would normally need to be increased. Not setting a priority means the frame rate and image quality will be affected approximately equally.</cbr_helpTxt2>
		<mbr_vbr_helpTxt type="text" minor="0">The bit rate type can be set as &#x3C;b&#x3E;Variable Bit Rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (VBR) or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Maximum Bit Rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (MBR). VBR will adjust the 
bit rate according to the images' complexity, and thus uses a lot of bandwidth for a lot of activity in the image and less when the monitored area is quiet. Note that, the maximum bitrate allowed is set to 50 Mbits/s to ensure compliance with H.264 level.</mbr_vbr_helpTxt>
		<mbr_helpTxt type="text" minor="0">When using MBR you can set a fixed &#x3C;b&#x3E;Target bit rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, which will ensure that the level of bandwidth consumed is predictable. The bit rate will try to stay as close as possible under the target but may bounce up and down within the set target. When there is a lot of activity (so higher bandwidth need) the rate controller will degrade the quality (image quality and/or framerate) to maintain a bandwidth under this target.</mbr_helpTxt>
		<cbr_helpTxt2-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Priority&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - As the bit rate would usually need to increase for increased image activity, but cannot when MBR is selected, the frame rate and image quality will both be affected negatively. To go some of the way towards compensating for this, it is possible to prioritize either the frame rate or the image quality whenever the bit rate would normally need to be increased. The image quality is related to the compression level setting, the lower is the compression the better is the possible image quality, see Compression. Not setting a priority means the frame rate and image quality will be affected approximately equally.</cbr_helpTxt2-1>
    <tabmpeg_Txt type="text" minor="0">MJPEG</tabmpeg_Txt>
		<tab_info4 type="text" minor="0">Check the boxes of the settings you wish to include in the profile.</tab_info4>
		<subTitle_sizecontrol_Txt type="text" minor="0">Frame Size Control</subTitle_sizecontrol_Txt>
		<framesizeTxt type="text" minor="0">In some situation the image size may get quite large due to low light or complex scenery. Adjusting the maximum frame size is a good way of controlling the bandwidth and storage used by the MJPEG video stream in these situations. Leaving the  frame size at &#x3C;b&#x3E;Default&#x3C;/b&#x3E; will provide consistently good image quality at the expense of increased bandwidth and storage usage during low light. Limiting the frame size will prevent excessive bandwidth and storage usage, but image quality will suffer. To prevent increase in bandwidth and storage usage, the maximum frame size should be set to an optimal amount.</framesizeTxt>
		<framesizeNote type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: The maximum frame size allowed increases compression in order to maintain a low frame size starting at the compression value set under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; tab &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Image Appearance&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Compression&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. When compression is 100, the image cannot be made smaller. You may also need to adjust the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Resolution&#x3C;/b&#x3E; setting if a smaller frame size is needed.</framesizeNote>
	</streamprofile_h>

	<streamprofilelist_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Stream Profile List</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Stream Profile List</titleTxt>
		<helpInfoTxt1 type="text" minor="0">The Video Stream settings include image appearance, frame rate, overlay settings, and more. Video stream settings can be adjusted from &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video Stream&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Pre-configured stream profiles can be set up in the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream Profile Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to be added to the drop-down list in Live View and used, for example, in image upload settings in individual action rules.</helpInfoTxt1>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Stream Profile List</subTitle1Txt>
		<helpInfoTxt2 type="text" minor="0">The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream Profile List&#x3C;/b&#x3E; shows all the stream profiles currently configured along with a description and the type of video encoding. There are several pre-programmed stream profiles available for quick set up or new stream profiles can be created based entirely on specifications needed.</helpInfoTxt2>
		<helpbuttons1 type="text" minor="0">To add a new stream profile, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, which opens the &#x3C;b&#x3E; Stream Profile Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; dialog.</helpbuttons1>
		<helpbuttons2 type="text" minor="0">An existing video profile can be used to create a new one. Select the desired profile and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Copy&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</helpbuttons2>
		<helpbuttons3 type="text" minor="0">To modify an existing video profile, select it and click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Modify&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button.</helpbuttons3>
		<helpbuttons4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Modifying a stream profile will not affect existing action rules using that stream profile. For changes to take effect the modified stream profile needs to be reselected in the action rule.</helpbuttons4>
		<helpbuttons5 type="text" minor="0">To delete a video profile, select it and click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button.</helpbuttons5>
		<helpbuttons6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Pre-programmed Stream Profiles, shown in blue, cannot be removed.</helpbuttons6>
	</streamprofilelist_h>
	
  <videostream_h>
    <pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Video Stream Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Video Stream Settings</titleTxt>
		<sizename6Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(partial)</sizename6Txt>
		<sizename7Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(partial; full speed)</sizename7Txt>
		<sizename8Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(16:9)</sizename8Txt>
		<sizename1Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(VGA)</sizename1Txt>
		<sizename2Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(CIF)</sizename2Txt>
		<sizename3Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(quarter VGA)</sizename3Txt>
		<sizename4Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(QCIF)</sizename4Txt>
		<sizename5Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">(1/8 VGA)</sizename5Txt>
		<pixTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">pixels</pixTxt>
    <saveTxt type="text" minor="0">Click Save to save your settings, or click Reset to return to the previous settings.</saveTxt>
    <subTitle_tabs_Txt type="text" minor="0">Tabs</subTitle_tabs_Txt>
    <tabinfoTxt type="text" minor="0">The settings are separated into different tabs:</tabinfoTxt>
    <tabGenTxt type="text" minor="0">Image</tabGenTxt>
    <tabAudioTxt type="text" minor="0">Audio</tabAudioTxt>
    <tabDirTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Direction</tabDirTxt1>
    <validitynote1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: The settings under the Image tab apply to both the Motion JPEG and the H.264/MPEG-4 video formats.</validitynote1Txt>
    <validitynote2Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: The settings under the Image tab apply to both the Motion JPEG and the H.264 video formats.</validitynote2Txt>
    <validitynote3Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: The settings under the Image tab apply to both the Motion JPEG and the MPEG-4 video formats.</validitynote3Txt>
    <subTitle_preview_Txt type="text" minor="0">Preview</subTitle_preview_Txt>
    <prevPixelTxt1 type="text" minor="0">To view the image while configuring the settings and check how many pixels are used in an area of the image, choose a &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video format&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Open&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</prevPixelTxt1>
    <prevPixelTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Pixel Counter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The pixel counter is useful in situations where there is a requirement that the image is  a certain size, for example face recognition. Note that, Pixel counter is available once you click open.</prevPixelTxt2>
    <prevPixelTxt3 type="text" minor="0">To set the size of the rectangle enter the number of pixels to show and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Apply&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Check &#x3C;b&#x3E;Show pixel counter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to enable the box in the image.</prevPixelTxt3>
    <prevBTxt type="text" minor="0">To view the image while configuring the settings, choose a &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video format&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Open&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</prevBTxt>
    <tabimage_Txt type="text" minor="0">Image</tabimage_Txt>
    <subTitle_capture_Txt type="text" minor="0">Image Capture</subTitle_capture_Txt>
    <captureTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Capture mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select which capture mode to use. This defines the size and scan mode of the sensor. HDTV format 720p (progressive scan) or 1080i (interlaced) with the option of de-interlacing. 720p provides a better quality video stream especially when capturing motion. 720p is recommended for all resolutions except 1920x1080 which would result in an upscaled image of lesser quality. 1080i provides a larger image, but also may contain motion artifacts which may degrade the image and should only be used with 1920x1080 resolution.</captureTxt1>
    <captureTxt2 type="text" minor="0">De-interlacing is used to improve image quality from an interlaced video source by removing motion artifacts. Note that deinterlacing may slightly reduce the sharpness of the image.</captureTxt2>
    <subTitle_appearance_Txt type="text" minor="0">Image Appearance</subTitle_appearance_Txt>
    <capturemodeTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Capture mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Shows the current capture mode set under Camera Settings or use the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Capture mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; link to open the Camera settings page.</capturemodeTxt>
    <viewAsizeTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;View area size&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Shows the size of the view area set under View Areas or use the &#x3C;b&#x3E;View area size&#x3C;/b&#x3E; link to open the View Areas page.</viewAsizeTxt>
    <viewAsize1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;View area size&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Shows the size of the view area set under View Area or use the &#x3C;b&#x3E;View area size&#x3C;/b&#x3E; link to open the View Area page.</viewAsize1Txt>
    <digitalPTZ2Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Digital PTZ&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Shows if Digital PTZ  have been enabled.</digitalPTZ2Txt>
    <maxZoomTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Max&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Shows the Max zoom set.</maxZoomTxt1>
    <maxZoomTxt2 type="text" minor="0">Digital PTZ and Max zoom are set under PTZ settings. Go to &#x3C;b&#x3E;PTZ &#x3E; PTZ Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or use the Digital PTZ link to open the PTZ Settings page.</maxZoomTxt2>
    <wideTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Widescreen resolutions&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to make widescreen resolutions (16:9) available in the drop-down list. Select the required resolution and click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Save&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button.</wideTxt1>
    <wideTxt2 type="text" minor="0">When changing resolutions to widescreen or back to 4:3 format, all the currently open video streams will be stopped. These will need to be restarted.</wideTxt2>
    <wideTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; After changing to or from widescreen format, always check that privacy masks and motion detection windows are still configured as intended.</wideTxt3>
    <sqpixTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Aspect ratio correction&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Checking this box improves the appearance of images in the browser when the video stream has a different aspect ratio. Pixels comprising the image are rearranged so as to provide a more accurate representation of the image.</sqpixTxt>
    <sqpixMP4Txt type="text" minor="0">Note that when using MPEG-4 as the video format, any aspect ratio correction for the image is applied by the viewing client (the correct aspect ratio is contained in the MPEG-4 stream). This can have consequences for e.g. snapshots saved from the Live View page - these will be saved in the original format.</sqpixMP4Txt>
    <res1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Resolution -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Select the resolution to use for the image. The options are:</res1Txt>
    <res1Txt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Resolution&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Listed are the resolutions supported by the Axis product. Select the resolution to use for the image from the drop-down list.</res1Txt-1>
    <resVSTxt type="text" minor="0">When using the &#x3C;b&#x3E;2CIF&#x3C;/b&#x3E; resolution, images are originally sent in the resolution 704x240 / 704x288 (NTSC/PAL) and then rescaled by the client to 704x480 / 704x576 (NTSC/PAL). This results in savings on bandwidth and eliminates problems concerning image interlacing.</resVSTxt>
    <resVS1Txt type="text" minor="0">The resolution &#x3C;b&#x3E;2CIF Expanded&#x3C;/b&#x3E; rescales the image on the server instead, which is more efficient than client-side rescaling.</resVS1Txt>
    <resVS2Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Snapshots &#x3C;/b&#x3E;saved in 2CIF will be saved at the original resolution, but snapshots in 2CIF Expanded are rescaled to the 4CIF resolution.</resVS2Txt>
    <vapixTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; More resolutions are available through AXIS VAPIX&#x3C;sup&#x3E;TM&#x3C;/sup&#x3E; HTTP API.</vapixTxt>
    <aspectTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Changing the aspect ratio also changes the available resolutions.</aspectTxt>
    <aspectStretchTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Image sizes in the 4x3 format (640x480 etc.) are rescaled from the image sensor's natural 5x4 aspect ratio. This requires a slight vertical compression of the image, but also gives the maximum vertical viewing angle.</aspectStretchTxt>
    <compr1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Compression&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Changing the compression level affects the amount of bandwidth required. Lower compression improves image quality, but uses more bandwidth.</compr1Txt>
    <comprMP4Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: When using bit rate control for H.264/MPEG-4, this setting will define the minimum compression level. The compression level will temporarily increase as and when required.</comprMP4Txt1>
    <comprMP4Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: When using bit rate control for MPEG-4, this setting will define the minimum compression level. The compression level will temporarily increase as and when required.</comprMP4Txt2>
    <comprMP4Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: When using bit rate control for H.264, this setting will define the minimum compression level. The compression level will temporarily increase as and when required.</comprMP4Txt3>
    <compr2Txt type="text" minor="0">The compression level also affects file sizes when saving images. The graph below provides approximate file sizes when saving Motion JPEG images in the</compr2Txt>
    <compr3Txt type="text" minor="0">resolution 320x240.</compr3Txt>
    <compr4Txt type="text" minor="0">CIF resolution (352x240).</compr4Txt>
    <mirror_man_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Mirror image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this option to show the mirrored image in Live View.</mirror_man_Txt>
    <rotTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Rotate image - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;The image can be rotated to suit requirements, by selecting any of the available values.</rotTxt>
    <rotQTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E; that rotating the image 90 or 270 degrees will lower the maximum frame rate.</rotQTxt>
    <autoRotate_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatically rotates the image based on how the Axis product is mounted. Automatic rotation may be useful when, for example, the product is mounted upside down.</autoRotate_Txt>
    <paletteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Palette&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the desired default palette. You can switch palette in the Live View page as well.</paletteTxt>
    <colorEnbTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Color setting&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select either &#x3C;b&#x3E;Color&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Black &#x26; White&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Black &#x26; White uses less bandwidth than Color.</colorEnbTxt>
    <subTitle_stream_Txt type="text" minor="0">Video Stream</subTitle_stream_Txt>
    <lmtFPS1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Maximum frame rate -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; To avoid bandwidth problems on the network, the frame rate allowed to each viewer can be &#x3C;b&#x3E;Limited to&#x3C;/b&#x3E; a fixed amount. Alternatively, the frame rate can be set as &#x3C;b&#x3E;Unlimited&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, which means the</lmtFPS1Txt>
    <lmtFPS2Txt type="text" minor="0">always delivers the highest frame rate possible under the current conditions.</lmtFPS2Txt>
    <lmtFPSNoteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: when using 50 or 60 fps mode, the de-interlacing parameter in &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Audio &#x3E; Camera Settings &#x3E; Video Input&#x3C;/b&#x3E; must be set to either Adaptive Interpolation or Motion Adaptive Interpolation.</lmtFPSNoteTxt>
    <lmtFPSNoteTxt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: for fps values higher than 30, the de-interlacing parameter in &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Audio &#x3E; Camera Settings &#x3E; Video Input&#x3C;/b&#x3E; must be set to either Adaptive Interpolation or Motion Adaptive Interpolation.</lmtFPSNoteTxt-1>
    <subTitle_overlay_Txt type="text" minor="0">Overlay Settings</subTitle_overlay_Txt>
    <ovlImgTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include overlay image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This option places an overlay image in the video image. When enabling this in the image settings &#x3C;i&#x3E;for the event type&#x3C;/i&#x3E;, any position coordinates entered in the global settings will automatically be used.</ovlImgTxt>
    <ovlImgTxt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include overlay image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This option places an overlay image in the video image.</ovlImgTxt-1>
    <ovlImgNTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; The overlay to use must first be selected in &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Audio - Overlay Image.&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</ovlImgNTxt>
   <ovlImgN2Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; The overlay image to use must first be selected in &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video - Overlay Image.&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</ovlImgN2Txt>
    <ovlHlpPlacementTxt type="text" minor="0">To place the overlay image at specific coordinates in the live view image, check &#x3C;b&#x3E;Include overlay image at the coordinates&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and enter the &#x3C;b&#x3E;X&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and &#x3C;b&#x3E;Y&#x3C;/b&#x3E; coordinates.</ovlHlpPlacementTxt>
    <ovlImgNTranspTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; See also the &#x3C;a HREF='transparency_h.shtml'&#x3E;Transparency&#x3C;/a&#x3E; settings.</ovlImgNTranspTxt>
    <ovlDTTTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Three text elements can be included in the video image. These are all included on one line and are as follows:</ovlDTTTxt1>
    <ovlDTTTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include date&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The format for the date display will be as configured in the &#x3C;a href='date_h.shtml'&#x3E;Date &#x26; Time&#x3C;/a&#x3E; settings in the System Options.</ovlDTTTxt2>
    <ovlDTTTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include time&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The time format will also be as configured in the Date &#x26; Time settings in the System Options.</ovlDTTTxt3>
    <ovlDTTTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include text&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter your own text in the field provided.</ovlDTTTxt4>
    <ovlOwnTxt type="text" minor="0">Alternatively, this field can be used to display various information types and formats, by entering special format strings, as described in &#x3C;a href='filenames_h.shtml'&#x3E;File Naming &#x26; Date/Time Formats.&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</ovlOwnTxt>
    <textOverSizeTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Text overlay size&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: select the size of the overlay text from the drop-down list.</textOverSizeTxt>
    <bgColorTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Text color and Text background color&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Set how the text and/or background are displayed. The options for text are black or white only, whereas the background can also be set as semi-transparent or transparent.</bgColorTxt>
    <ovlPlcTxt type="text" minor="0">Select placement of these items at the &#x3C;b&#x3E;top&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;bottom&#x3C;/b&#x3E; of the image.</ovlPlcTxt>
    <bgColorNoteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Overlay images and transparent text backgrounds are not available in Overview mode.</bgColorNoteTxt>
    <tabDirection_Txt type="text" minor="0">Direction</tabDirection_Txt>
    <subTitle_diradj_Txt type="text" minor="0">Direction Adjustment</subTitle_diradj_Txt>
    <subTitle_diradjset_Txt type="text" minor="0">This tab provides the tools to adjust the camera view to the position that is of interest to the operator. Use the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Pan/Tilt&#x3C;/b&#x3E; bar to adjust the direction of the camera view until you are satisfied with the results, the settings are automatically saved.</subTitle_diradjset_Txt>
    <subTitle_diradjset_1Txt type="text" minor="0">Check the box &#x3C;b&#x3E;Lock this position&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to lock the camera view to the current set position and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Save&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to save the settings. Note that the Pan/Tilt bar will be disabled until you uncheck the Lock this position box again.</subTitle_diradjset_1Txt>
    <subTitle_diradjset_2Txt type="text" minor="0">Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Reset&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button to return to previous settings. Note that, resetting will change all settings except Pan / Tilt to the previous setting.</subTitle_diradjset_2Txt>
    <subTitle_diradjnote_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; The Direction tab is only available in Panorama, Double Panorama and Quad View modes.</subTitle_diradjnote_Txt>
    <tabaudio_Txt type="text" minor="0">Audio</tabaudio_Txt>
    <subTitle_audioenb_Txt type="text" minor="0">Enable Audio</subTitle_audioenb_Txt>
    <audio1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable audio&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to enable audio functionality.</audio1Txt>
    <audio2Txt type="text" minor="0">From the drop-down list select the audio channel to be used with the current video channel.</audio2Txt>
    <audio3Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Audio support must be also enabled under &#x3C;b&#x3E;System Options&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Security&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio Support&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</audio3Txt>
    <audioEncTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Current Audio Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The settings chosen under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; will be shown here.</audioEncTxt>
    <subTitle_Encoder_settings_Txt type="text" minor="0">Encoder Settings</subTitle_Encoder_settings_Txt>
    <gOVlength1_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Length&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The GOV structure describes the composition of the H.264/MPEG-4 video stream which consists of 2 image forms, I-images and P-images. An I-image is a complete image, whereas a P-image is only the differences in the image as compared with the previous image.</gOVlength1_Txt1>
    <gOVlength2_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Length&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The GOV structure describes the composition of the H.264 video stream which consists of 2 image forms, I-images and P-images. An I-image is a complete image, whereas a P-image is only the differences in the image as compared with the previous image.</gOVlength2_Txt1>
    <gOVlength3_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Length&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The GOV structure describes the composition of the MPEG-4 video stream which consists of 2 image forms, I-images and P-images. An I-image is a complete image, whereas a P-image is only the differences in the image as compared with the previous image.</gOVlength3_Txt1>
    <gOVlength_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">The GOV length determines how many P-images are sent before the next complete I-image is sent.</gOVlength_Txt2>
    <gOVlength_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">Setting the GOV-length to a higher value saves considerably on bandwidth but if there is congestion on the network, there may be noticeable decay in the video quality. Setting the GOV-length to a lower value increases the video quality, in this case.</gOVlength_Txt3>
    <encrSettH264Prof1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;H.264 profile&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select one of the sub profiles described below from the drop-down list.</encrSettH264Prof1Txt>
    <encrSettH264Prof2Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Baseline&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select this option if the client does not support CABAC entropy coding.</encrSettH264Prof2Txt>
    <encrSettH264Prof3Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Main&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This option uses CABAC and provides a better compression with maintained video quality. It also requires a larger amount of processing power to decode.</encrSettH264Prof3Txt>
		<encrSettH264Prof4Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;High&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Provides higher compression than both Main and Baseline profiles, but requires more processing power to decode. High profile supports 8x8 blocks which reduce the bitrate further compared to the Main profile.</encrSettH264Prof4Txt>
    <mpeg4_help_cyclic_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Cyclic refresh&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Cyclic refresh gives a smoother bit rate and can be useful if there is limited bandwidth available.</mpeg4_help_cyclic_Txt>
    <subTitle_bitratecontrol_Txt type="text" minor="0">Bit Rate Control</subTitle_bitratecontrol_Txt>
    <bitrate_intro_helpTxt type="text" minor="0">Adjusting the maximum bit rate and setting it to variable or constant is a good way of controlling the bandwidth used by the MPEG-4 video stream.</bitrate_intro_helpTxt>
    <maxbitrate_helpTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Leaving the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Maximum bit rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; as unlimited will provide consistently good image quality, but at the expense of increased bandwidth usage whenever there is more activity in the image.</maxbitrate_helpTxt1>
    <maxbitrate_helpTxt2 type="text" minor="0">Limiting the bit rate to a defined value will prevent excessive bandwidth usage, but images will be lost when the limit is exceeded.</maxbitrate_helpTxt2>
    <maxbitrate_Note2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: A a maximum bit rate can be used for both variable and constant bit rates.</maxbitrate_Note2>
    <cbr_vbr_helpTxt type="text" minor="0">The bit rate type can be set as &#x3C;b&#x3E;Variable Bit Rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (VBR) or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Constant Bit Rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (CBR). VBR will adjust the bit rate according to the images' complexity, and thus uses a lot of bandwidth for a lot of activity in the image and less when the monitored area is quiet.</cbr_vbr_helpTxt>
    <cbr_helpTxt type="text" minor="0">When using CBR you can set a fixed &#x3C;b&#x3E;Target bit rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, which will ensure that the level of bandwidth consumed is predictable.</cbr_helpTxt>
    <cbr_helpTxt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Constant bit rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; allows the operator to set the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Target bit rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; value that will be used by the Axis product in calculating the bit rate that should be applied to the video stream. CBR is mostly suitable when bandwidth is limited, since the operator can predict the level of bandwidth consumed. Note that, the bit rate applied to the video stream may be slightly above the set target bit rate depending on the situation the product operates in.</cbr_helpTxt-1>
    <cbr_helpTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Priority&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - As the bit rate would usually need to increase for increased image activity, but cannot when CBR is selected, the frame rate and image quality will both be affected negatively. To go some of the way towards compensating for this, it is possible to prioritize either the frame rate or the image quality whenever the bit rate would normally need to be increased. Not setting a priority means the frame rate and image quality will be affected approximately equally.</cbr_helpTxt2>
		<mbr_vbr_helpTxt type="text" minor="0">The bit rate type can be set as &#x3C;b&#x3E;Variable Bit Rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (VBR) or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Maximum Bit Rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (MBR). VBR will adjust the 
bit rate according to the images' complexity, and thus uses a lot of bandwidth for a lot of activity in the image and less when the monitored area is quiet. Note that, the maximum bitrate allowed is set to 50 Mbits/s to ensure compliance with H.264 level.</mbr_vbr_helpTxt>
		<mbr_helpTxt type="text" minor="0">When using MBR you can set a fixed &#x3C;b&#x3E;Target bit rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, which will ensure that the level of bandwidth consumed is predictable. The bit rate will try to stay as close as possible under the target but may bounce up and down within the set target. When there is a lot of activity (so higher bandwidth need) the rate controller will degrade the quality (image quality and/or framerate) to maintain a bandwidth under this target.</mbr_helpTxt>
		<cbr_helpTxt2-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Priority&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - As the bit rate would usually need to increase for increased image activity, but cannot when MBR is selected, the frame rate and image quality will both be affected negatively. To go some of the way towards compensating for this, it is possible to prioritize either the frame rate or the image quality whenever the bit rate would normally need to be increased. The image quality is related to the compression level setting, the lower is the compression the better is the possible image quality, see Compression. Not setting a priority means the frame rate and image quality will be affected approximately equally.</cbr_helpTxt2-1>
    <tabmpeg_Txt type="text" minor="0">MJPEG</tabmpeg_Txt>
    <subTitle_sizecontrol_Txt type="text" minor="0">Frame Size Control</subTitle_sizecontrol_Txt>
    <framesizeTxt type="text" minor="0">In some situation the image size may get quite large due to low light or complex scenery. Adjusting the maximum frame size is a good way of controlling the bandwidth and storage used by the MJPEG video stream in these situations. Leaving the  frame size at &#x3C;b&#x3E;Default&#x3C;/b&#x3E; will provide consistently good image quality at the expense of increased bandwidth and storage usage during low light. Limiting the frame size will prevent excessive bandwidth and storage usage, but image quality will suffer. To prevent increase in bandwidth and storage usage, the maximum frame size should be set to an optimal amount.</framesizeTxt>
    <framesizeNoteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: The maximum frame size allowed increases compression in order to maintain a low frame size starting at the compression value set under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Image settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Image Appearance&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Compression&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. When compression is 100, the image cannot be made smaller. You may also need to adjust the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Resolution&#x3C;/b&#x3E; setting if a smaller frame size is needed.</framesizeNoteTxt>
  </videostream_h>
</language_xml>
