<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<enter_exit_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/EnterExit Detector</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Enter/Exit Detector</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">The Enter/Exit detector page provides tools to define a virtual area that the camera should trigger an alarm if for example an object has entered or exited.</intro_Txt>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Enter/Exit Detector Setup</subTitle1Txt>
		<ptz_preset_Txt type="text" minor="0">To setup the Enter/Exit detector, define the below configuration options as required.</ptz_preset_Txt>
		<remove_ptz_preset_Txt type="text" minor="0">To remove a detector configuration, select it in the drop-down list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</remove_ptz_preset_Txt>
		<define_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Define&#x3C;/b&#x3E;:</define_Txt>
		<define_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Area of interest&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is a virtual area that is defined to detect moving objects entering a defined area and may trigger a camera to generate an action. To define a new area of interest, place the mouse pointer inside the video image, drag to create a shape on the area of interest and release the mouse. Note that, it is possible to define only 1 area of interest.</define_Txt1>
		<define_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Object size&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Defines the size of the objects to be detected. The product will detect any object whose size falls within the minimum (blue rectangle) and maximum (white rectangle) range.</define_Txt2>
		<define_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exclude area&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is a virtual area that is defined whenever it is required to mask a part of an area of interest to avoid unwanted triggering of camera action. It is defined when swaying objects such trees or flags are inside the area of interest. To define a new exclude area, place the mouse pointer inside the video image, drag to create a rectangle and release the mouse. Note that, it is possible to define a maximum of 4 exclude areas.</define_Txt3>
		<sensitivity_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this slidebar to define how sensitive the detection should be.</sensitivity_Txt>
		<drawingOpacity_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Drawing Opacity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this slidebar to define how transparent the area of interest shape should be. Note that, this change will not be saved.</drawingOpacity_Txt>
		<removeShape_Txt type="text" minor="0">To remove the area of interest, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove shapes&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</removeShape_Txt>
	</enter_exit_h>





	<fence_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Fence Detector</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Fence Detector</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">The fence detector page provides tools to define a virtual line that will detect objects that move across it, in this scenario, the Axis product will automatically trigger an event.</intro_Txt>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Fence Detector Setup</subTitle1Txt>
		<ptz_preset_Txt type="text" minor="0">To setup the fence detector, define the below configuration options as required.</ptz_preset_Txt>
		<remove_ptz_preset_Txt type="text" minor="0">To remove a detector configuration, select it in the drop-down list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</remove_ptz_preset_Txt>
		<define_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Define&#x3C;/b&#x3E;:</define_Txt>
		<define_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Area of interest&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is a virtual line that is defined to detect objects moving across it and trigger a camera to generate an action. To define a new line, place the mouse pointer inside the video image, drag to create a shaped line and release the mouse. An area with red color will be created, Left and Right represent directions that an object might cross the line from. Note that, it is possible to define only 1 line..</define_Txt1>
		<define_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Object size&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Defines the size of the objects to be detected. The product will detect any object whose size falls within the minimum (blue rectangle) and maximum (white rectangle) range.</define_Txt2>
		<define_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exclude area&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is a virtual area that is defined whenever it is required to mask a part of an area of the line to avoid unwanted triggering of camera action. It is defined when swaying objects such trees or flags are inside the line of interest. To define a new exclude area, place the mouse pointer inside the video image, drag to create a rectangle and release the mouse. Note that, it is possible to define a maximum of 4 exclude areas.</define_Txt3>
		<sensitivity_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this slidebar to define how sensitive the detection should be.</sensitivity_Txt>
		<drawingOpacity_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Drawing Opacity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this slidebar to define how transparent the area of interest shape should be. Note that, this change will not be saved.</drawingOpacity_Txt>
		<removeShape_Txt type="text" minor="0">To remove the area of interest, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove shapes&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</removeShape_Txt>
	</fence_h>





	<object_counter_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Object Counter</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Object Counter</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">The object counter page provides tools to define a virtual line that will keep track of objects that move across it and provide a count.</intro_Txt>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Object Counter Setup</subTitle1Txt>
		<ptz_preset_Txt type="text" minor="0">To setup the object counter detector, define the below configuration options as required..</ptz_preset_Txt>
		<remove_ptz_preset_Txt type="text" minor="0">To remove a detector configuration, select it in the drop-down list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</remove_ptz_preset_Txt>
		<define_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Define&#x3C;/b&#x3E;:</define_Txt>
		<define_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Area of interest&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is a virtual line that is defined to detect objects moving across it and keep count. To define a new line, place the mouse pointer inside the video image, drag to create a shaped line and release the mouse. An area with red color will be created, Left and Right represent directions that an object might cross the line from. Note that, it is possible to define only 1 line.</define_Txt1>
		<define_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Object size&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Defines the size of the objects to be detected. The product will detect any object whose size falls within the minimum (blue rectangle) and maximum (white rectangle) range.</define_Txt2>
		<define_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exclude area&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is a virtual area that is defined whenever it is required to mask a part of an area of the line to avoid unwanted triggering of camera action. It is defined when swaying objects such trees or flags are inside the line of interest. To define a new exclude area, place the mouse pointer inside the video image, drag to create a rectangle and release the mouse. Note that, it is possible to define a maximum of 4 exclude areas.</define_Txt3>
		<sensitivity_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this slidebar to define how sensitive the detection should be.</sensitivity_Txt>
		<drawingOpacity_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Drawing Opacity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this slidebar to define how transparent the area of interest shape should be. Note that, this change will not be saved.</drawingOpacity_Txt>
		<removeShape_Txt type="text" minor="0">To remove the area of interest, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove shapes&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</removeShape_Txt>
	</object_counter_h>





	<object_removal_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Object Removed</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Object Removed</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">The object removed page provides tools to define a detection area around an object of interest, that the camera should trigger an alarm if for example that object has been removed.</intro_Txt>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Object Removed Setup</subTitle1Txt>
		<ptz_preset_Txt type="text" minor="0">To setup the object removed detector, define the below configuration options as required.</ptz_preset_Txt>
		<remove_ptz_preset_Txt type="text" minor="0">To remove a detector configuration, select it in the drop-down list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</remove_ptz_preset_Txt>
		<define_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Define&#x3C;/b&#x3E;:</define_Txt>
		<define_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Area of interest&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is a virtual area that is defined around an object to detect if that object has been removed from the scene and may trigger a camera to generate an action. To define a new area of interest, place the mouse pointer inside the video image, drag to create a shape around the object and release the mouse. Note that, it is possible to define only 1 area of interest.</define_Txt1>
		<define_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Object size&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Defines the size of the objects to be detected. The product will detect any object whose size falls within the minimum (blue rectangle) and maximum (white rectangle) range.</define_Txt2>
		<define_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exclude area&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is a virtual area that is defined whenever it is required to mask a part of an area of interest to avoid unwanted triggering of camera action. It is defined when swaying objects such trees or flags are inside the area of interest. . To define a new exclude area, place the mouse pointer inside the video image, drag to create a rectangle around the object and release the mouse. Note that, it is possible to define a maximum of 4 exclude areas.</define_Txt3>
		<sensitivity_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this slidebar to define how sensitive the detection should be.</sensitivity_Txt>
		<drawingOpacity_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Drawing Opacity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this slidebar to define how transparent the area of interest shape should be. Note that, this change will not be saved.</drawingOpacity_Txt>
		<removeShape_Txt type="text" minor="0">To remove the area of interest, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove shapes&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</removeShape_Txt>
	</object_removal_h>
</language_xml>
