<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<audioclip_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Audio Clip List</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Audio Clip List</titleTxt>
		<introTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Audio clips can be played when an event occurs or manually from the Live View page. Audio clips are created either by recording sound using a microphone or by uploading a sound file to the Axis product. Listed here are the audio clips that have been added. Follow the instructions below to add new clips, play, download, modify and remove clips.</introTxt1>
		<introTxt2 type="text" minor="0">Audio clips can be played when an event occurs or manually from the Live View page. Audio clips are created either by recording sound using the product's microphone or by uploading a sound file to the Axis product. Listed here are the audio clips that have been added to the product. Follow the instructions below to add new clips, play, download, modify and remove clips.</introTxt2>
		<introTxt2-1 type="text" minor="0">Audio clips can be played when an event occurs. Audio clips are created either by recording sound using the product's microphone or by uploading a sound file to the Axis product. Listed here are the audio clips that have been added to the product. Follow the instructions below to add new clips, play, download, modify and remove clips.</introTxt2-1>
		<subTitle_appearance_Txt type="text" minor="0">Add a new audio clip</subTitle_appearance_Txt>
		<listintroTxt type="text" minor="0">New audio clips can be recorded or uploaded to the product. Click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button. The dialog expands with two choices &#x3C;b&#x3E;Record&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and &#x3C;b&#x3E;Upload&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</listintroTxt>
		<micro1Txt type="text" minor="0">To record a new clip using a microphone:</micro1Txt>
		<micro2Txt type="text" minor="0">To record a new clip using the product's microphone:</micro2Txt>
		<listTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Select the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Record&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button.</listTxt1>
		<listTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Name&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter a descriptive name.</listTxt2>
		<listTxt3 type="text" minor="0">If the recording should not start at once upon clicking the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Record...&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button, enter the number of seconds to wait before recording actually starts.</listTxt3>
		<listTxt4 type="text" minor="0">Enter the number of seconds to record.</listTxt4>
		<listTxt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; The number of seconds entered in each of the field &#x3C;b&#x3E;wait for&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and &#x3C;b&#x3E;recording for&#x3C;/b&#x3E; should not be greater than</listTxt5>
		<listTxt6 type="text" minor="0">seconds. To increase the maximum values for these fields please set the value for System.BoaKeepAliveTimeout parameter to a higher number.</listTxt6>
		<listTxt7 type="text" minor="0">Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Record...&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</listTxt7>
		<listTxt8 type="text" minor="0">The status LED on the product will flash amber while waiting and flash red while recording.</listTxt8>
		<listNoteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; You may want to adjust the Input gain under Audio Settings for best audio quality.</listNoteTxt>
		<listTxt10 type="text" minor="0">To upload a file from a local hard drive or network disk, select the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Upload&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button and click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Browse&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button. Navigate to the desired file and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Upload...&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</listTxt10>
		<filetypeTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Allowed audio clips for uploading are:</filetypeTxt1>
		<filetypeTxt2 type="text" minor="0">.au G.711 u-law, 8-bit, mono (8, 16 KHz)</filetypeTxt2>
		<filetypeTxt3 type="text" minor="0">.wav PCM, 16-bit, mono (8, 16, 32 KHz)</filetypeTxt3>
		<subTitle_buttons_Txt type="text" minor="0">Working with audio clips</subTitle_buttons_Txt>
		<workTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Play&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - To hear a clip play, select an audio clip and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Play&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</workTxt1>
		<workTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Download&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - To download a recording to a hard drive or network disk, select it and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Download&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</workTxt2>
		<workTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Modify&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Change the name of the audio clip.</workTxt3>
		<workTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the audio clip to delete and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</workTxt4>
	</audioclip_h>
</language_xml>
