<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<cameraTampering_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Camera Tampering</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Camera Tampering</titleTxt>
		<overview_Txt type="text" minor="0">The camera tampering application generates an alarm whenever the camera is repositioned, or when the lens is covered, sprayed or severely put out of focus. The tampering application will only become active and ready after the camera has not moved for at least 10 seconds. During this period the application sets up a &#x3C;b&#x3E;Scene Model&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to use as a comparison to detect tampering in current images.</overview_Txt>
		<sceneModelPTZ_Txt type="text" minor="0">This means that PTZ movements will also reset the application - if the PTZ movements are too frequent there will be no tampering alarms. PTZ should be used sparingly when camera tampering is enabled.</sceneModelPTZ_Txt>
		<sceneModel2_Txt type="text" minor="0">For the scene model to be set up properly make sure that the camera is in focus, the lighting conditions are correct, and the camera is not pointed at a scene that lacks contours, for example a blank wall.</sceneModel2_Txt>
		<action_rule_link type="text" minor="0">Camera Tampering can also be used as a condition to trigger Action Rules. See &#x3C;a href='action_rule_setup_h.shtml'&#x3E;Action Rule Setup&#x3C;/a&#x3E; for more information.</action_rule_link>
		<subTitle_param_Txt type="text" minor="0">Settings</subTitle_param_Txt>
		<subTitle_tampPeriod_Txt type="text" minor="0">Tampering Period</subTitle_tampPeriod_Txt>
		<subTitle_darkImages_Txt type="text" minor="0">Dark Images</subTitle_darkImages_Txt>
		<subTitle_shockDetection_Txt type="text" minor="0">Shock Detection</subTitle_shockDetection_Txt>
		<duration_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Minimum duration - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;This parameter sets the minimum tampering period, i.e. an alarm will not be triggered until this period has elapsed, even if the tampering conditions are otherwise met. This can help prevent false alarms for known conditions that affect the image.</duration_Txt>
		<dark_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Alarm for dark images - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;If the camera lens is sprayed and the image is darkened, it will not be possible to distinguish this from other situations where the same effect is seen, i.e. when the lighting conditions change.</dark_Txt1>
		<dark_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">When this parameter is enabled, alarms will be generated for all cases where the image turns dark or the lens is sprayed. If not enabled, no alarm will be sent.</dark_Txt2>
		<save_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">After making these settings, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Save&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</save_Txt1>
		<save_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: When &#x3C;b&#x3E;Alarm for dark images&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is enabled, it may take longer for an alarm to be generated than the amount of time that is entered under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Minimum duration&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</save_Txt2>
		<shockDetection_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable shock detection - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;The Axis product can detect if it has been tilted or hit. Shock detection can be used, for example, to generate an alarm if the product's mounting position changes due to intentional or unintentional rotation or when the product is hit.</shockDetection_Txt>
		<shockSensitivity_Txt type="text" minor="0">Use the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Shock sensitivity slidebar&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to adjust the sensitivity level at which the product should send an alarm upon being displaced. Low sensitivity value implies that, the product will generate an alarm only if a big displacement occurs.</shockSensitivity_Txt>
	</cameraTampering_h>



	<shockDetection_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Shock Detection</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Shock Detection</titleTxt>
		<subTitle_settings_Txt type="text" minor="0">Settings</subTitle_settings_Txt>
		<enableShockDetection_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable shock detection&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The Axis product can detect if it has been hit. Shock detection can be used, for example, to generate an alarm if the product is hit.</enableShockDetection_Txt>
		<shockSensitivity_Txt type="text" minor="1">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Shock sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use the shock sensitivity slidebar to adjust the sensitivity level at which the product should send an alarm upon being hit. Low sensitivity value implies that the product will generate an alarm only if a big hit occurs.</shockSensitivity_Txt>
	</shockDetection_h>
</language_xml>
