<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<layout_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Live View Layout</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Live View Layout</titleTxt>
		<general1_Txt type="text" minor="0">The main application page for the Axis product can be altered to suit your own requirements, by customizing the features on the Live View page.</general1_Txt>
		<general2_Txt type="text" minor="0">Select whether to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Use Axis look&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for the whole product, or select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Use Custom settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. For the latter, settings are made by clicking the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Configure&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button. &#x3C;a href='personalSettings_setup_h.shtml'&#x3E;More on custom settings&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</general2_Txt>
		<subTitle_default_view_Txt type="text" minor="0">Default Live View Video</subTitle_default_view_Txt>
		<default_view_Txt type="text" minor="0">To change the video source displayed as the default on the Live View page, select the individual source (or the quad stream) here.</default_view_Txt>
		<subTitle4aTxta type="text" minor="0">Stream Profile</subTitle4aTxta>
		<subTitle4aTxtb type="text" minor="0">Default Video Format</subTitle4aTxtb>
		<streamprofile_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream profile&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the stream profile from the drop-down list to use for the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Live View&#x3C;/b&#x3E; page. Listed are the standard stream profiles as well as the ones created under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x3C;/b&#x3E;</streamprofile_Txt>
		<streamprofile_add_audio_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;&#x26; Audio &#x3C;/b&#x3E;</streamprofile_add_audio_Txt>
		<streamprofile_end_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream Profiles&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</streamprofile_end_Txt>
		<videoformat_Txt type="text" minor="0">Select the video format to use for the&#x3C;b&#x3E;Live View&#x3C;/b&#x3E; page.</videoformat_Txt>
		<mJPEGTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Motion JPEG&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Delivers a high quality video stream, from which individual images can be extracted and saved</mJPEGTxt>
		<mPEG4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;MPEG-4&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Video quality is comparable to Motion JPEG, but requires much less bandwidth</mPEG4>
		<h264Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;H.264&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Better image quality with less bandwidth</h264Txt>
		<qualityTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Quality&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Best image quality and full frame rate</qualityTxt>
		<balancedTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Balanced&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Medium image quality and frame rate</balancedTxt>
		<bandTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Bandwidth&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Low bandwidth with medium image quality</bandTxt>
		<mobileTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Mobile&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Mobile device settings</mobileTxt>
		<showTxt type="text" minor="0">Check &#x3C;b&#x3E;Show stream profile selection&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to place a stream profile drop-down list in Live View enabling the user to choose a profile for viewing.</showTxt>
		<showPalTxt type="text" minor="0">Check &#x3C;b&#x3E;Show palette selection&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to place a palette drop-down list in Live View enabling the user to choose a palette for viewing.</showPalTxt>
		<subTitle5Txt type="text" minor="0">Default Viewer</subTitle5Txt>
		<iE_view_Txt type="text" minor="0">When using &#x3C;i&#x3E;Microsoft Internet Explorer (IE)&#x3C;/i&#x3E; in Windows, select your preferred method of viewing moving images. The options are:</iE_view_Txt>
		<view_IEhm_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;AMC (ActiveX)&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is the best choice for fast image updating in Internet Explorer for all stream profiles (MPEG-4, H.264 and Motion JPEG), but might not be possible on computers that have restrictions on the installation of additional software.</view_IEhm_Txt>
		<view_IEh_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;AMC (ActiveX)&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is the best choice for fast image updating in Internet Explorer for all stream profiles (H.264 and Motion JPEG), but might not be possible on computers that have restrictions on the installation of additional software.</view_IEh_Txt>
		<view_IEm_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;AMC (ActiveX)&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is the best choice for fast image updating in Internet Explorer for all stream profiles (MPEG-4 and Motion JPEG), but might not be possible on computers that have restrictions on the installation of additional software.</view_IEm_Txt>
		<iE_AMC_check_Txt type="text" minor="0">When accessing the product with Internet Explorer for the first time, your computer is checked to see if AMC is already installed. If not found, or if the version found is older than the version supported in the product, you will be prompted to install the latest version.</iE_AMC_check_Txt>
		<view_qtHM_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;QuickTime&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - For use with H.264 and MPEG-4 only.</view_qtHM_Txt>
		<view_qtH_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;QuickTime&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - For use with H.264.</view_qtH_Txt>
		<view_qt3_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;QuickTime&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - For use with MPEG-4 only.</view_qt3_Txt>
		<view_qt4_Txt type="text" minor="0">Note that in the settings for &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Image &#x3E; Advanced &#x3E; MPEG-4&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video object type&#x3C;/b&#x3E; must be set to &#x3C;i&#x3E;Simple&#x3C;/i&#x3E;.</view_qt4_Txt>
		<view_javaAudio_Txta type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Java applet&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - A slower imaging alternative to AMC for Motion JPEG, this alternative uses a Java applet to update the images in IE. AAC digital audio encoding cannot be used with Java applet. See &#x3C;a href='audio_settings_h.shtml'&#x3E;Audio Settings&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</view_javaAudio_Txta>
		<view_javaAudio_Txtb type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Java applet&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - A slower imaging alternative to AMC for Motion JPEG, this alternative uses a Java applet to update the images in IE.</view_javaAudio_Txtb>
		<java_note1_1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E; that when this alternative is selected, external video sources will not be available on the Live View page</java_note1_1Txt>
		<java_note2_Txt type="text" minor="0">, and audio will be mono-directional only (to the client).</java_note2_Txt>
		<java_note3_Txt type="text" minor="0">.</java_note3_Txt>
		<view_still_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Still Image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Displays still images only (Motion JPEG). Hit the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Refresh&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button in your browser to view a new image.</view_still_Txt1>
		<others_view_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">When using any other browser than Internet Explorer, select your preferred method of viewing images. The available options are:</others_view_Txt1>
		<others_view_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Server Push &#x3C;/b&#x3E;- With this method, the product maintains and controls an open HTTP connection to the browser and sends data as and when required, for as long as required.</others_view_Txt2>
		<others_view_Txt2-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Server Push &#x3C;/b&#x3E;- With this method, the product maintains and controls an open HTTP connection to the browser and sends data as and when required, for as long as required. Note that it may not be possible to get audio when server push is used as a default viewer in Firefox browser.</others_view_Txt2-1>
		<view_qtHM_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;QuickTime&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - For use with H.264 and MPEG-4 only.</view_qtHM_Txt2>
		<view_qtH_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;QuickTime&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - For use with H.264.</view_qtH_Txt2>
		<view_qt3_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;QuickTime&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - For use with MPEG-4 only.</view_qt3_Txt2>
		<view_qt4_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Note that in the settings for &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Image &#x3E; Advanced &#x3E; MPEG-4&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video object type&#x3C;/b&#x3E; must be set to &#x3C;i&#x3E;Simple&#x3C;/i&#x3E;.</view_qt4_Txt2>
		<view_other_java_Txta type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Java applet&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This alternative uses a Java applet to update the images in the browser. No download required. AAC digital audio encoding cannot be used with Java applet. See &#x3C;a href='audio_settings_h.shtml'&#x3E;Audio Settings&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</view_other_java_Txta>
		<java_audio_note1_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E; that when this alternative is selected, external video sources will not be available on the Live View page</java_audio_note1_Txt>
		<java_audio_note1_add_audio_Txt type="text" minor="0">, and audio will be mono-directional only (to the client)</java_audio_note1_add_audio_Txt>
		<java_audio_note1_end_Txt type="text" minor="0">.</java_audio_note1_end_Txt>
		<java_note1_2Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E; that when this alternative is selected, external video sources will not be available on the Live View page.</java_note1_2Txt>
		<view_other_java_Txtb type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Java applet&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This alternative uses a Java applet to update the images in the browser. No download required.</view_other_java_Txtb>
		<view_still_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Still Image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Displays still images only. Hit the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Refresh&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button in your browser to view a new image.</view_still_Txt2>
		<subTitle4bTxt type="text" minor="0">Viewer Settings</subTitle4bTxt>
		<show_AAC_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable AAC decoder installation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to enable the installation of the AAC decoder included with the AXIS Media Control. To prevent the installation of unlicensed copies uncheck this box.</show_AAC_Txt>
		<show_toolbar_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show viewer toolbar&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to display the viewer toolbar under the image in your browser. The toolbar provides various controls for e.g. pausing the video stream, switching to full screen mode, etc.</show_toolbar_Txt>
		<mPEG_install_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable MPEG-4 decoder installation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - By checking/unchecking this box, the administrator can enable or disable the installation of the MPEG-4 decoder included with AMC. This is used to prevent the installation of unlicensed copies. Further decoder licenses can be purchased from your Axis dealer.</mPEG_install_Txt>
		<h264_install_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable H.264 decoder installation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - By checking/unchecking this box, the administrator can enable or disable the installation of the H.264 decoder included with AMC. This is used to prevent the installation of unlicensed copies. Further decoder licenses can be purchased from your Axis dealer.</h264_install_Txt>
		<relCross_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show crosshair in PTZ joystick mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This cross indicates the center of the image when viewing the video stream in PTZ joystick mode.</relCross_Txt>
		<defaultjoystick_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Use PTZ joystick mode as default&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enabling this sets the PTZ mode to joystick. The mode can be changed temporarily on the PTZ Control Panel, but will default to joystick if this is selected.</defaultjoystick_Txt>
		<mPEG_rec_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable recording button&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enabling this button allows the user to start a recording directly from the Live View page. The recording is saved in the folder specified in the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Recording&#x3C;/b&#x3E; tab in the AMC Control Applet. Note that this button is only available when viewing with AMC.</mPEG_rec_Txt>
		<sVG_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show IV SVG data in image stream&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The currently running IV module can display data directly in the video image. Check this box to enable.</sVG_Txt>
		<subTitle3Txt type="text" minor="0">Action Buttons</subTitle3Txt>
		<trigger_buttons_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show manual trigger button&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - When displayed on the Live View page, clicking these buttons (On and Off) manually starts and stops all events that are configured to trigger in this way.</trigger_buttons_Txt>
		<snapshot_button_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show snapshot button&#x3C;/b&#x3E;  - Enabling the display of the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Snapshot&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button allows users to save a Motion JPEG snapshot from the video stream by clicking the button. This button is mainly intended for use with browsers other than Internet Explorer (IE), or when otherwise not using AXIS Media Control (AMC) to view the video stream. AMC provides its own snapshot button.</snapshot_button_Txt>
		<audio_clip_button_Txta type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show audio clip section&#x3C;/b&#x3E;  - Enabling the display of the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio clip&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down box and play button allows users to play a pre-recorded audio clip from the camera. Go to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Audio &#x3E; Audio Clips &#x3C;/b&#x3E; to work with the audio clips.</audio_clip_button_Txta>
		<audio_clip_button_Txtb type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Play audio clip section&#x3C;/b&#x3E;  - Enabling the display of the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio clip&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down box and play button allows users to play a pre-recorded audio clip from the product. Go to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio &#x3E; Audio Clips &#x3C;/b&#x3E; to work with the audio clips.</audio_clip_button_Txtb>
		<autoTrack_buttons_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show autotracking button&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - When displayed on the Live View page, this button (Stop/Start Autotrack) manually stops and starts the autotracking feature. Autotracking detects movement in the camera's field of view and will follow the motion, e.g. a person or vehicle, until it disappears from the monitored area.</autoTrack_buttons_Txt>
		<irillumination_buttons_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show IR illumination&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to make IR Illumination buttons (Activate IR illumination and Deactivate IR illumination) appear on the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Live View&#x3C;/b&#x3E; page. The buttons can be used to manually turn on/off the light, use the slider bar to adjust the intensity of the IR LEDs. Note that the slider bar may not be active, depending on settings in the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Camera Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; page.</irillumination_buttons_Txt>
		<heater_fan_buttons_Txta type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show fan button&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - When displayed on the Live View page, this button manually starts the fan. Set the number of minutes the fan should run when the button is clicked.</heater_fan_buttons_Txta>
		<heater_fan_buttons_Txtb type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show heater button&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - When displayed on the Live View page, this button manually starts the heater. Set the number of minutes the heater should run when the button is clicked.</heater_fan_buttons_Txtb>
		<subTitle2Txt type="text" minor="0">User Defined Links</subTitle2Txt>
		<links_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">To display user-defined links on the Live View page, check the box for &#x3C;b&#x3E;Show custom link&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, give the link a name and then enter the URL to link to. When defining a web link do not remove the 'http://' from the URL address.</links_Txt1>
		<links_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Custom links can be used to e.g. run scripts or activate external devices connected to the server, or they can link to a standard web URL, i.e. to a web page.</links_Txt2>
		<links_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">Custom links defined as &#x3C;b&#x3E;cgi links&#x3C;/b&#x3E; will run e.g. the script in the background, in a hidden frame. Defining the link as a &#x3C;b&#x3E;web link&#x3C;/b&#x3E; will open the link in a new window.</links_Txt3>
		<lightBtnTxt type="text" minor="0">Light Buttons</lightBtnTxt>
		<light_buttons_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">The light source can be controlled directly from the Live View page, by enabling the display of light buttons.</light_buttons_Txt1>
		<light_buttons_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">To enable, select the type of control to use for the light. This can be set as &#x3C;b&#x3E;Pulse&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, where clicking the single button activates the light with the defined Activate and Inactivate actions for the defined period.The pulse time can be set as short as 1/100 second, and as long as 60 seconds.</light_buttons_Txt2>
		<light_buttons_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Active/Inactive&#x3C;/b&#x3E; displays 2 buttons, one for each action.</light_buttons_Txt3>
		<light_buttons_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Slider&#x3C;/b&#x3E; provides a bar where sliding it to the left makes the light dimmer and sliding the bar to the right makes the light brighter.</light_buttons_Txt4>
		<light_buttons_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">For advanced users it is also possible to specify a custom Activate and Inactivate command sequence, using Plain config.</light_buttons_Txt5>
		<subTitleInputTxt type="text" minor="0">Input Ports</subTitleInputTxt>
		<input_ports_Txt type="text" minor="0">Check the boxes to show the status of the Input ports on the product Live View page. Go to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Ports &#x26; Devices&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;I/O Ports&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to configure input ports.</input_ports_Txt>
		<subTitle4Txt type="text" minor="0">Output Buttons</subTitle4Txt>
		<output_buttons_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">An output on the product can be controlled directly from the Live View page, by enabling the display of output buttons.</output_buttons_Txt1>
		<output_buttons_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">To enable, select the type of control to use for the port. This can be set as &#x3C;b&#x3E;Pulse&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, where clicking the single button activates the port for the defined period, or as &#x3C;b&#x3E;Active/Inactive&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, which displays 2 buttons, one for each action. The selected type automatically displays the correct button(s) on the Live View page.</output_buttons_Txt2>
		<output_buttons_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">The pulse time can be set as short as 1/100 second, and as long as 60 seconds.</output_buttons_Txt3>
		<subTitle_extVidTxt type="text" minor="0">External Video Source Setup</subTitle_extVidTxt>
		<ext_video_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">Audio from product can be combined with live video from Axis network cameras and video encoders. When enabled, live video is displayed on the Live View page, for full functionality use Internet Explorer.</ext_video_Txt1>
		<ext_video_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;External Video enabled&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to enable external video on the live view page.</ext_video_Txt2>
		<ext_video_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;IP address&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the IP address of the video source.</ext_video_Txt3>
		<ext_video_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Video format&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select a video format H.264 or MPEG-4. If the camera has both types of video streams choose H.264.</ext_video_Txt4>
		<ext_video_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;User name and Password&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Optionally, enter the video source's user name and password. If no credentials are entered, a login  window will appear when accessing the Live View page. Note that the user name and password are saved on product and are sent unencrypted.</ext_video_Txt5>
		<ext_video_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">To receive synchronized video and audio, it is recommended that the time settings in the product, the video source and the client computer are synchronized with an NTP Server. Go to System Options &#x3E; Date &#x26; Time.</ext_video_Txt6>
	</layout_h>





	<fileUpload_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Upload/Remove Own Web Files</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Upload/Remove Own Web Files</titleTxt>
		<help1Txt1 type="text" minor="0">To use your own files (e.g. web pages and images) as custom settings, they must first be uploaded to the Axis product.</help1Txt1>
		<help1Txt2 type="text" minor="0">To do this, enter the name and path to the file to upload in the field provided. The file might be on e.g. your workstation. As an alternative to entering the path directly, click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Browse&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button and then select the correct file.</help1Txt2>
    <notSupCharTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Only a-z, A-Z, 0-9, . and _ characters can be used in the uploaded file's name.</notSupCharTxt>
		<help3Txt1 type="text" minor="0">Now select the &#x3C;b&#x3E;user level&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for the uploaded file. Setting the user access level means that you have complete control over which files can be viewed by which users.</help3Txt1>
		<help3Txt2 type="text" minor="0">When the file is shown correctly in the text field, click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Upload&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button.</help3Txt2>
		<help4Txt type="text" minor="0">All uploaded files are shown in the list in the lower section of the page. To remove a file, check the box provided next to it and then click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</help4Txt>
	</fileUpload_h>





	<personalSettings_setup_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Custom Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Custom Settings</titleTxt>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">General</subTitle1Txt>
		<help1Txt type="text" minor="0">The main application page for the Axis product can be adapted to suit requirements, by customizing the features on the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Live View&#x3C;/b&#x3E; page or by uploading and using your own custom web page.</help1Txt>
		<subTitle2Txt type="text" minor="0">Upload Own Web Files</subTitle2Txt>
		<help2Txt type="text" minor="0">To upload your own files (web pages or images), click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Upload/Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button. Once this has been done, the files will be available in the drop-down list on this page. &#x3C;a href='fileUpload_h.shtml'&#x3E;Help on uploading files&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</help2Txt>
		<subTitle3Txt type="text" minor="0">Modify the Axis Look</subTitle3Txt>
		<help3Txt1 type="text" minor="0">Most of the items that can be configured will also require you to specify the location for the resource, e.g. the location of the background picture you wish to use.</help3Txt1>
		<help3Txt2 type="text" minor="0">This location may be one of your &#x3C;b&#x3E;Own&#x3C;/b&#x3E; uploaded files, in which case it can be selected from the drop-down list associated with the item, but it may also be an &#x3C;b&#x3E;External&#x3C;/b&#x3E; file located somewhere other than in the product. To use an external file, enter the URL in the field provided.</help3Txt2>
		<help4Txt1 type="text" minor="0">The following settings can be customized:</help4Txt1>
		<help4Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Background color &#x3C;/b&#x3E;- This is the color behind all of the text and images on the page.</help4Txt2>
		<help4Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Text color - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Applies to all text on the page.</help4Txt3>
		<help4Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Background picture&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the URL to the picture.</help4Txt4>
		<help4Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Banner &#x3C;/b&#x3E;- The banner shown at the top of the window.</help4Txt5>
		<help4Txt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Banner link&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - To link the banner to a web address, enter the link here.</help4Txt6>
		<help4Txt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Logo&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The logo for the server.</help4Txt7>
		<help4Txt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Logo link&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the link URL here.</help4Txt8>
		<help4Txt9 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Title&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is the title shown above the video stream.</help4Txt9>
		<help4Txt10 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Description&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This text will be used as a description below the video stream.</help4Txt10>
		<help4Txt11 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show setup link - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Unchecking this link will mean that the setup tools for the product will then only be accessible by entering the full path to the tools in your browser. Please make a note of this address for future use.</help4Txt11>
		<subTitle4Txt type="text" minor="0">Own Home Page</subTitle4Txt>
		<help6Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Use own home page &#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This should be checked to use a previously uploaded web page as the default page. Select the page from the drop-down list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;OK&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</help6Txt>
	</personalSettings_setup_h>
</language_xml>
