<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<video_settings_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Camera Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Camera Settings</titleTxt>
		<alternativePageTitle type="msgAsText" minor="0">Help/Video Source Settings</alternativePageTitle>
		<alternativeTitleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Video Source Settings</alternativeTitleTxt>
		<help1Txt type="text" minor="0">This is where settings for the equipment connected to the video</help1Txt>
		<help2Txt type="text" minor="0">source</help2Txt>
		<help2aTxt type="text" minor="0">sources</help2aTxt>
		<help3Txt type="text" minor="0">on the Axis product are made.</help3Txt>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Image Appearance</subTitle1Txt>
		<help10Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Color level -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Select an appropriate level by entering a value in the range 0-100. Lower values mean less color saturation, while the value 100 gives maximum color saturation.</help10Txt1>
		<help10Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Brightness -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; The image brightness can be adjusted in the range 0-100, where a higher value produces a brighter image.</help10Txt2>
		<help10Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Contrast -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Adjust the image's contrast by raising or lowering the value in this field.</help10Txt3>
		<localContrTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Local contrast -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Applies contrast to a specific area of the image. Use the slidebar to  adjust the image's contrast, where a higher value produces an image with high contrast between dark and light areas.</localContrTxt>
		<sharpnessTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Sharpness -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Controls the amount of sharpening applied to the image. In general, a higher setting will improve the image's sharpness, but at the expense of increased image noise, especially in low light conditions. There may also be image artifacts present around areas with high contrast (e.g. sharp edges). A lower setting reduces the amount of image noise, but makes the image less sharp.</sharpnessTxt>
		<subTitle2Txt type="text" minor="0">Video Input</subTitle2Txt>
		<help4Txt type="text" minor="0">Enter a descriptive &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video source name&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</help4Txt>
		<help5Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Physical connector -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Set the connection type for the video source.</help5Txt>
		<help55Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The product first checks the BNC and then the tele plug connector for a video signal. It will keep checking until it finds a signal from one of the connectors</help55Txt>
		<helpbncTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;BNC&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (composite video) - Connects a standard video camera or other video equipment</helpbncTxt>
		<helptelpubTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Tele plug&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - 2.5 mm connector for covert camera</helptelpubTxt>
		<help11Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;BNC&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (composite video) - connects a standard video camera or other video equipment</help11Txt>
		<help12Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Y/C&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (S-video) - connects an S-video camera or other video equipment,</help12Txt>
		<no_cable_Txt type="text" minor="0">directly via the Y/C connector.</no_cable_Txt>
		<cable_Txt type="text" minor="0">which requires a Y/C to BNC cable - please refer to the user's manual.</cable_Txt>
		<help8aTxt type="text" minor="0">If the product is to be connected in parallel with other equipment, disable the input termination by setting the DIP switch to the right position (OFF). Failure to do so can impair the image quality. This only applies when using the BNC composite video input.</help8aTxt>
		<term_dipTxt type="text" minor="0">When connecting the video source, set the termination DIP switches according to the selected connection type:</term_dipTxt>
		<subTitle4aTxt1 type="text" minor="0">DIP 1</subTitle4aTxt1>
		<subTitle4aTxt2 type="text" minor="0">75 Ohm</subTitle4aTxt2>
		<subTitle4aTxt3 type="text" minor="0">video IN</subTitle4aTxt3>
		<subTitle4aTxt4 type="text" minor="0">termination</subTitle4aTxt4>
		<subTitle4bTxt1 type="text" minor="0">DIP 2</subTitle4bTxt1>
		<subTitle4bTxt2 type="text" minor="0">75 Ohm</subTitle4bTxt2>
		<subTitle4bTxt3 type="text" minor="0">video OUT</subTitle4bTxt3>
		<subTitle4bTxt4 type="text" minor="0">termination</subTitle4bTxt4>
		<subTitle4cTxt1 type="text" minor="0">DIP 3</subTitle4cTxt1>
		<subTitle4cTxt2 type="text" minor="0">Connects video IN to video OUT</subTitle4cTxt2>
		<subTitle4dTxt1 type="text" minor="0">DIP 4</subTitle4dTxt1>
		<subTitle4dTxt2 type="text" minor="0">Not used</subTitle4dTxt2>
		<help6aTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Tele plug&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</help6aTxt1>
		<help6aTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Y/C&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</help6aTxt2>
		<help6bTxt type="text" minor="0">ON</help6bTxt>
		<help6cTxt type="text" minor="0">OFF</help6cTxt>
		<help6dTxt type="text" minor="0">ON</help6dTxt>
		<help6eTxt type="text" minor="0">Not used</help6eTxt>
		<help7aTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;BNC&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</help7aTxt>
		<help7bTxt type="text" minor="0">ON</help7bTxt>
		<help7cTxt type="text" minor="0">ON</help7cTxt>
		<help7dTxt type="text" minor="0">OFF</help7dTxt>
		<help7eTxt type="text" minor="0">Not used</help7eTxt>
		<help88Txt type="text" minor="0">When connecting the product in loop-through with other equipment (e.g. to a monitor), disable the input termination by setting DIP switch 1 to the up position (OFF). Failure to do so can impair the image quality. This only applies when using the BNC composite video input.</help88Txt>
		<help8Txt type="text" minor="0">When connecting the product in loop-through with other equipment (e.g. to a monitor), disable the input termination by setting DIP switch 1 to the up position (OFF). Failure to do so can impair the image quality. This only applies when using the BNC composite video input. Loop-through is not possible when using the Y/C connection.</help8Txt>
		<help9Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Offset Adjustments -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Entering values in these fields changes the horizontal and vertical synchronization for the image. This can be used to eliminate any black border surrounding the image.</help9Txt1>
		<help9Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Be careful when using high values, both negative and positive, because they could put the image out of sync.</help9Txt2>
		<helpDeinterlaceTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;De-interlacing -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is used to improve video stream image quality from analog devices.</helpDeinterlaceTxt>
		<helpTeleplugTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Select any of the following options from the &#x3C;b&#x3E;De-interlacing&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list.</helpTeleplugTxt1>
		<helpTeleplugTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;None - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;If de-interlacing is not necessary.</helpTeleplugTxt2>
		<helpTeleplugTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Blending - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;For improved image quality that is not as processor intensive.</helpTeleplugTxt3>
		<helpTeleplugTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Adaptive Interpolation - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Performs de-interlacing of the video stream by applying different filters on the image. This may give a better result than &#x3C;b&#x3E;Motion Adaptive Interpolation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; in rare cases.</helpTeleplugTxt4>
		<helpTeleplugTxt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Motion Adaptive Interpolation - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Performs de-interlacing of the video stream by applying different filters depending on the motion in different parts of the image. This will in most cases result in the best image quality.</helpTeleplugTxt5>
		<help10Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;DIP Switches &#x3C;/b&#x3E;- Each video output is supplied with a corresponding line termination switch, which is enabled by default, i.e. the DIP switch is set in the down position.</help10Txt4>
		<help10Txt5 type="text" minor="0">If the product is to be connected in parallel with other equipment, disable the input termination for the video output by setting the corresponding DIP switch to the up position (OFF). Failure to do so can impair the image quality.</help10Txt5>
		<antialTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Antialiasing&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This will minimize distortion known as aliasing, which is when a high-resolution image is represented at a lower resolution.</antialTxt>
		<vidTerTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Video termination&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - If the product is to be connected in parallel with other equipment, disable the  video termination by checking this box. Failure to do so can impair the image quality.</vidTerTxt>
		<subTitle3Txt type="text" minor="0">Image Settings</subTitle3Txt>
		<noiseReductionTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Noise Reduction&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The noise reduction filter reduces noise in the image stream by comparing two sequential images and remove any changes that are considered noise. Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;On&#x3C;/b&#x3E; from the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Noise Reduction&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list to increase the image quality.</noiseReductionTxt>
		<noiseReduction_ARTPEC5Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Noise Reduction&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The noise reduction filter reduces noise in the image stream by comparing two sequential images and remove any changes that are considered noise. Use the slidebar to adjust the noise reduction level. A higher value produces an image with little noise, but at the expense of more details in the image.</noiseReduction_ARTPEC5Txt>
	</video_settings_h>





	<quad_settings_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Quad Stream Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Quad Stream Settings</titleTxt>
		<help1Txt type="text" minor="0">The quad stream provided by the Axis product can be configured much as any single video source.</help1Txt>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Quad Stream Appearance</subTitle1Txt>
		<help3Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Resolution -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Select the resolution to use for the quad stream. The available resolutions are:</help3Txt1>
		<help3Txt2 type="text" minor="0">4CIF</help3Txt2>
		<help3Txt3 type="text" minor="0">704x480 (NTSC)</help3Txt3>
		<help3Txt4 type="text" minor="0">704x576 (PAL)</help3Txt4>
		<help3Txt5 type="text" minor="0">CIF</help3Txt5>
		<help3Txt6 type="text" minor="0">352x240 (NTSC)</help3Txt6>
		<help3Txt7 type="text" minor="0">352x288 (PAL)</help3Txt7>
		<help3aTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Aspect ratio correction&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Checking this box improves the appearance of images from analog video sources when displayed on digital screens (i.e. computer monitors.) The pixels comprising the image are rearranged so as to provide a more accurate representation of the image.</help3aTxt>
		<help4Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Compression&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Changing the compression level affects total file sizes. Lower compression improves image quality, but generates larger files.</help4Txt>
		<help5Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Color settings -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Select either &#x3C;b&#x3E;Color&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Black &#x26; White&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Black &#x26; White uses less bandwidth than Color.</help5Txt>
		<subTitle2Txt type="text" minor="0">Overlay Settings</subTitle2Txt>
		<help6Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Include overlay&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This option places an overlay in the quad stream.</help6Txt1>
		<help6Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; The overlay to use must first be selected in &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Image - Overlay Image&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</help6Txt2>
		<help7Txt type="text" minor="0">Three other elements can also be included in the quad stream. These elements are all included on one line, which can be placed at the top or bottom of the stream. These elements are:</help7Txt>
		<help8Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Date&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Available in 3 different pre-defined formats. The format is selected in the &#x3C;a href='date_h.shtml'&#x3E;Date &#x26; Time&#x3C;/a&#x3E; settings in the System Options.</help8Txt>
		<help9Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Time&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Available in 12h or 24h format, with accuracy up to 1/100 seconds. The format is selected in the &#x3C;a href='date_h.shtml'&#x3E;Date &#x26; Time&#x3C;/a&#x3E; settings in the System Options.</help9Txt>
		<help10Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Text&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter your own text in the field provided. Alternatively, this field can be used to display various information types and formats, by entering special format strings, as described in &#x3C;a href='filenames_h.shtml'&#x3E;File Naming &#x26; Date/Time Formats.&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</help10Txt>
		<help11Txt1 type="text" minor="0">It is also possible to set how the text and/or background are displayed. The options for text are black or white only, whereas the background can also be set as semi-transparent or transparent.</help11Txt1>
		<help11Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Select placement of the selected items at the top or the bottom of the stream.</help11Txt2>
		<subTitle3Txt type="text" minor="0">Video Stream</subTitle3Txt>
		<help12Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Limit video stream time to - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;This is used to limit the length of time the stream is displayed for. A maximum time can be defined in seconds, minutes or hours.</help12Txt1>
		<help12Txt2 type="text" minor="0">When the set time has expired, a new stream can be started by refreshing the page in the browser. For unlimited video stream time, set this value to 0.</help12Txt2>
		<help13Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Limit frame rate to: x fps (frames per second) per viewer -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; To avoid bandwidth problems on the network, the frame rate allowed to each viewer can be limited to a fixed amount.</help13Txt1>
		<help13Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Define a maximum number of frames/second available to each viewer. Setting this value to 0 means the frame rate is unlimited.</help13Txt2>
		<help14Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Limit frame rate to: x fps (frames per second) per viewer -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; To avoid bandwidth problems on the network, the frame rate allowed to each viewer can be limited to a fixed amount.</help14Txt1>
		<help14Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Define a maximum number of frames/second available to each viewer. Setting this value to 0 means the frame rate is unlimited.</help14Txt2>
	</quad_settings_h>
</language_xml>
