<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<advanced_audio_settings_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Advanced Audio</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Advanced Audio</titleTxt>
		<help1Txt1 type="text" minor="0">Configure the advanced audio settings for the</help1Txt1>
		<help1Txt2 type="text" minor="0">.</help1Txt2>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Audio Quality Settings</subTitle1Txt>
		<help2Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable speech filter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This band pass filter reduces noise by filtering out all frequencies below 100 Hz and all above 3500 Hz. The filter cuts the lowest and the highest frequencies.</help2Txt>
		<help3Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable echo cancellation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - If audio from the speaker is captured by the microphone, this will produce an echo. Enable this option to reduce acoustic echoing.</help3Txt>
		<okiChip type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Noise canceller attenuation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Noise cancelling is a way of reducing the background noise when a microphone, for example, is set up in a noisy environment and you are only interested in hearing a person who is talking close to it. The &#x3C;b&#x3E;noise canceller attenuation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; produces maximum noise reduction when set to 18 dB of attenuation. If the Noise canceller attenuation is set to 0 dB, no noise cancellation is performed. Optimize the sound quality by listening to the sound and adjusting the attenuation level as required.</okiChip>
		<help4Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Noise canceller threshold value&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and &#x3C;b&#x3E;Noise canceller attenuation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Noise cancelling is a way of reducing the background noise when there is no useful audio. A typical application is that the camera is set up in a noisy environment, and you are only interested in hearing sound e.g. when a person is talking close to the microphone. &#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;  There are two parameters available to optimize this function:  &#x3C;ul&#x3E;  &#x3C;li&#x3E;Noise canceller threshold value  &#x3C;li&#x3E;Noise canceller attenuation&#x3C;/ul&#x3E;  When the incoming sound is louder than the threshold, it will pass without any changes. When the incoming sound is weaker than the threshold, it will be reduced by a certain attenuation factor (measured in dB). &#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;  The &#x3C;b&#x3E;threshold value&#x3C;/b&#x3E; should be set higher than the background noise, but lower than the useful audio. A lower threshold will accept most of the audio, only the weakest background noise will be reduced. A higher threshold will make the noise canceller act on even stronger background noise.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;     The &#x3C;b&#x3E;noise canceller attenuation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; produces maximum noise reduction when set to 17 dB of attenuation. If the Noise canceller attenuation is set to 0 dB, no noise cancellation is performed.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;     &#x3C;b&#x3E;Notes:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;     &#x3C;ul&#x3E;&#x3C;li&#x3E;Setting the maximum noise canceller threshold value to &#x3C;b&#x3E;High&#x3C;/b&#x3E; may reduce the amount of useful audio.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;  &#x3C;li&#x3E;There is a trade-off between noise cancelling and sound quality. Increasing the noise attenuation causes sound quality to deteriorate, and decreasing it causes sound quality to improve.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;  &#x3C;/ul&#x3E;  Optimize the threshold and the attenuation by listening to the sound quality and adjusting the levels as required.</help4Txt>
		<help5Txt type="text" minor="0">Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Save&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to save the settings, or click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Reset&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to reset to factory default values.</help5Txt>
	</advanced_audio_settings_h>





	<audio_settings_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Audio Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Audio Settings</titleTxt>
		<introTxt2 type="text" minor="0">Configure the audio settings for this device.</introTxt2>
		<subTitle2Txt type="text" minor="0">Enable Audio</subTitle2Txt>
		<enable_audioTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable audio&#x3C;/b&#x3E; -</enable_audioTxt>
		<enable_one_sourceTxt type="text" minor="0">Check this box to enable audio functionality.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</enable_one_sourceTxt>
		<associate_audioTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Associate audio with&#x3C;/b&#x3E; -</associate_audioTxt>
		<enable_multiple_sourcesTxt type="text" minor="0">Check the required boxes to enable audio functionality on the individual video sources.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</enable_multiple_sourcesTxt>
		<subTitle5Txt type="text" minor="0">Audio Channels</subTitle5Txt>
		<modeTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This sets the type of audio transmission. The available options are:</modeTxt1>
		<modeTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Full duplex&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Simultaneous two-way audio. Transmit and receive audio (talk and listen) at the same time. &#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; There is no echo cancellation; if feedback loops occur, try moving the microphone or the speaker.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</modeTxt2>
		<modeTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Half-duplex&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Half-duplex mode sends and receives audio in one direction at a time. A Talk/Listen button is used to switch between sending and receiving audio. For more information about the Talk/Listen button go to &#x3C;a href='liveview_h.shtml'&#x3E;Live View&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</modeTxt3>
		<modeTxt4a type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Simplex -&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</modeTxt4a>
		<modeTxt4b type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;speaker only&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - In simplex mode, audio is sent in one direction only. In this case, audio is sent by the operator to the speaker connected to the</modeTxt4b>
		<modeTxt4c type="text" minor="0">. This could be used,  to provide spoken instructions to a person seen on the camera. This mode requires you to use the Talk button. For more information about the Talk button go to &#x3C;a href='liveview_h.shtml'&#x3E;Live View&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</modeTxt4c>
		<modeTxt5a type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Simplex -&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</modeTxt5a>
		<modeTxt5b type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;microphone only&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - A simplex mode that transmits audio from the</modeTxt5b>
		<modeTxt5c type="text" minor="0">to one or more clients. This can be used in remote monitoring.</modeTxt5c>
		<clientTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Send the sound from the active client to all other clients&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The audio feed from one client will be broadcast to all other connected clients. Note that this option can only be enabled when using Half-duplex mode.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</clientTxt>
		<subTitle3Txt type="text" minor="0">Audio Input</subTitle3Txt>
		<input_portTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Port&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio 1&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio 2&#x3C;/b&#x3E; from the drop-down list. Audio 1 can be used for an electret microphone or an unbalanced dynamic microphone. Audio 2 is for a balanced microphone. Audio 1 cannot be combined with equipment connected to Audio 2. See the product's user's manual for more information on connecting microphones.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;</input_portTxt>
		<input_PinTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Source&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for an internal microphone or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Line&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for a Line in device, e.g. an audio mixer for multiple microphones or a microphone with a built-in amplifier. If no external microphone is connected the internal microphone will be used.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</input_PinTxt>
		<input_micTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Source&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Internal microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; if audio is to be transmitted from the microphone built into the camera, or &#x3C;b&#x3E;External microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to use a separate microphone connected to the audio input. &#x3C;b&#x3E;Line&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is to be selected when connecting a Line in device, e.g. an audio mixer for multiple microphones or a microphone with a built-in amplifier.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</input_micTxt>
		<input_micLineTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Source&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Internal microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; if audio is to be transmitted from the microphone built into the camera, or &#x3C;b&#x3E;External microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to use a separate microphone connected to the audio input.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</input_micLineTxt>
		<input_VSTxt type="text" minor="1">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Source&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for an external microphone or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Line&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for a Line in device e.g. an audio mixer for multiple microphones or a microphone with a built-in amplifier.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</input_VSTxt>
		<input_VS_1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Source&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for an internal microphone or select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Line&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for a Line in device e.g. an audio mixer for multiple microphones or a microphone with a built-in amplifier. Note that, if no external microphone is connected, the internal microphone will be used.</input_VS_1Txt>
		<all_SourcesTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Source&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Internal microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; if audio is to be transmitted from the microphone built into the Axis product, or &#x3C;b&#x3E;External microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to use a separate microphone connected to the audio input. &#x3C;b&#x3E;Line&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is to be selected when connecting a Line in device, for example, an audio mixer for multiple microphones or a microphone with a built-in amplifier.</all_SourcesTxt>
		<input_builtinmicTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Source&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - &#x3C;b&#x3E;Microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, audio will be transmitted from the microphone built into the camera.</input_builtinmicTxt>
		<srcTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Source&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Lists the internal microphone in this product.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</srcTxt>
		<balTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Balanced&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button if the microphone is balanced.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</balTxt>
		<micBoostTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;+30 dB microphone boost&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to amplify the signal of the external microphone connected to the Axis product. Microphone boost option is useful when a microphone's volume is too low and you want to increase it.</micBoostTxt>
		<micBoostTxt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;+30 dB microphone boost&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to amplify the signal of the external microphone connected to the Axis product. Microphone boost option is useful when a microphone's volume is too low and you want to increase it. This option is not available when the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Line&#x3C;/b&#x3E; source is selected.</micBoostTxt-1>
		<sens_internal_only_camTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Microphone - Input sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set the sensitivity level of the microphone depending on the sound level in the monitored area, e.g. set to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Low&#x3C;/b&#x3E; if the</sens_internal_only_camTxt1>
		<sens_internal_only_camTxt2 type="text" minor="0">is installed in a noisy environment.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</sens_internal_only_camTxt2>
		<sens_camTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Input sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - set the sensitivity level of the audio input according to the following:&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;If &#x3C;b&#x3E;Internal microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is selected (see &#x3C;b&#x3E;Source&#x3C;/b&#x3E; above) - set the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Input sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to &#x3C;b&#x3E;High&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Low&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, depending on the sound level in the monitored area, e.g. &#x3C;b&#x3E;Low&#x3C;/b&#x3E; if the</sens_camTxt1>
		<sens_camTxt2 type="text" minor="0">is installed in a noisy environment.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;    	If &#x3C;b&#x3E;External microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is selected - set the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Input sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to:    	&#x3C;ul&#x3E;    	&#x3C;li&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;High&#x3C;/b&#x3E; if the connected microphone is an ordinary (unamplified) microphone, e.g. a computer microphone or clip-on microphone.    	&#x3C;li&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Low&#x3C;/b&#x3E; if the connected microphone has a built-in line amplifier. &#x3C;/ul&#x3E;</sens_camTxt2>
		<sens_VSTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Input sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - When &#x3C;b&#x3E;Microphone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is selected for &#x3C;b&#x3E;Source&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (see above), set this to:    	&#x3C;ul&#x3E;    	&#x3C;li&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;High&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for an ordinary (unamplified) microphone, e.g. a computer microphone or clip-on microphone.    	&#x3C;li&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Low&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for a microphone with a built-in line amplifier.&#x3C;/ul&#x3E;</sens_VSTxt>
		<micPwrTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Microphone power&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Look at the user documentation for your microphone and select the appropriate voltage or phantom voltage from the drop-down list. &#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</micPwrTxt>
		<micPwrTxt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Microphone power&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The microphone power option provides DC power for an external microphone. Microphone power should only be used with microphones that have no battery and should not be enabled when using a dynamic or battery powered microphone. Look at the user documentation for your microphone and select the appropriate voltage or phantom voltage from the drop-down list.</micPwrTxt-1>
		<dC1Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Microphone power&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Microphone power should only be used with electric microphones that have no battery. This setting should &#x3C;b&#x3E;not&#x3C;/b&#x3E; be enabled when using a dynamic or battery powered microphone.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</dC1Txt>
		<dC2Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable microphone power&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Microphone power should only be used with electric microphones that have no battery and when using the internal microphone. This setting should &#x3C;b&#x3E;not&#x3C;/b&#x3E; be enabled when using a dynamic or battery powered microphone.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</dC2Txt>
		<mic48vTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable 48V microphone phantom power&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Provides 48 V DC phantom power to a microphone connected to Audio 2.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</mic48vTxt>
		<lEDTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable microphone level LED&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The microphone level LED is used to indicate the strength of the sound captured by the microphone. See the User's Manual for more information.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</lEDTxt>
		<gainTITxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Input gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Volume control of the audio input represented in dB value. Use the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Level&#x3C;/b&#x3E; bar for a visual representation of the audio signal strength. If the sound is too low choose a higher value. If the sound is too high choose a lower value.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</gainTITxt>
		<levelTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Level&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Level&#x3C;/b&#x3E; bar is a visual representation of the audio signal in dB.&#x3C;br&#x3E;  &#x3C;ul&#x3E;&#x3C;li&#x3E;Green - The signal is at a good level.&#x3C;/li&#x3E;  &#x3C;li&#x3E;Yellow - The signal is becoming distorted.&#x3C;/li&#x3E;  &#x3C;li&#x3E;Red - The signal is distorted.&#x3C;/li&#x3E;&#x3C;/ul&#x3E;  Use the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Input gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list to adjust the volume.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</levelTxt>
		<gain_commentTxt type="text" minor="0">The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Input sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; levels &#x3C;b&#x3E;High&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and &#x3C;b&#x3E;Low&#x3C;/b&#x3E; are volume settings made earlier in the audio path (see above). &#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;      &#x3C;blockquote&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Low &#x3C;b&#x3E;Input sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; should never be compensated by a high Input gain, as this may cause unwanted noise.&#x3C;/blockquote&#x3E;</gain_commentTxt>
		<encodingTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Encoding&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the digital audio encoding format to use.</encodingTxt1>
		<encodingTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;G711&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - is an unlicensed standard codec that is useful when integrating audio into a VoIP system.</encodingTxt2>
		<encodingTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;G726&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - is an unlicensed speech codec that is most commonly used within the security industry.</encodingTxt3>
		<encodingTxt4a type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;AAC&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - requires a license for both encoding and decoding. AAC is the least complicated and most widely used codec. If achieving the best possible audio quality is a priority, AAC is the recommended codec to use. AAC license is included in the</encodingTxt4a>
		<encodingTxt4b type="text" minor="0">.&#x3C;/li&#x3E;&#x3C;/ul&#x3E;</encodingTxt4b>
		<samplerateTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Sample rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The number of times per second the sound is sampled. A higher sample rate will provide better audio quality, but also requires a greater bandwidth.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</samplerateTxt>
		<bitrateTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Bit rate&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Depending on the selected encoding, set the required bit rate. A higher bit rate will give better audio quality. A lower bit rate may have latency or delay, but will require less bandwidth.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</bitrateTxt>
		<subTitle4Txt type="text" minor="0">Audio Output</subTitle4Txt>
		<outputNoheadphoneTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Output gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Volume control of the line audio output in dB. The output can be connected to an amplifier with speakers. &#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</outputNoheadphoneTxt>
		<outputTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Output gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Volume control of the line audio output in dB. The output can be used with high impedance headphones or connected to another amplifier with speakers. &#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;</outputTxt>
		<speakAmpTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable speaker amplifier&#x3C;/b&#x3E; -To use the built-in amplifier for speakers connected to Audio 2, check this box. &#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; If speakers are connected to both Audio 1 and Audio 2, Audio 1 is used.</speakAmpTxt>
	</audio_settings_h>





	<audio_support_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Audio Support</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Audio Support</titleTxt>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Settings</subTitle1Txt>
		<help2Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable audio support&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Allow clients to retrieve audio streams from the</help2Txt1>
		<help2Txt2 type="text" minor="0">.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;/br&#x3E;If disabled there will be no support for audio in the product. For example, no audio will be available even if audio in the video stream is enabled.&#x3C;br&#x3E;&#x3C;/br&#x3E;</help2Txt2>
	</audio_support_h>
</language_xml>
