<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<overlay_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Overlay Image</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Overlay Image</titleTxt>
		<alternativePageTitle type="msgAsText" minor="0">Help/Overlay Image Settings</alternativePageTitle>
		<alternativeTitleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Overlay Image Settings</alternativeTitleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">An overlay image is a static image superimposed over the video image. An overlay can be used to e.g. provide extra information, or to mask a part of the video image.</intro_Txt>
		<subTitle_select_Txt type="text" minor="0">Selecting and Uploading Overlay Images</subTitle_select_Txt>
		<use_select_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">To use an overlay image in the Axis product, it must be selected from the drop-down list of available images. The overlay (e.g. a logo) is then displayed in the video image.</use_select_Txt1>
		<use_select_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">To use your own image, first upload it to the product by entering the name of the file in the field provided, or by clicking the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Browse&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button and locating it. Then click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Upload&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button.</use_select_Txt2>
		<use_select_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">Once your own image has been uploaded it will be available for selection from the &#x3C;b&#x3E;use overlay image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list.</use_select_Txt3>
		<subTitle_scalable_txt type="text" minor="0">Scalable Image Overlay</subTitle_scalable_txt>
		<scalable_txt type="text" minor="0">Scalable image overlay provide a means to automatically scale down the overlay image to fit the resolution that is used by the Axis product.</scalable_txt>
		<subTitle_requirements_Txt type="text" minor="0">Overlay Image Requirements and Limitations</subTitle_requirements_Txt>
		<formats_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">The uploaded image must be Windows 24-bit BMP (full color) format. The size of the overlay image in pixels (width by height) must be exactly divisible by 4.</formats_Txt1>
		<formats_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">The uploaded image must be in format:</formats_Txt2>
		<formats_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">Windows 24-bit BMP (full color)</formats_Txt3>
		<formats_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">The size of the overlay image in pixels (width by height) must be exactly divisible by 4.</formats_Txt4>
		<formats_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">The uploaded image must be in one of the following formats:</formats_Txt5>
		<formats_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">Windows 24-bit BMP (full color)</formats_Txt6>
		<formats_Txt7 type="text" minor="0">Windows 4-bit BMP (16 colors)</formats_Txt7>
		<formats_Txt8 type="text" minor="0">The size of the overlay image in pixels (width by height) must be exactly divisible by 4.</formats_Txt8>
		<formats_Txt9 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Limitations&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</formats_Txt9>
		<formats_Txt10 type="text" minor="0">The maximum overlay image size supported</formats_Txt10>
		<maxres_Txt type="text" minor="0">is the same as the maximum image resolution, prior to Aspect ratio correction.</maxres_Txt>
		<h640res_Txt type="text" minor="0">is the same as the maximum image resolution.</h640res_Txt>
		<placement_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">The width / height needs to be a multiple of 4.</placement_Txt1>
		<placement_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">The image needs to be a 24bit BMP.</placement_Txt2>
		<placement_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">The maximum number of individual colors in an image is 250.</placement_Txt3>
		<placement_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">The maximum number of pixels (width by height) is 135000</placement_Txt4>
		<placement_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Example&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: If an image has width 352 pixels and height 353 pixels. The size of the image will be 352 x 353 = 124256 pixels. But since the height 353 pixels is not evenly divisible by 32, transparent pixels will be added (padding) to make the height 384 pixels, meaning that the size of the image will be 352 x 384 = 135168 pixels. This image cannot be used as overlay image because its size is bigger than the maximum size that can be used (135000 pixels).</placement_Txt5>
		<placement_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">If the image overlay and text overlay are larger than the video image, no overlay will be displayed. When also using a text overlay, this will occupy 16 or 32 pixels in height (depending on the resolution) and as many in width as the video image. Please consider this when configuring the overlay image.</placement_Txt6>
		<vSformats_Txt type="text" minor="0">When using the 2CIF format, overlays (both text and image) will be scaled vertically by the client on the Live View page or in a media player. Images in the 2CIF Expanded format are scaled directly in the server. See also the &#x3C;a href='image_h.shtml'&#x3E;Image&#x3C;/a&#x3E; settings.</vSformats_Txt>
		<position_Txt type="text" minor="1">If the overlay is initially positioned so that part of it is outside the video image, it will be relocated so that it appears over the video image, i.e. it is always the entire image that is displayed.</position_Txt>
		<subTitle_use_overlay_Txt type="text" minor="0">Using an Overlay Image</subTitle_use_overlay_Txt>
		<included_Txt type="text" minor="1">To use an overlay image once it has been specified, select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Include Overlay&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and set the coordinates in the</included_Txt>
		<cam_settings_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">Video Stream Settings</cam_settings_Txt1>
		<cam_settings_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Image Settings</cam_settings_Txt2>
		<transparency_Txt type="text" minor="0">See also &#x3C;a href='transparency_h.shtml'&#x3E;Transparency&#x3C;/a&#x3E; settings.</transparency_Txt>
	</overlay_h>





	<transparency_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Transparency Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Transparency Settings</titleTxt>
		<helpTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Colors in the overlay image can be made transparent. The options available depend on the type of image being used.</helpTxt1>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Full Color Overlay Images</subTitle1Txt>
		<helpTxt2 type="text" minor="0">When using a full color overlay image (a 24-bit BMP), a single color can be defined as transparent. To make a color transparent, check the box &#x3C;b&#x3E;Use transparency&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and then enter the RGB hexadecimal value for that color, using the format RRGGBB.</helpTxt2>
		<helpTxt3 type="text" minor="0">Examples of hexadecimal values:</helpTxt3>
		<helpTxt4 type="text" minor="0">#FFFFFF for white</helpTxt4>
		<helpTxt5 type="text" minor="0">#000000 for black</helpTxt5>
		<helpTxt6 type="text" minor="0">#FF0000 for this &#x3C;font color='#ff0000'&#x3E;red&#x3C;/font&#x3E;</helpTxt6>
		<helpTxt7 type="text" minor="0">#6633FF for this &#x3C;font color='#6633ff'&#x3E;blue&#x3C;/font&#x3E;</helpTxt7>
		<helpTxt8 type="text" minor="0">#669900 for this &#x3C;font color='#669900'&#x3E;green&#x3C;/font&#x3E;</helpTxt8>
		<subTitle_scalable_txt1 type="text" minor="0">Scalable Image Overlay</subTitle_scalable_txt1>
		<scalable_overlay_txt type="text" minor="0">Check the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Scale with resolution&#x3C;/b&#x3E; box for the overlay image to automatically be scaled down to fit the resolution that is used by the Axis product.</scalable_overlay_txt>
		<subTitle2Txt type="text" minor="0">16-Color Overlays</subTitle2Txt>
		<helpTxt9 type="text" minor="0">When using a 16-color overlay image (a 4-bit BMP), each color can have its own individual transparency setting. The available settings are:</helpTxt9>
		<helpTxt10 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Opaque&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The color is displayed normally, i.e. it is not transparent and the background video image is obscured.</helpTxt10>
		<helpTxt11 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Semi-transparent&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The color is mixed with the background video image, which is partially visible.</helpTxt11>
		<helpTxt12 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Transparent&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The color is completely transparent and the background video image is fully visible.</helpTxt12>
		<helpTxt13 type="text" minor="0">Note that transparency settings can only be applied &#x3C;b&#x3E;once&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to each uploaded image. To change the transparency for an image, upload it again and then make the new settings.</helpTxt13>
	</transparency_h>
</language_xml>
