<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<restrictIP_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/IP Address Filtering</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">IP Address Filtering</titleTxt>
		<general_subTitle_refer_Txt type="text" minor="0">General</general_subTitle_refer_Txt>
		<allow_deny_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable IP Address Filtering&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Checking this box enables the IP address filtering function. Once enabled, the addresses</allow_deny_Txt>
		<iPv6_Txt type="text" minor="0">(IP version 4 or IP version 6)</iPv6_Txt>
		<allow_deny_continue_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">in the list of IP addresses will be allowed &#x3C;b&#x3E;or&#x3C;/b&#x3E; denied access to the Axis product.</allow_deny_continue_Txt1>
		<allow_deny_continue_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">All other IP addresses not in this list will be allowed or denied access accordingly, i.e. if the addresses in the list are allowed, then all others are denied access and vice versa. Do not forget to add the IP addresses of other network devices that may need access to the product,for example NTP server.</allow_deny_continue_Txt2>
		<allow_deny_continue_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Allow&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Deny&#x3C;/b&#x3E; from the drop-down list and click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Apply&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button to enable.</allow_deny_continue_Txt3>
		<allow_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable IP Address Filtering&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Checking this box enables the IP address filtering function. Once enabled, only the addresses</allow_Txt>
		<iPv6a_Txt type="text" minor="0">(IP version 4 or IP version 6)</iPv6a_Txt>
		<allow_continue_Txt type="text" minor="0">shown in the list of allowed IP addresses will be permitted to access the product, all others will be blocked. Click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Apply&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button to enable.</allow_continue_Txt>
		<subTitle_filter_Txt type="text" minor="0">Filtered IP Addresses</subTitle_filter_Txt>
		<subTitle_allow_Txt type="text" minor="0">Allowed IP Addresses</subTitle_allow_Txt>
		<filtered_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Filtered IP Addresses -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; This list box shows the currently configured IP addresses. Up to 256 IP address entries may be specified (a single entry can contain multiple IP addresses). Click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button to</filtered_Txt>
		<help5Txt1a type="text" minor="0">add new filtered addresses</help5Txt1a>
		<help5Txt1b type="text" minor="0">.</help5Txt1b>
		<allowed_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Allowed IP Addresses -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; This list box shows the currently configured IP addresses. Up to 256 IP address entries may be specified (a single entry can contain multiple IP addresses). Click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button to</allowed_Txt>
		<help4Txt1a type="text" minor="0">add new allowed addresses</help4Txt1a>
		<help4Txt1b type="text" minor="0">.</help4Txt1b>
		<removeTxt type="text" minor="0">To remove an address entry from the list, select it and click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button.</removeTxt>
		<subTitle_refer_Txt type="text" minor="0">Referrals</subTitle_refer_Txt>
		<refer_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Only allow referrals from&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - As the video stream from the product can be included in any web page, it is in theory also possible for unauthorized sources to include the stream in other pages.</refer_Txt1>
		<refer_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">To prevent unauthorized referrals, enter the IP addresses or host names of allowed referrers in the field provided and check the box to enable. Multiple addresses can be separated by semicolons (;)</refer_Txt2>
		<refer_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Important notes!&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</refer_Txt3>
		<refer_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">If this feature is enabled and you wish to also allow normal access to the Live View page, the product's own IP address or host name must also be added to the list of allowed referrers.</refer_Txt4>
		<refer_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">Restricting referrers has no effect on an MPEG-4 video stream. To  restrict an MPEG-4 stream, IP address filtering must be enabled.</refer_Txt5>
		<refer_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">Restricting referrers is of greatest value when &#x3C;b&#x3E;not&#x3C;/b&#x3E; using IP address filtering (see above). If IP address filtering is used, allowed referrers are automatically restricted to allowed IP addresses.</refer_Txt6>
		<refer_Txt7 type="text" minor="0">If the check box has been selected but the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Only allow referrals from&#x3C;/b&#x3E; field is empty, the functionality has not been enabled.</refer_Txt7>
	</restrictIP_h>





	<restrictIP_setup_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Filtered IP Address Setup</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Filtered IP Address Setup</titleTxt>
		<allow_deny_Txt type="text" minor="0">This dialog allows you to add new allowed/denied IP addresses. These can be added individually one by one, or whole ranges (subnets) of IP addresses can be added directly.</allow_deny_Txt>
		<allow_1_Txt type="text" minor="0">This dialog allows you to add new allowed IP addresses. These can be added individually one by one, or whole ranges (subnets) of IP addresses can be added directly.</allow_1_Txt>
		<add_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">To add a subnet of network addresses, these must be added in CIDR notation.</add_Txt1>
		<add_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">For example:</add_Txt2>
		<add_ipv4_6_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">for IP v4, entering 192.168.1.0/24 will add all the addresses in the range 192.168.1.1 to 192.168.1.254.</add_ipv4_6_Txt1>
		<add_ipv4_6_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">for IP v6, entering 12AB::/64 will add all the addresses in the range 12AB:0000:0000:0000:0000:0000:0000:0000 to 12AB:0000:0000:0000:ffff:ffff:ffff:ffff</add_ipv4_6_Txt2>
		<add_ipv4Txt type="text" minor="0">entering 192.168.1.0/24 will add all the addresses in the range 192.168.1.1 to 192.168.1.254.</add_ipv4Txt>
		<add_okTxt1 type="text" minor="0">After adding a new IP address or range of addresses, click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;OK&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button.</add_okTxt1>
		<add_okTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; If you are accessing the Axis product via a proxy server, the IP address for the proxy server must be added as an allowed address.</add_okTxt2>
		<add_okTxt3 type="text" minor="0">For more information on CIDR notation, please visit the &#x3C;a href='http://www.axis.com/techsup' target='_blank'&#x3E;Axis Support web&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</add_okTxt3>
	</restrictIP_setup_h>
</language_xml>
