<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<disk_management_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Storage Management</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Storage Management</titleTxt>
		<alternativePageTitle type="msgAsText" minor="0">Help/Disk Management</alternativePageTitle>
		<alternativeTitleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Disk Management</alternativeTitleTxt>
		<sm_ar_introTxt type="text" minor="0">Storage Management is used to setup and manage SD cards, monitor its status, enable automatic cleanup, and prevent a disk from being overwritten. The storage unit can be used to store recorded video from Action Rules or Continuous Recordings. For more information on setting up recordings see:</sm_ar_introTxt>
		<sm_ar_introTxt_links1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;a href='action_rule_setup_h.shtml'&#x3E;Action Rule Setup&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</sm_ar_introTxt_links1>
		<sm_ar_introTxt_links2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;a href='continuously_h.shtml'&#x3E;Continuous Recording&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</sm_ar_introTxt_links2>
		<sm_subTitle_StDev_Txt type="text" minor="0">SD Card</sm_subTitle_StDev_Txt>
		<sm_storedevTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;File system&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Shows the file system currently used. See &#x3C;b&#x3E;Format&#x3C;/b&#x3E; below for more information about the file types.</sm_storedevTxt1>
		<sm_storedevTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Mount/Unmount&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Mount makes the memory card accessible to the system. SD Cards are normally preformatted with vFAT when purchased. If the SD Card needs to be formatted or you would like to change the formatting, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Format&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. See the format section for the available file system options.</sm_storedevTxt2>
		<sm_storedevTxt3 type="text" minor="0">Mounting is done automatically when a new memory card is inserted, or when the system boots. The only time you need to do a manual mount, is when you have clicked &#x3C;b&#x3E;Unmount&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and the memory card has not been ejected and re-inserted.</sm_storedevTxt3>
		<sm_storedevTxt4 type="text" minor="0">Never eject the card without unmounting it and turning off the power first because recordings may be lost.  &#x3C;b&#x3E;Status&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The following are the possible statuses:</sm_storedevTxt4>
		<sm_storeStatusTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Status&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The following are the possible statuses:</sm_storeStatusTxt>
		<sm_storedevTxt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;ready&#x3C;/b&#x3E;- The storage device is mounted and working correctly</sm_storedevTxt5>
		<sm_storedevTxt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;unmounted&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - the storage device is present but not mounted</sm_storedevTxt6>
		<sm_storedevTxt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;no card&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - the storage device is not present</sm_storedevTxt7>
		<sm_storedevTxt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;failed&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - A problem has been discovered, if ext4 has been selected as the file system click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Check disk&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to see if the problem can be found and then try &#x3C;b&#x3E;Repair&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</sm_storedevTxt8>
		<sm_storedevTxt9 type="text" minor="0">As a final measure the SD card might need to be reformatted. If there is important data on the SD card, make sure you backup the data before formating the SD card.</sm_storedevTxt9>
		<databaseCorruptTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: The status above shows if the storage device is properly mounted, it does not show the state of the data stored in the storage device. To get the status of the stored data, check the product's log messages.</databaseCorruptTxt>
		<sm_storedevTxt10 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: It is advised to stop all recordings before unmouting the disk in order to avoid loss of recordings or the information about recordings.</sm_storedevTxt10>
		<sm_subTitle_DevSet_Txt type="text" minor="0">Storage Tools</sm_subTitle_DevSet_Txt>
		<sm_storeTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Format&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Format an SD card when needed to change the file system or to quickly erase all the data, VFAT and ext4 are the two available file system options. Any previous data stored on the disk will be lost.  The recommended format is ext4, due to its resilience against data loss if the card is ejected or there is an abrupt power loss, however a third-party ext4 driver or application will be needed to access the file system from Windows. Note that most SD cards are preformatted with vFAT when purchased.</sm_storeTxt1>
		<sm_storeTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Check Disk&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use to check for errors on the SD card. Check disk only works for the file system ext4.</sm_storeTxt2>
		<sm_storeTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Repair&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Repairs the SD card of errors in the file system ext4.  To repair a vFAT formatted SD card, eject the SD card, insert it in a PC and perform a disk repair.</sm_storeTxt3>
		<sm_storeTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; The SD card must first be &#x3C;b&#x3E;unmounted&#x3C;/b&#x3E; before performing Check disk and Repair operations.</sm_storeTxt4>
		<sm_storeTxt5 type="text" minor="0">Note 2: For vFAT file system use a card reader or PC to perform card maintenance.</sm_storeTxt5>
		<sm_subTitle_genSet_Txt type="text" minor="0">General Settings</sm_subTitle_genSet_Txt>
		<sm_recSet_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove recordings older than&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Continuously removes older recordings. This option can be used to limit the amount of old recordings in order to avoid filling the SD card and also to comply with regulations regarding data storage. Enter the number of days or weeks to remove the old recordings. The default value is 7 days. However, old recordings will be removed sooner if the storage device becomes full.</sm_recSet_Txt1>
		<sm_recSet_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Lock (write protection)&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this option to stop writing to the SD card and protect recordings from being removed. A locked storage unit cannot be formatted.</sm_recSet_Txt2>
		<sm_autoFormat_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Autoformat to&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this option to automatically format an SD card to ext4 file system. The Axis product will check the inserted SD card to verify if its file system is ext4, if not the product will automatically format the SD card into ext4 file system.</sm_autoFormat_Txt>
		<sm_autoFormat_2Txt type="text" minor="0">It is recommended that, Autoformat be enabled to ext4 in order for the new or inserted SD card to automatically be formated to ext4 as it is a more reliable file system.</sm_autoFormat_2Txt>
		<sm_autoFormat_NoteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; It is recommended to only insert new and empty SD cards. Any data stored on the SD card will be lost.</sm_autoFormat_NoteTxt>
		<dm_ar_introTxt type="text" minor="0">Disk Management is used to setup and manage SD cards monitor a disk's status, enable automatic cleanup, and prevent a disk from being overwritten. Local storage can be used to store recorded video from triggered, scheduled or continuous recordings.  For more information on setting up recordings see:</dm_ar_introTxt>
		<dm_ar_introTxt_links1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;a href='action_rule_setup_h.shtml'&#x3E;Action Rule Setup&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</dm_ar_introTxt_links1>
		<dm_ar_introTxt_links2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;a href='continuously_h.shtml'&#x3E;Continuous Recording&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</dm_ar_introTxt_links2>
		<dm_subTitle_StDev_Txt type="text" minor="0">Storage Device</dm_subTitle_StDev_Txt>
		<dm_storedevTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Storage Device&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is used to mount and unmount, format, and monitor the status of available space of the disk.</dm_storedevTxt1>
		<dm_storedevTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Disk ID&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - When a memory card is connected it is given the label or Disk ID of SD_DISK.</dm_storedevTxt2>
		<dm_storedevTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Mount&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Makes the memory card accessible to the system. The memory card must be formatted to be mountable. SD Cards are normally preformatted when purchased, but if needed, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Format&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Mounting is done automatically when a new memory card is inserted, or when the system boots. The only time you need to do a manual mount, is when you have executed an unmount command and the memory card has not been ejected and re-inserted.</dm_storedevTxt3>
		<dm_storedevTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Free Space&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The available space left for recorded video.</dm_storedevTxt4>
		<dm_storedevTxt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Total size&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The total size of the memory card that is connected.</dm_storedevTxt5>
		<dm_storedevTxt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Status&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The following are the possible statuses:</dm_storedevTxt6>
		<dm_storedevTxt7 type="text" minor="0">OK - The storage device is mounted and working correctly</dm_storedevTxt7>
		<dm_storedevTxt8 type="text" minor="0">connected - the storage device is present but not mounted</dm_storedevTxt8>
		<dm_storedevTxt9 type="text" minor="0">disconnected - the storage device is not present</dm_storedevTxt9>
		<dm_storedevTxt10 type="text" minor="0">failed - A problem has been discovered.</dm_storedevTxt10>
		<dm_storedevTxt11 type="text" minor="0">If the status shows as &#x3C;b&#x3E;failed&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Check disk&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to see if the problem can be found and then try &#x3C;b&#x3E;Repair&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. As a final measure the storage device might need to be reformatted. If there is important data on the storage device, try using a card reader.</dm_storedevTxt11>
		<dm_storedevTxt12 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Full&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The disk is full when there is less than 1000KB of space left on the memory card.</dm_storedevTxt12>
		<dm_storedevTxt13 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Format&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Format an SD card so that it can be written to. Any previous data stored on the disk will be lost. Note that most SD cards are preformatted when purchased with vFAT.</dm_storedevTxt13>
		<dm_storedevTxt14 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Read only&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Shows the status of write-protect tab on the memory card. The status &#x3C;b&#x3E;no&#x3C;/b&#x3E; means the tab is in the write-enabled mode and recordings can be saved to the memory card. The status &#x3C;b&#x3E;yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; means the memory card's tab is in the write-protected/read-only position, or there is a system error. In these cases, recordings cannot be saved to the SD card.</dm_storedevTxt14>
		<dm_subTitle_DevSet_Txt type="text" minor="0">Storage Device Settings</dm_subTitle_DevSet_Txt>
		<dm_storesettingTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Device Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is used to configure the removal of recorded video.</dm_storesettingTxt1>
		<dm_storesettingTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable automatic disk cleanup&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - To avoid filling a storage device, Automatic Disk Cleanup can be set to continually remove older recordings to create more space.</dm_storesettingTxt2>
		<dm_storesettingTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove recordings older than&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter number of days or weeks.</dm_storesettingTxt3>
		<dm_storesettingTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove oldest recordings when disk is&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter a limit to how full the disk can be before disk cleanup will start. For Continuous Recording to work properly do not set the limit to more than 95% full.</dm_storesettingTxt4>
		<dm_storesettingTxt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Since parts of recordings are removed it is recommended to use a text overlay. See Overlay settings under &#x3C;a href='videostream_h.shtml'&#x3E;Video Stream Settings&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</dm_storesettingTxt5>
		<dm_storesettingTxt6 type="text" minor="0">Interrupted recordings with an Unknown status, partial recordings and any other recording that has not been removed by automatic disk cleanup can be removed manually from the Recording List using the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button.</dm_storesettingTxt6>
		<dm_storesettingTxt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Lock disk&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this option to stop writing to the disk and protect recordings from being removed. A locked disk cannot be formatted.</dm_storesettingTxt7>
	</disk_management_h>





	<diskmgmt_nas_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Storage Management</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Storage Management</titleTxt>
		<introTxt type="text" minor="0">Storage Management is used to set up and manage a Network Share, monitor its status, enable automatic cleanup, and prevent over writing. The storage unit can be used to store recorded video from Action Rules or Continuous Recordings.  For more information on setting up recordings see:</introTxt>
		<introTxt_links1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;a href='action_rule_setup_h.shtml'&#x3E;Action Rule Setup&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</introTxt_links1>
		<introTxt_links2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;a href='continuously_h.shtml'&#x3E;Continuous Recording&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</introTxt_links2>
		<subTitle_StDev_Txt type="text" minor="0">Network Share</subTitle_StDev_Txt>
		<nasTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Host&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The IP-address to the host server, typically a NAS (Network Attached Storage). It is recommended to configure the host to use fixed IP address (not DHCP) as the DHCP address can change over time. Alternatively use DNS or Bonjour names for the host. Windows SMB/CIFS names are not supported.</nasTxt1>
		<nasTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Share&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the name of the share on the host. Multiple cameras can use the same network share as they are each given a unique directory.</nasTxt2>
		<nasTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;The share requires a login&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box and enter the &#x3C;b&#x3E;User name&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and &#x3C;b&#x3E;Password&#x3C;/b&#x3E; if the network share requires login credentials.</nasTxt3>
		<nasTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Click this button to remove the Network Share from this product. Note that, all settings for the network share will be removed. This button may be useful when needed to remove network share and remain with SD card as storage option or for conducting network share tests.</nasTxt4>
		<nasTxt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Connect/Disconnect&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Click connect button to make local storage disk accessible and ready to store recorded videos and images. Click Disconnect button when you want to end the connection to a Network Share storage disk. After providing host address and share name details click connect,the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Status&#x3C;/b&#x3E; indicator field will show any of the below possible statuses for the network share:</nasTxt5>
		<nasTxt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;ready&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The share is online and connected. The camera can record and playback.</nasTxt6>
		<nasTxt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;online&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The share is online but is not connected. The camera cannot record or playback.</nasTxt7>
		<nasTxt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;offline&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The share cannot be reached. Check that the correct information has been entered for the host address, share name and credentials.</nasTxt8>
		<nasTxt9 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;not defined&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The share has not yet been initiated.</nasTxt9>
		<databaseCorruptTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: The status above shows if the storage device is properly mounted, it does not show the state of the data stored in the storage device. To get the status of the stored data, check the product's log messages.</databaseCorruptTxt>
		<nasTxt10 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: It is advised to stop all recordings before unmouting the disk in order to avoid loss of recordings or the information about recordings.</nasTxt10>
		<subTitle_StorageToolTxt type="text" minor="0">Storage Tools</subTitle_StorageToolTxt>
		<buttonTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Clear&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Click to clear all recordings and data from the camera's folder in the designated share.</buttonTxt1>
		<buttonTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Test&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Test the connection to the network share. The test verifies that the network share can be used as a storage device.</buttonTxt2>
		<subTitle_recSet_Txt type="text" minor="0">Recording Settings</subTitle_recSet_Txt>
		<subTitle_recSet_Txt-1 type="text" minor="0">General Settings</subTitle_recSet_Txt-1>
		<recSet_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove recordings older than&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - To avoid filling the share, older recordings can be set to continually be removed. Enter number of days or weeks. The default value is 7 days. However, old recordings will be removed sooner if the storage device becomes full.</recSet_Txt1>
		<recSet_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Lock (write protection)&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this option to stop writing to the share and protect recordings from being removed.</recSet_Txt2>
	</diskmgmt_nas_h>





	<storagelist_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Storage Overview</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Storage Overview</titleTxt>
		<introTxt type="text" minor="0">Storage Overview contains a list of all storage devices used for recordings.</introTxt>
		<subTitle_Txt type="text" minor="0">Camera Controlled Storage</subTitle_Txt>
		<listTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Type&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Type of storage unit, for example an SD card or a network share. Click the link to open the unit's management page.</listTxt1>
		<listTxt1-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Type&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Storage device supported by this product. Depending on your product, listed storage device may be for example an SD card or a Network Share. Click the link to open the device's management page.</listTxt1-1>
		<listTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Status&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Possible statuses are ready, connected, no disk, or failure if connection to the storage unit failed. See the unit's management help page for  detailed status descriptions.</listTxt2>
		<listTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Total size&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This is the size available for recordings, however the actual size may be smaller if quotas are used on the share.</listTxt3>
		<listTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: The total size of the SD Card shown by the Axis product is less than the one stated on the SD Card because some disk space is allocated to the file system. It can be noted that, ext4 file system uses more disk space and this is done in order to guarantee integrity of the data in the disk.</listTxt4>
		<listTxt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Used space&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Includes the amount of used space on the storage unit that is reserved for internal use as well as recordings.</listTxt5>
	</storagelist_h>
</language_xml>
