<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<advanced_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Camera Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Camera Settings</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">This page provides access to the advanced image settings for this device.</intro_Txt>
		<subTitleCapModTxt type="text" minor="0">Capture Mode</subTitleCapModTxt>
		<captureModeTxt01 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Capture mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The capture mode setting reduces image flicker in fluorescent light environments and is set the first time the product is accessed. Changing capture mode is not recommended as most video stream settings will either be removed or reset.</captureModeTxt01>
		<captureModeTxt02 type="text" minor="0">To reduce image flicker, select the capture mode with the power line frequency (50 Hz or 60 Hz) used at the location of the Axis product. When using 50 Hz, the maximum frame rate is limited to 25 fps.</captureModeTxt02>
		<captureModeTxt03 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Capture mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Capture mode defines the maximum resolution and maximum frame rate available in the Axis product. The capture mode setting also affects the camera's angle of view, if using a capture mode with a smaller maximum resolution, the angle of view is reduced.</captureModeTxt03>
		<captureModeTxt04a type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Capture mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is set the first time the product is accessed.</captureModeTxt04a>
		<captureModeTxt04b type="text" minor="0">Changing capture mode is not recommended as most other settings will be either removed or reset to default, for example:</captureModeTxt04b>
		<captureModeTxt05 type="text" minor="0">View Areas</captureModeTxt05>
		<captureModeTxt06 type="text" minor="0">Motion detection windows</captureModeTxt06>
		<captureModeTxt07 type="text" minor="0">Privacy masks</captureModeTxt07>
		<captureModeTxt08 type="text" minor="0">Image overlays</captureModeTxt08>
		<captureModeTxt09 type="text" minor="0">Preset positions</captureModeTxt09>
		<captureModeTxt10 type="text" minor="0">Guard tours</captureModeTxt10>
		<captureModeTxt11 type="text" minor="0">Events</captureModeTxt11>
		<captureModeTxt12 type="text" minor="0">Exposure windows</captureModeTxt12>
		<captureModeTxt13 type="text" minor="0">Stream profiles</captureModeTxt13>
		<subTitleViewAreaTxt1 type="text" minor="0">View Area</subTitleViewAreaTxt1>
		<viewAreaTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Check this box to enable the ability to define specific areas of the overview image called view areas. To set up a view area go to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Audio&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;View Area&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</viewAreaTxt1>
		<subTitleViewAreaTxt2 type="text" minor="0">View Areas</subTitleViewAreaTxt2>
		<viewAreaTxt2 type="text" minor="0">Check this box to enable the ability to define specific areas of the overview image called view areas, that are treated as different video sources. To set up a view area go to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Audio&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;View Areas&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</viewAreaTxt2>
		<viewAreaOpticNote type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: View Areas is not available when &#x3C;b&#x3E;Optical Live Zoom&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is selected as a PTZ mode.</viewAreaOpticNote>
		<viewAreaUploadableDrNote type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: View Areas is not available when &#x3C;b&#x3E;Uploadable PTZ driver&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is selected as a PTZ mode.</viewAreaUploadableDrNote>
		<subTitleCamOrientTxt type="text" minor="0">Camera Orientation</subTitleCamOrientTxt>
		<CamOriHelpTxt type="text" minor="0">To change the camera's orientation, go to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Setup &#x3E; System Options &#x3E; Maintenance&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Restore&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button. Note that all except IP parameters will be reset to original settings. After restore, the product will present an initial screen, select the required orientation from the list.</CamOriHelpTxt>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Image Appearance</subTitle1Txt>
		<colorLTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Color level -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Lower values mean less color saturation, while the value 100 gives maximum color saturation. The value 0 gives a black and white image.</colorLTxt>
		<brightTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Brightness&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This slidebar adjusts the image brightness, where a higher value produces a brighter image.</brightTxt>
		<shrpTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Sharpness&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Controls the amount of sharpening applied to the image.</shrpTxt1>
		<shrpTxt2 type="text" minor="0">In general, a higher setting will improve the image's sharpness, but at the expense of increased image noise, especially in low light conditions. There may also be image artifacts present around areas with high contrast (e.g. sharp edges).</shrpTxt2>
		<shrpTxt3 type="text" minor="0">A lower setting reduces the amount of image noise, but makes the image less sharp.</shrpTxt3>
		<contrTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Contrast&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This slidebar adjusts the image's contrast, where a higher value produces an image with high contrast between dark and light areas.</contrTxt>
		<localContrTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Local contrast -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Applies contrast to a specific area of the image. Use the slidebar to  adjust the image's contrast, where a higher value produces an image with high contrast between dark and light areas.</localContrTxt>
		<barrelDistCorrTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Barrel distortion correction&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Provides an option to correct or disable the barrel distortion. Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Custom&#x3C;/b&#x3E; from the drop-down list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Edit&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to launch the barrel distortion correction page.</barrelDistCorrTxt>
		<iRCF_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;IR cut filter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set this filter to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Off&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to allow the camera to 'see' infrared light, e.g. at night, and/or when using an infrared lamp. This makes the image clearer.</iRCF_Txt1>
		<iRCF_auto_note_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">If set to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, the camera will automatically switch between IR cut filter On and Off, according to the current lighting conditions.</iRCF_auto_note_Txt1>
		<iRCF_dome_note_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">This is only possible when the iris is set to Auto Iris, and the exposure control is set to Automatic.</iRCF_dome_note_Txt1>
		<iRlamp_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">Setting the IR cut filter to OFF will also enable the buttons controlling the IR lamp. Set the lamp to ON or OFF as required.</iRlamp_Txt1>
		<subTitleImgCorrTxt type="text" minor="0">Image Correction</subTitleImgCorrTxt>
		<imgCorrOffTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Off&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - select off to disable image correction.</imgCorrOffTxt>
		<electrImgStabTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Electronic image stabilization (EIS)&#x3C;/b&#x3E; -  When monitoring an environment that is subject to vibrations e.g. train station or traffic control, images may appear to be unsteady.</electrImgStabTxt>
		<autoElectrImgStabTxt type="text" minor="0">To automatically improve image stability, check the Electronic image stabilization (EIS) box.</autoElectrImgStabTxt>
		<mannElectrImgStabTxt type="text" minor="0">To improve image stability, manually adjust focus and zoom and note the approximate focal length value as indicated in the camera unit below the zoom puller. Check the Electronic image stabilization (EIS) box and use the slider to adjust the focal length to match the focal length value previously set manually to get the best image stability. Open the Live view page on another window and observe how the image stabilizes after adjusting the slider and saving.</mannElectrImgStabTxt>
		<electrImgStabNoteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: The focal length values (Micrometer) available depends on the selected optics.</electrImgStabNoteTxt>
		<subTitleTxt type="text" minor="0">White Balance</subTitleTxt>
		<white_balance type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;White Balance - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;</white_balance>
		<whitebal_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">This adjusts the relative amount of red, green and blue primary colors in the image so that the neutral colors are reproduced correctly.</whitebal_Txt1>
		<whitebal_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">The camera can be set to automatically adjust for the type of light and compensate for its color.</whitebal_Txt2>
		<whitebal_man_Txt type="text" minor="0">Alternatively, the type of light source can be set manually.</whitebal_man_Txt>
		<options_Txt type="text" minor="0">From the drop-down list, select the white balance setting suitable for the lighting used for your camera. The available options are:</options_Txt>
		<other_fixedin_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Indoor&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment, ideal for a room with some artificial light other than fluorescent lighting and good for normal light temperatures at around 2600K.</other_fixedin_Txt1>
		<other_fixedfluor1_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Fluorescent 1&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment; good for fluorescent lighting with color temperatures at around 4000K.</other_fixedfluor1_Txt1>
		<other_fixedfluor2_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Fluorescent 2&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment; good for fluorescent lighting with color temperatures at around 5000K.</other_fixedfluor2_Txt1>
		<other_fixedout1_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Outdoor 1&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment. Good for sky light in bright conditions, for color temperatures at around 5500K.</other_fixedout1_Txt1>
		<other_fixedout2_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Outdoor 2&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment. Good for sky light in less bright conditions, for color temperatures at around 6500K.</other_fixedout2_Txt1>
		<other_auto_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic identification and compensation for the light source color. This can be used in most situations and is the recommended setting.</other_auto_Txt1>
		<street_auto_Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic Outdoor&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic color adjustment for outdoors. It allows images to be captured in natural white balance in morning and evening light.</street_auto_Txt>
		<auto_sodium_Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic Sodium&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic color adjustment that compensates for the yellow orange color of sodium vapor lights common in street lighting.</auto_sodium_Txt>
		<street_sodium_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Street lighting - Sodium&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic color adjustment that compensates for the yellow orange color of sodium vapor lights common in street lighting.</street_sodium_Txt1>
		<other_hold_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Hold Current&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixes the white balance at its current state. As an aid when doing this - open 2 browser windows - one showing the live image and one showing these settings.</other_hold_Txt1>
		<other_hold_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Set the White balance to Automatic</other_hold_Txt2>
		<other_hold_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">Position the camera so that most of the image is filled by the object that should be neutral (white/grey) and then allow the camera to automatically adjust</other_hold_Txt3>
		<other_hold_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">Set to Hold Current when the image meets requirements.</other_hold_Txt4>
		<dome_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic identification and compensation for the light source color. This can be used in most situations and is the recommended setting.</dome_Txt1>
		<dome_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Indoor&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment, ideal for a room with some artificial light other than fluorescent lighting and good for normal light temperatures at around 3200K.</dome_Txt2>
		<dome_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Indoor bulb&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment; ideal for a room with artificial light other than fluorescent lighting; e.g. for areas illuminated using standard light bulbs. Good for normal light temperatures up to 3200K</dome_Txt3>
		<dome_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Outdoor&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment. Good for sky light in bright conditions, for color temperatures at around 5800K.</dome_Txt4>
		<street_sodium_Txt2 type="msgAsText" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Street lighting - Sodium&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic color adjustment that compensates for the yellow orange color of sodium vapor lights common in street lighting.</street_sodium_Txt2>
		<street_mercury_Txt1 type="msgAsText" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Street lighting - Mercury&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic color adjustment for the mercury vapor lights common in street lighting.</street_mercury_Txt1>
		<imgh_whitebalance2_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic identification and compensation for the light source color. This can be used in most situations and is the recommended setting.</imgh_whitebalance2_Txt1>
		<imgh_whitebalance2_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic - wide&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this setting for automatic compensation in difficult lighting conditions, when the standard automatic setting is not enough. This may be useful when compensating for e.g. the lighting conditions commonly found around dawn and dusk.</imgh_whitebalance2_Txt2>
		<imgh_whitebalance2_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Indoor&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment, ideal for a room with some artificial light other than fluorescent lighting and good for normal light temperatures at around 2600K.</imgh_whitebalance2_Txt3>
		<imgh_whitebalance2_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Outdoor&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment. Good for sky light in bright conditions, for color temperatures at around 5500K.</imgh_whitebalance2_Txt4>
		<imgh_whitebalance2_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Fluorescent&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment; good for fluorescent lighting with color temperatures at around 4000K.</imgh_whitebalance2_Txt5>
		<street_sodium_Txt3 type="msgAsText" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Street lighting - Sodium&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic color adjustment that compensates for the yellow orange color of sodium vapor lights common in street lighting.</street_sodium_Txt3>
		<street_mercury_Txt2 type="msgAsText" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Street lighting - Mercury&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic color adjustment for the mercury vapor lights common in street lighting.</street_mercury_Txt2>
		<other_auto_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic identification and compensation for the light source color. This can be used in most situations and is the recommended setting.</other_auto_Txt2>
		<other_auto_cont1 type="text" minor="0">This option enables the &#x3C;b&#x3E;White balance window&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list.</other_auto_cont1>
		<other_auto_outTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic Outdoor&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic color adjustment that compensates for typical outdoor lighting such as the yellow orange color of sodium vapor lights common in street lighting or the color caused by light reflected in snow.</other_auto_outTxt>
		<other_auto_cont2 type="text" minor="0">This option enables the &#x3C;b&#x3E;White balance window&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list.</other_auto_cont2>
		<other_auto_wideTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic - wide&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this setting for automatic compensation in difficult lighting conditions, when the standard automatic setting is not enough. This may be useful when compensating for e.g. the lighting conditions commonly found around dawn and dusk.</other_auto_wideTxt>
		<other_hold_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Hold Current&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixes the white balance at its current state.</other_hold_Txt5>
		<other_fixedout1_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Outdoor 1&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment for sunny, with a color temperature around 5500K.</other_fixedout1_Txt2>
		<other_fixedout2_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Outdoor 2&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment for cloudy, with a color temperature around 6500K.</other_fixedout2_Txt2>
		<other_fixedin_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Indoor&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment, ideal for a room with some artificial light other than fluorescent lighting and good for a normal color temperature around 2800K.</other_fixedin_Txt2>
		<other_fixedfluor1_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Fluorescent 1&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment; good for fluorescent lighting with a color temperature around 4000K.</other_fixedfluor1_Txt2>
		<other_fixedfluor2_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fixed Fluorescent 2&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Fixed color adjustment; good for fluorescent lighting with a color temperature around 3000K.</other_fixedfluor2_Txt2>
		<other_manual_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Manual&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select this option and click Edit to manually set a reference point for the white balance in the View area.</other_manual_Txt>
		<street_sodium_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Street lighting - Sodium&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic color adjustment that compensates for the yellow orange color of sodium vapor lights common in street lighting.</street_sodium_Txt4>
		<street_mercury_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Street lighting - Mercury&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Automatic color adjustment for the mercury vapor lights common in street lighting.</street_mercury_Txt3>
		<whitebal_notes_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Notes:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</whitebal_notes_Txt1>
		<whitebal_notes_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">The automatic white balance setting reduces the risk of color flicker by adapting to changes gradually. When changing the lighting, or when the camera is first powered up, it can take up to 30 seconds to lock on to the new light source.</whitebal_notes_Txt2>
		<whitebal_notes_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">If a scene is illuminated by more than one type of light source, i.e. they differ in color temperature, the dominating light source will act as a reference for the automatic white balance algorithm. This behavior can be overridden by choosing a fixed white balance setting that matches the light source you want to use as a reference.</whitebal_notes_Txt3>
		<white_balance_window1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;White balance window&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The white balance window is enabled for the Automatic and Automatic outdoor options set in the White balance drop-down list. Select one of the options below from the drop-down list to set the white balance window properties.</white_balance_window1>
		<white_balance_window2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select this option to use the default settings for the Automatic and Automatic outdoor options, set in the &#x3C;b&#x3E;White balance&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list.</white_balance_window2>
		<white_balance_window3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Custom&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select this option to manually set a reference window for the white balance in the view area.</white_balance_window3>
		<subTitlewdrTxt type="text" minor="0">Wide Dynamic Range</subTitlewdrTxt>
		<subTitlewdrTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Wide Dynamic Range</subTitlewdrTxt1>
		<wdrTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;WDR - Dynamic Capture&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;On&#x3C;/b&#x3E; from the drop-down list to enable Dynamic Capture. This option improves the exposure when there is a considerable contrast between light and dark areas in an image.</wdrTxt1>
		<wdrTxt1-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;WDR - Dynamic Capture&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Wide Dynamic Range can improve the exposure when there is a considerable contrast between light and dark areas in an image.</wdrTxt1-1>
		<wdrForeCaptTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;WDR - Forensic Capture&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Wide Dynamic Range can improve the exposure when there is a considerable contrast between light and dark areas in an image.</wdrForeCaptTxt>
		<wdrTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;WDR On&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select WDR On to enable Wide Dynamic Range (WDR). WDR may be used in monitoring dark and bright areas. It is adviced to use  WDR Mode in bright conditions for example when monitoring cars, because WDR Mode handles the headlights well therefore performing better compared to Lightfinder Mode.</wdrTxt4>
		<wdrTxt4_noLightfinderTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;WDR On&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select WDR On to enable Wide Dynamic Range (WDR). WDR may be used in monitoring dark and bright areas. It is adviced to use  WDR Mode in bright conditions for example when monitoring cars, because WDR Mode handles the headlights well therefore performing better compared to when WDR is Off.</wdrTxt4_noLightfinderTxt>
    <wdrOffTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;WDR Off&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select this option to disable Wide Dynamic Range.</wdrOffTxt>
		<wdrTxt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Lightfinder Mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select this option to switch to Lightfinder Mode. By selecting Lightfinder Mode, the product will be optimized for low light conditions in order to give a better image quality. Lightfinder Mode may be used in a variety of low light applications such as parking lots, city surveilance and construction sites.</wdrTxt5>
		<wdrTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Dynamic Capture is only possible when the Exposure control setting is set to Automatic.</wdrTxt2>
		<wdrTxt2-1 type="text" minor="0">Dynamic Capture is only possible when the Exposure control setting is set to Automatic.</wdrTxt2-1>
		<wdrForeCaptNoteTxt type="text" minor="0">Forensic Capture is only possible when the Exposure control setting is set to Automatic.</wdrForeCaptNoteTxt>
		<wdr_notes_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Notes:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</wdr_notes_Txt>
		<wdrCaptureMode_noteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; The WDR On and Lightfinder Mode options are only available when Capture mode is set to 720p @ 25/30 fps.</wdrCaptureMode_noteTxt>
		<wdrCaptureMode_noteTxt-1 type="text" minor="0">The WDR On and Lightfinder Mode options are only available when Capture mode is set to 720p @ 25/30 fps.</wdrCaptureMode_noteTxt-1>
		<wdrSpecFeatures_noteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Functionalities such as Exposure value, Exposure zones, Backlight compensation and Shutter &#x26; Gain's Normal Light are not available when WDR is On or when the selected Capture mode has WDR enabled.</wdrSpecFeatures_noteTxt>
		<wdrSpecFeatures_noteTxt-1 type="text" minor="0">Functionalities such as Exposure value, Exposure zones, Backlight compensation and Shutter &#x26; Gain's Normal Light are not available when WDR is On or when the selected Capture mode has WDR enabled.</wdrSpecFeatures_noteTxt-1>
		<highlightsRecovery_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Highlights recovery&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Improves the image appearance by decreasing brightness to the bright parts of the image. Use the slidebar to adjust the highlight recovery where, a high value reduces the brightness in the image.</highlightsRecovery_Txt>
		<shadowsRecovery_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Shadows recovery&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Improves the image appearance by increasing brightness to the dark parts of the image. Use the slidebar to adjust the shadow recovery where, a high value increases the brightness in the image.</shadowsRecovery_Txt>
		<dcTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable Dynamic Contrast&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This option improves the exposure when there is a considerable contrast between light and dark areas in an image. Use the slidebar to adjust dynamic contrast, where high applies more dynamic contrast to the image. The scene may affect how the changes to an image are seen when adjusting dynamic contrast.</dcTxt1>
		<dcTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Dynamic contrast is only possible when the Exposure control setting is set to Automatic.</dcTxt2>
		<wdrTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Wide dynamic range:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Wide dynamic range can improve the exposure when there is a considerable contrast between light and dark areas in the image. Enable WDR in intense backlight conditions. The different WDR settings adjust for various amounts of contrast in the image. Use a higher WDR number for a higher contrast. Disable WDR in low light conditions for optimal exposure.</wdrTxt3>
		<trafficmodesubTxt type="text" minor="0">Traffic Light Mode</trafficmodesubTxt>
		<trafficmodeTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Traffic Light Mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This mode will modify the exposure settings,  so that traffic lights and other bright light sources will not saturate when in view at night. In this mode, it is possible to distinguish the color of the traffic light at any surrounding light level.</trafficmodeTxt>
		<trafficmodeNoteTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; The decrease in exposure will make the whole image darker, during conditions above.</trafficmodeNoteTxt1>
		<trafficmodeNoteTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; This setting will disable the Exposure Settings for best results.</trafficmodeNoteTxt2>
		<expsubTxt type="text" minor="0">Exposure Settings</expsubTxt>
		<rotQTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable Backlight compensation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Backlight compensation makes the subject appear clearer when the image background is too bright, or the subject is too dark.</rotQTxt>
		<expcont_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure control&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This setting can be used to adapt to the amount/type of light being used. The available settings are:</expcont_Txt1>
		<expcont_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This setting is the default and can be used in most situations. The shutter speed, iris and gain are automatically set to produce optimum image quality.</expcont_Txt2>
		<expcont_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Manual Shutter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This allows you to manually adjust the shutter speed. A slower speed in dark conditions will help to produce a brighter image, but will produce fewer frames per second, which may cause blurry images during motion.</expcont_Txt3>
		<expcont_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Manual Iris&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This allows you to manually adjust the iris opening in the lens. A larger F value means less light sensitivity, but a larger depth of field.</expcont_Txt4>
		<expcont_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Manual&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - If you have special requirements for the exposure setting and wish to lock it, select this option. Select the desired Shutter speed, Iris f-number and Gain from the drop-down lists.</expcont_Txt5>
		<expcont_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">Measured in decibels (dB), &#x3C;b&#x3E;Gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; describes the amount of amplification applied to a signal, in this case the visual information in the image. Although it is possible to attain a high level of amplification, and thereby provide viewable images in very low light, high gain levels will also increase the amount of image noise.</expcont_Txt6>
		<expcont_Txt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Backlight compensation and IR cut filter in auto mode is only possible when the Exposure control is set to Auto</expcont_Txt7>
		<max_exp_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Max exposure time&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Increasing the exposure time will improve image quality, but there may be an increase in motion blur.</max_exp_Txt1>
		<viewsubTxt1 type="text" minor="0">View Image Settings</viewsubTxt1>
		<viewsetTxt1 type="text" minor="0">To view the video stream with the current configuration, click first &#x3C;b&#x3E;Save&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and then &#x3C;b&#x3E;View&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. A pop-up window appears showing the current video stream configuration.</viewsetTxt1>
		<expcont_Txt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure control&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This setting can be used to adapt to the amount/type of light being used.</expcont_Txt8>
		<expcont_settings_Txt type="text" minor="0">The available settings are:</expcont_settings_Txt>
		<expcont_settings_domeTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This setting is the default and can be used in most situations. The maximum exposure time is automatically set to produce optimum image quality.</expcont_settings_domeTxt1>
		<expcont_settings_domeTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Checking the box &#x3C;b&#x3E;Allow slow shutter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; will result in a decrease in shutter speed in poor light, which allows more light in and increases the image brightness. This may also result in a drop in the frame rate, as well as blurry images. If full frame rate in all lighting conditions is always required, then this setting should not be enabled.</expcont_settings_domeTxt2>
		<expcont_settings_domeTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Manual&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - If you have special requirements for the exposure setting and wish to lock it - select this option. Select the desired exposure time from the drop-down list.</expcont_settings_domeTxt3>
		<expcont_settings_domeTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: that this setting may cause unwanted image effects.</expcont_settings_domeTxt4>
		<expvTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure value&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this slidebar to fine tune the exposure.</expvTxt>
		<expcontthermal_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure control&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This setting is used to adapt to the amount of light being used. For most situations, the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic&#x3C;/b&#x3E; setting can be used. Different settings may show variations in apparent image quality depending on the scene. Linear settings provide the best true thermal image of the scene, but may also increase image noise.</expcontthermal_Txt>
		<expcont_Txt9 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure control&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set to  &#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for optimal exposure settings automatically, for example brightness and noise. &#x3C;b&#x3E;Flicker-free 50 or 60 Hz &#x3C;/b&#x3E;is used to remove flicker which can be caused by fluorescent and other light sources. The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Hold current&#x3C;/b&#x3E; option locks the current exposure settings.</expcont_Txt9>
		<expcont_Txt9-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure control&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set to  &#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for optimal exposure settings automatically, for example brightness and noise. &#x3C;b&#x3E;Flicker-reduced 50 or 60 Hz &#x3C;/b&#x3E;is used to remove flicker which can be caused by fluorescent and other light sources. The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Hold current&#x3C;/b&#x3E; option locks the current exposure settings.</expcont_Txt9-1>
		<max_exp_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Max exposure time&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Increasing the exposure time will improve image quality, but at the expense of the total frame rate. There may also be an increase in motion blur.</max_exp_Txt2>
		<slow_shutter_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Allow slow shutter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - checking this box will result in a decrease in shutter speed in poor light, which allows more light in and increases the image brightness. This may also result in a drop in the frame rate, as well as blurry images. Do not enable this if full frame rate in all lighting conditions is always required.</slow_shutter_Txt>
		<backlightTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable Backlight compensation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Backlight compensation makes the subject appear clearer when the image background is too bright, or the subject is too dark.</backlightTxt1>
		<backlightTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable Backlight compensation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Backlight compensation makes the subject appear clearer when the image background is too bright, or the subject is too dark.</backlightTxt2>
		<expcont_settings_area3_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure zones&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This setting determines which part of the image will be used to calculate the exposure. The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E; setting can be used in many situations, but for particular requirements, select one of the other predefined areas.</expcont_settings_area3_Txt>
		<expcont_settings_area1_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure zones&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This setting determines which part of the image will be used to calculate the exposure. The Auto setting can be used in most situations, but for particular requirements, select Defined and click the Edit button to open the Exposure Windows dialog to custom define the exposure zone.</expcont_settings_area1_Txt>
		<expcont_settings_area1Note_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; When using custom exposure zones, other parts of the image may exhibit poor image quality due to saturation.</expcont_settings_area1Note_Txt>
		<expcont_settings_area2_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure zones&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This setting determines which part of the image will be used to calculate the exposure. The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E; setting can be used in many situations, but for particular requirements, select one of the other predefined areas.</expcont_settings_area2_Txt1>
		<expcont_settings_area2_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Selecting a predefined exposure area will show (as percentages) how each part of the image will be used to calculate the exposure. Note that a percentage value does not reflect the size of that area, but is instead an indication of how much 'weight' is given to that area when calculating the exposure.</expcont_settings_area2_Txt2>
		<expcont_settings_gainThermal_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This defines the amount of amplification applied to a signal, in this case the visual information in the image. Although it is possible to attain a high level of amplification, and thereby providing better detail in the  images, high gain levels will also increase the amount of image noise. Lowering the gain reduces image noise but can result in a darker image.</expcont_settings_gainThermal_Txt>
		<iRCF_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;IR cut filter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set this filter to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Off&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to allow the camera to 'see' infrared light, e.g. at night, and/or when using an infrared lamp. This makes the image clearer.</iRCF_Txt2>
		<iRCF_auto_note_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">If set to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, the camera will automatically switch between IR cut filter On and Off, according to the current lighting conditions.</iRCF_auto_note_Txt2>
		<iRCF_dome_note_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">This is only possible when the iris is set to Auto Iris, and the exposure control is set to Automatic.</iRCF_dome_note_Txt2>
		<iRlamp_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Setting the IR cut filter to OFF will also enable the buttons controlling the IR lamp. Set the lamp to ON or OFF as required.</iRlamp_Txt2>
		<adv_SShuAndGaiTxt type="text" minor="0">Shutter &#x26; Gain</adv_SShuAndGaiTxt>
		<shutter_gain1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Shutter and Gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The Shutter and Gain drop-down lists can be configured in four ways:</shutter_gain1>
		<shutter_gain2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Shutter=Auto, Gain=Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This configuration enables the possibilty to manually set the priority between low noise and low motion blur for both low light and normal light. It also allows the user to set the maximum value for shutter time in low light and the maximum values for gain in both normal light and low light.</shutter_gain2>
		<shutter_gain3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Shutter=Fixed, Gain=Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This configuration enables the possibilty to set a fixed value for the shutter time and a maximum value for the gain, allowing the camera to automatically set the gain depending on brightness.</shutter_gain3>
		<shutter_gain4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Shutter=Auto, Gain=Fixed&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This configuration enables the possibilty to set a fixed value for the gain and a maximum value for the shutter time, allowing the camera to automatically set the shutter time depending on brightness.</shutter_gain4>
		<shutter_gain5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Shutter=Fixed, Gain=Fixed&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This configuration enables the possibilty to set a fixed value for the shutter and the gain.</shutter_gain5>
		<shutter_gain_notes1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Notes:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</shutter_gain_notes1>
		<shutter_gain_notes2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Shutter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - A smaller value means less motion blur, but requires a well lit scene. A larger value will allow more light in the camera so that even a low lit scene can produce a good image, but at the expense of increased motion blur.</shutter_gain_notes2>
		<shutter_gain_notes3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - A lower value means less noise, but which can in dark situations lead to a very dark image. A larger value means more amplification making it possible to observe a dark scene, but with increased noise and an increased bandwidth usage.</shutter_gain_notes3>
		<normal_light type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Normal Light&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</normal_light>
		<priority_normal_light1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Priority&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use the slide bar to set the priority between Low motion blur and Low noise in the normal light area (see</priority_normal_light1>
		<priority_normal_light1Note type="text" minor="0">Exposure priority control</priority_normal_light1Note>
		<priority_normal_light1Note2 type="text" minor="0">).</priority_normal_light1Note2>
		<priority_normal_light2 type="text" minor="0">When prioritizing low noise (slide bar all the way to the left) the camera will automatically decrease shutter speed as brightness decreases. When the shutter speed reaches 1/30 s the camera will increase gain until the set maximum gain for normal light is reached. This is the default priority setting for normal light.</priority_normal_light2>
		<max_gain_normal_light type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Max gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select a value from the drop-down list. This defines the upper limit of the normal light area.</max_gain_normal_light>
		<max_fastShutterNormalLight type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Max fast shutter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sets shutter speed limit in normal light condition. Depending on a scenario, the shutter speed limit may need to be set, this is done through &#x3C;b&#x3E;System Options&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Advanced&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Plain Config&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</max_fastShutterNormalLight>
		<low_light type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Low Light&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</low_light>
		<priority_low_light1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Priority&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use the slide bar to set the priority between Low motion blur and Low noise in the low light area (see</priority_low_light1>
		<priority_low_light2 type="text" minor="0">Exposure priority control</priority_low_light2>
		<priority_low_light2-1 type="text" minor="0">).</priority_low_light2-1>
		<priority_low_light3 type="text" minor="0">When prioritizing low motion blur (slide bar all the way to the right) the camera will automatically increase gain as brightness decreases. When the gain reaches the set maximum gain for low light the camera will decrease shutter speed until the set maximum shutter for low light is reached. This is the default priority setting for low light.</priority_low_light3>
		<max_gain_low_light type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Max gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select a value from the drop-down list. This defines the upper limit of the low light area.</max_gain_low_light>
		<max_shutter_low_light type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Max shutter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select a value from the drop-down list. This defines the right limit of the low light area.</max_shutter_low_light>
		<exposurepriority_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure priority&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This defines the balance between image quality and the frame rate. When &#x3C;b&#x3E;Motion&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is prioritized, motion blur is minimized, but the image quality may be reduced with a higher frame rate. A prioritized &#x3C;b&#x3E;Low noise&#x3C;/b&#x3E; will provide better image quality with a lower frame rate.</exposurepriority_Txt>
		<shutter_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Shutter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - A smaller value means less motion blur, but requires a well lit scene. A larger value will allow more light in the camera so that even a low lit scene can produce a good image, but at the expense of increased motion blur. When using Flicker-free 50 Hz the shortest shutter time is 1/100 s, and when using Flicker-free 60 Hz the shortest shutter time is 1/120 s. This setting is only available when the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure priority&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is set to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Motion&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Low noise&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</shutter_Txt>
		<gain_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - A lower value means less noise, but which can in dark situations lead to a very dark image. A larger value means more amplification making it possible to observe a dark scene, but with increased noise. This setting is only available when the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Exposure priority&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is set to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Motion&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Low noise&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</gain_Txt1>
		<gain_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">When motion is prioritized the shutter time is kept as low as possible. When low noise is prioritized the gain is kept as low as possible.</gain_Txt2>
		<gain_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">Setting min/max to the same values is equivalent to setting a fixed value.</gain_Txt3>
		<expcont_settings_irisMngr_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Iris configuration&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This field displays the current configured iris type. To change iris configuration, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Edit...&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</expcont_settings_irisMngr_Txt>
		<expcont_settings_DCiris_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable automatic iris adjustment&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This should always be set to &#x3C;b&#x3E; Enabled&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, except during focusing, or when using a fixed iris lens.</expcont_settings_DCiris_Txt>
		<expcont_settings_positionable_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Iris adjustment&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set the preferred F value, with this slide bar. When the option &#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable automatic iris adjustment&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is enabled, the precise iris will use this value as long as light conditions are favorable for the setting, otherwise it will adjust itself to the best iris setting. If the automatic iris adjustment is NOT enabled, the precise iris will lock on this setting regardless of light conditions.</expcont_settings_positionable_Txt1>
		<expcont_settings_positionable_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">The number scale represents the amount the iris is open. When the scale is set at 0 the iris is opened as much as allowed. At the setting 100 the iris is closed as much as allowed. The default setting is 50. The actual F value is shown under the Iris adjustment bar</expcont_settings_positionable_Txt2>
		<max_gain_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Max gain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Measured in decibels (dB), gain describes the amount of amplification applied to a signal, in this case the visual information in the image. Although it is possible to attain a high level of amplification, thus providing viewable images in very low light, high gain levels will also increase the amount of image noise.</max_gain_Txt>
		<highLightCompensation_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Highlight Compensation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The Axis product will detect a bright light from a source such as a torch or car headlights and mask that image area. This setting is useful when the camera operates in a very dark area where a bright light may overexpose part of the image and prevent the operator from seeing other parts of the scene.</highLightCompensation_Txt>
		<highLightCompensation1_Txt type="text" minor="0">Adjust the sensitivity by selecting the options from the &#x3C;b&#x3E;highlight compensation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list.&#x3C;b&#x3E;High&#x3C;/b&#x3E; means that the Axis product will apply a maximum masking and &#x3C;b&#x3E;Low&#x3C;/b&#x3E; means the product will apply very little mask to the over exposed part of the image.</highLightCompensation1_Txt>
		<highLightCompensation_Txt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable Highlight Compensation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The Axis product will detect a bright light from a source such as a torch or car headlights and mask that image area. This setting is useful when the camera operates in a very dark area where a bright light may overexpose part of the image and prevent the operator from seeing other parts of the scene. To enable highlight compensation, check the box &#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable Highlight Compensation&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</highLightCompensation_Txt-1>
		<highLightCompensation2_Txt type="text" minor="0">Adjust the color of the mask by selecting the options from the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Mask tone&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list.</highLightCompensation2_Txt>
		<subTitle2Txt type="text" minor="0">Image Settings</subTitle2Txt>
		<autofocus_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Autofocus enabled&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to enable the camera's automatic focusing function. This setting is enabled by default.</autofocus_Txt>
		<autodefog_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto defog&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The Axis product will detect the fog effect and automatically remove it to get a clear image.  Select the level of fog removal from the drop-down list. &#x3C;b&#x3E;High&#x3C;/b&#x3E; implies that maximum fog removal is applied while &#x3C;b&#x3E;Off&#x3C;/b&#x3E; implies that no fog removal will be applied.</autodefog_Txt>
		<autodefogNote_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Auto defog can be activated incorrectly especially in scenes with low contrast, high light level variations or when auto focus is slightly off. This can affect the image quality by for example, increasing image contrast. Also, too much brightness can negatively impact the image quality when defog is active.</autodefogNote_Txt>
		<noiseREduction_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Noise reduction&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Image noise is caused by random brightness or color information that produces a grainy appearance in the image. Check this box to enable the camera's noise reduction function. Note that noise reduction may increase the amount of motion blur.</noiseREduction_Txt>
		<stabilizer_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Stabilizer&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - When monitoring environments that are subject to vibrations (e.g. traffic control), images may appear to be unsteady. Depending on the environment, select the frequency (High or Low) that gives the best improvement in image quality.</stabilizer_Txt1>
		<stabilizer_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Enabling the stabilizer will limit the digital zoom to 2x (70x total zoom).</stabilizer_Txt2>
		<stabilizer_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Image freeze on PTZ&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use this option to freeze the image while the camera is moving during a pan, tilt or zoom operation. Once the camera reaches its new position, the image from that position is shown.</stabilizer_Txt3>
		<dayN type="text" minor="0">Day/Night</dayN>
		<niViTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;IR cut filter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set this filter to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Off&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to allow the camera to 'see' infrared light, for instance at night, and/or when using an infrared lamp. This makes the image clearer. Set to &#x3C;b&#x3E;On&#x3C;/b&#x3E; during daylight or bright light conditions to cut out infrared light which will improve colors in the image. When set to &#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, the camera will automatically switch between On and Off, according to the current lighting conditions.</niViTxt>
		<adv_help_DaNiShLeTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Day/Night shift level&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This setting can be used to change when the camera shifts into night mode. By default, the camera will automatically change from day to night mode at a pre-defined level which corresponds to level 100 in the slider. By setting this slider to a lower value, the camera will change to night mode earlier.</adv_help_DaNiShLeTxt>
		<adv_help_DaNiShPrioSliderTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Day/Night shift priority&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This slidebar can be used to change when the camera shifts into either day mode or night mode. By default, the camera will automatically change from day to night mode at a pre-defined level which corresponds to light conditions. By dragging the slider knob towards the sun, the camera will change to day mode earlier and change to night mode late.</adv_help_DaNiShPrioSliderTxt>
		<enFoAdTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable focus adjustment for IR illumination&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The camera lens is IR corrected, which means that it maintains focus in mixed light, however a small focus adjustment is recommended when IR illumination is used. Check this box to automatically adjust the focus when the IR cut filter switches between on and off.</enFoAdTxt>
		<IrIllTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;IR Illumination&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</IrIllTxt>
		<adv_help_EnIrIllTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable IR illumination&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to enable the built in IR light. The built in IR light can be used for video surveillance in areas with low light, without requiring addition of external lighting. The IR light can be disabled, by unchecking the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable IR illumination&#x3C;/b&#x3E; box, this is useful in order to be able to use the Axis product in areas where the use of IR light is forbidden.</adv_help_EnIrIllTxt>
		<adv_help_SyncIrIllTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Synchronize IR illumination with day/night&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to synchronize the IR light illumination with Day/Night detection, that is the IR light will automatically be turned on during the night and turned off during the day. Uncheck this box to disable the IR light synchronization with Day/Night. Note that for Axis products with &#x3C;b&#x3E;IR cut filter&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, the filter setting must be &#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Off&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, in order for the Day/Night synchronization to work.</adv_help_SyncIrIllTxt>
		<adv_help_ConfIrIllTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Configure IR illumination:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Edit&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to see advanced settings for configuring IR illumination.</adv_help_ConfIrIllTxt>
		<viewsubTxt2 type="text" minor="0">View Image Settings</viewsubTxt2>
		<viewsetTxt2 type="text" minor="0">To view the video stream with the current configuration, click first &#x3C;b&#x3E;Save&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and then &#x3C;b&#x3E;View&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. A pop-up window appears showing the current video stream configuration</viewsetTxt2>
		<viewsubTxt3 type="text" minor="0">View Image Settings</viewsubTxt3>
		<viewsetTxt3 type="text" minor="0">To view the video stream with the current configuration, click first &#x3C;b&#x3E;Save&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and then &#x3C;b&#x3E;View&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. A pop-up window appears showing the current video stream configuration.</viewsetTxt3>
	</advanced_h>





	<exposure_priority_control_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Exposure priority control</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Exposure priority control</titleTxt>
		<brightTxt type="text" minor="0">BRIGHT</brightTxt>
		<darkTxt type="text" minor="0">DARK</darkTxt>
		<moNoTxt type="text" minor="0">More noise</moNoTxt>
		<moMoBlTxt type="text" minor="0">More motion blur</moMoBlTxt>
		<gainTxt type="text" minor="0">Gain</gainTxt>
		<shuSpeTxt type="text" minor="0">1/Shutter speed</shuSpeTxt>
		<noLiTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Normal light&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</noLiTxt>
		<loLiTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Low light&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</loLiTxt>
		<maGaLOLiTxt type="text" minor="0">Max gain&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(low light)</maGaLOLiTxt>
		<maGaNOLiTxt type="text" minor="0">Max gain&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(normal light)</maGaNOLiTxt>
		<h130Txt type="text" minor="0">1/30</h130Txt>
		<maShLOLiTxt type="text" minor="0">Max shutter&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(low light)</maShLOLiTxt>
		<loMoBlNOLiTxt type="text" minor="0">Low motion blur</loMoBlNOLiTxt>
		<loMoBlLOLiTxt type="text" minor="0">Low motion blur</loMoBlLOLiTxt>
		<loNoNOLiTxt type="text" minor="0">Low noise</loNoNOLiTxt>
		<loNoLOLiTxt type="text" minor="0">Low noise</loNoLOLiTxt>
		<title type="text" minor="0">Exposure priority control</title>
	</exposure_priority_control_h>


	


	<ir_light_settings_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/IR Light Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">IR Illumination</titleTxt>
		<subTitleTxt1 type="text" minor="0">IR Illumination Area</subTitleTxt1>
		<irLiAreaTxt type="text" minor="0">The IR illumination window displays the approximate area the IR light will illuminate given the current settings.</irLiAreaTxt> 
		<subTitleTxt2 type="text" minor="0">IR Illumination Settings</subTitleTxt2>
		<irLiAutoTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Auto&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (follow zoom) - Automatically adjusts the IR illumination according to the camera's zoom information. The angle of view (zoom) will be the same as the angle of illumination.  If the camera's angle of view changes, the IR illumination will change with it.</irLiAutoTxt>
		<irLiManualTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Manual&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sets the angle of illumination manually. This setting is useful when needed to set the angle of illumination to be different from the camera's angle of view.</irLiManualTxt>
		<irLiManualExTxt type="text" minor="0">If the camera has a wide angle of view you can set the angle of illumination to a more tele position. Note that this will result in dark corners in the image, use this setup if for some reasons it fits your installation requirements.</irLiManualExTxt>
		<irLiAngOfIllTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Angle of illumination&#x3C;/b&#x3E;- Use the slider to adjust the angle of illumination. The default IR illumination zoom is set at 1. If the camera's zoom is adjusted to a different value, move the Angle of illumination slider to the same value, for optimal IR illumination in the IR illumination window.</irLiAngOfIllTxt>
		<irLiAngOfIllTxt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Angle of illumination&#x3C;/b&#x3E;- Use the slider to adjust the angle of illumination. If the camera's zoom is adjusted to a different value, move the Angle of illumination slider to the same value, for optimal IR illumination in the IR illumination window.</irLiAngOfIllTxt-1>
	</ir_light_settings_h>





	<exposure_windows_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Exposure Windows</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Exposure Windows</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">Determine which part of the image will be used to calculate the exposure by setting up an exposure window setting.</intro_Txt>
		<subTitleTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Exposure Windows</subTitleTxt1>
		<selWinTxt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Select window setting&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Use the drop-down list to select an area in the image that will be used to calculate the exposure. The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic&#x3C;/b&#x3E; setting can be used in many situations, but if you have particular requirements, select one of the other predefined areas or create a custom area.</selWinTxt1>
		<selWinTxt2 type="text" minor="0">Selecting a predefined exposure area will show (as a percentage) how each part of the image will be used to calculate the exposure. Note that a percentage value does not reflect the size of that area, but is instead an indication of how much 'weight' is given to that area when calculating the exposure.</selWinTxt2>
		<subTitleTxt2 type="text" minor="0">Custom exposure windows</subTitleTxt2>
		<custWinTxt1 type="text" minor="0">A custom area can either include or exclude part of the image when calculating the exposure.</custWinTxt1>
		<custWinTxt9 type="text" minor="0">A custom area can include a part of the image when calculating the exposure.</custWinTxt9>
		<custWinThermalTxt1 type="text" minor="0">A custom area includes a part of the image to be used when calculating the exposure.</custWinThermalTxt1>
		<custWinTxt2 type="text" minor="0">To create a &#x3C;b&#x3E;Custom&#x3C;/b&#x3E; area:</custWinTxt2>
		<custWinTxt3 type="text" minor="0">Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Custom&#x3C;/b&#x3E; from the drop-down list.</custWinTxt3>
		<custWinTxt4 type="text" minor="0">Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add include&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, and a blue box appears in the image.</custWinTxt4>
		<custWinTxt5 type="text" minor="0">Using the mouse, click in the box to adjust its size and position to the desired area in the image.</custWinTxt5>
		<custWinTxt6 type="text" minor="0">Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Save selected window&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</custWinTxt6>
		<custWinTxt7 type="text" minor="0">To create a window for an area that should not be used for calculating exposure, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add exclude&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and follow the instructions above. Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to delete an include or exclude window. Up to 10 custom include and exlude windows can be set up and used at one time.</custWinTxt7>
		<custWinTxt8 type="text" minor="0">Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to delete an include window. Only one custom include window can be set up and used at one time.</custWinTxt8>
		<custWinThermalTxt2 type="text" minor="0">To delete an include window, select it and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Note that, only one exposure window can be set up and used at one time.</custWinThermalTxt2>
	</exposure_windows_h>





	<one-click_white_balance_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/One-click White Balance</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">One-click White Balance</titleTxt>
		<subTitle type="text" minor="0">Edit White Balance Point</subTitle>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">Drag the small square in the view area to the desired location to define the white balance point. Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;OK&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to save. Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Close&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to exit.</intro_Txt>
	</one-click_white_balance_h>





	<white_balance_window_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/White Balance Window</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">White Balance Window</titleTxt>
		<subTitle type="text" minor="0">Edit White Balance Window</subTitle>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">Rezise and drag the &#x3C;b&#x3E;White balance window&#x3C;/b&#x3E; in the view area to the desired location to define an area for the white balance. Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;OK&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to save. Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Close&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to exit.</intro_Txt>
	</white_balance_window_h>





	<iris_config_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Iris Configuration</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Iris Configuration</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">Change the iris configuration for the iris lens installed.</intro_Txt>
		<subTitleTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Iris Selection</subTitleTxt1>
		<select_h_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Select which iris is installed&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the iris lens from the drop-down list which has been installed and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Ok&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. If the iris lens is not listed, upload the configuration file under the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Upload&#x3C;/b&#x3E; tab.</select_h_Txt>
		<subTitleTxt2 type="text" minor="0">Upload Iris Configuration</subTitleTxt2>
		<upload_h_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Upload a new iris configuration file&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - If the iris lens is not in the list, then a new iris configuration file is needed. To upload a new configuration, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Browse&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and select the configuration file which was downloaded from www.axis.com or included with the iris. Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Upload&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. The installed iris should now be included in the drop-down list under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Iris&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</upload_h_Txt>
	</iris_config_h>





	<barrel_distortion_correction_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Barrel Distortion Correction</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Barrel Distortion Correction</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">Barrel distortion makes an image appear curved and bent outwards. This condition is seen more clearly when the image is zoomed out too much. The level of distortion is determined by the zoom level applied on the image.</intro_Txt>
		<intro_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">Correct the barrel distortion effect by using the Correction factor.  The image will be cropped and stretched in order to correct distortion.</intro_Txt1>
		<correctionFactorTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Correction factor&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Use the slide bar to modify the barrel distortion values. To correct barrel distortion, slide the bar towards the left until the correction level meets your requirements.</correctionFactorTxt>
		<showGridTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Show grid&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Select this option to see the grid lines on top of the image. The lines assist when correcting the distortion as they make it easy to see if the corrected image aligns with the grid lines.</showGridTxt>
	</barrel_distortion_correction_h>
</language_xml>
