<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<packages_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Application Packages</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Application Packages</titleTxt>
		<introhelpTxt1 type="text" minor="1">The Application packages feature allows you to upload 3rd party application packages for use on this Axis product. Listed under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Applications&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Packages&#x3C;/b&#x3E; are the packages that have already been installed. Click on the name to open the menu options &#x3C;b&#x3E;Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E;, &#x3C;b&#x3E;License&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and &#x3C;b&#x3E;About&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</introhelpTxt1>
		<introhelpTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - is dependent on the application package.</introhelpTxt2>
		<introhelpTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;License&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Once uploaded a license is needed to run the application. If there is an Internet connection &#x3C;b&#x3E;Automatic Installation&#x3C;/b&#x3E; will appear in the web page. If there is no Internet Connection go to www.axis.com to acquire a License key file. You will need a license code and the device's serial number to receive a license key.</introhelpTxt3>
		<introhelpTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;About&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Shows where to go for support for this application.</introhelpTxt4>
		<uploadTxt1 type="text" minor="1">To upload an application, browse to the package and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Upload Package&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</uploadTxt1>
		<uploadTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Installed Applications&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - A list of installed packages along with the version of the application, the vendor that authored the package, the status of the application and if a license key is installed. The status can assume the following values:</uploadTxt2>
		<uploadTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Not Running&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The application has not been started.</uploadTxt3>
		<statusStopTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Stopped&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The application is not running.</statusStopTxt>
		<uploadTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Idle&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The application has been started, but no event trigger has been configured for the application. The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Idle&#x3C;/b&#x3E; status is dependent on the type of application installed and is not used in all applications. Refer to the uploaded application's user's guide for more information.</uploadTxt4>
		<uploadTxt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Running&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The application is up and fully running.</uploadTxt5>
		<uploadTxt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Start/Stop&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Start or stop the application.</uploadTxt6>
		<uploadTxt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - To delete an application package, select it and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</uploadTxt7>
		<uploadTxt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Log&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - To generate a log of the application happenings, select an application and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Log&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. This log will be helpful when requesting support from the vendor of the application package.</uploadTxt8>
	</packages_h>
</language_xml>
