<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<snmp_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/SNMP Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">SNMP Settings</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">The Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) allows remote monitoring and management of network devices. An SNMP community is the group of devices and management station running SNMP. Community names are used to identify groups. The Axis product can be configured to support SNMP.</intro_Txt>
		<version_Txt type="text" minor="1">SNMP v1/v2c</version_Txt>
		<enable_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable SNMP&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - select the version of SNMP to use by checking the appropriate box.</enable_Txt>
		<read_community_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Read community &#x3C;/b&#x3E;- Specify the community name that has read-only access to all supported SNMP objects.</read_community_Txt1>
		<read_community_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Default value = public.</read_community_Txt2>
		<write_community_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Write community&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Specify the community name that has read/write access to all supported SNMP objects  			  (except read-only objects).</write_community_Txt1>
		<write_community_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Default value = write.</write_community_Txt2>
		<traps_Txt type="text" minor="1">Traps for SNMP v1/v2c</traps_Txt>
		<traps_intro_Txt type="text" minor="1">Traps are used by the camera to send messages to a management system for important events or status changes. These settings are used with SNMP v1/v2c.</traps_intro_Txt>
		<enable_Rraps_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable traps&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box to activate trap reporting.</enable_Rraps_Txt>
		<traps_addr_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Trap address&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the IP address of the management server.</traps_addr_Txt>
		<traps_addrNote_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: The trap address field can not be used when SNMP v3 is enabled. When using SNMP v3, the trap address is set through the SNMP v3 management application.</traps_addrNote_Txt>
		<traps_comm_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Trap community&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Community to use when sending a trap message to the management system.</traps_comm_Txt>
		<traps_available_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Avaliable traps&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</traps_available_Txt1>
		<traps_available_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Cold start&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sends a trap message when SNMP has started and the configuration as well as the MIB (Management Information Base) may have changed</traps_available_Txt2>
		<traps_available_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Warm start&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sends a trap message when SNMP has started and the configure file has changed, but not the MIB.</traps_available_Txt3>
		<traps_available_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Link up&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sends a trap message when a link changes from down to up</traps_available_Txt4>
		<traps_available_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Authentication failed&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sends a trap message when an authentication attempt fails</traps_available_Txt5>
		<mib_traps_Txt type="text" minor="1">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: All AXIS Video MIB traps are enabled when you enable SNMP v1/v2c traps. For more information see</mib_traps_Txt>
		<axisSupURL type="msg" minor="0">http://www.axis.com/r/?keyword=techsup</axisSupURL>
		<axisSupURLTxt type="text" minor="0">www.axis.com/techsup/</axisSupURLTxt>
		<sNMPv3_Txt type="text" minor="0">SNMP v3</sNMPv3_Txt>
		<sNMPv3_intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">SNMP v3 is a more secure version providing encryption and secure passwords. To use SNMP v3, HTTPS must be activated. To use traps with SNMP v3 an SNMP v3 management application is needed.</sNMPv3_intro_Txt>
		<sNMPv3_intro_Txt-1 type="text" minor="0">SNMP v3 is a more secure version providing encryption and secure passwords. To use SNMP v3, HTTPS must be activated as password is sent over HTTPS to avoid unencrypted SNMP v1/v2c traps being accessed by unauthorized parties. SNMP v3 traps are setup through the protocol, that is, the settings in the SNMP management application.</sNMPv3_intro_Txt-1>
		<enable3_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable SNMP v3&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this option to activate SNMP v3. HTTPS must also be activated.</enable3_Txt>
		<password_v3_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;SNMP v3 Initial password&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the SNMP password here.</password_v3_Txt1>
		<password_v3_Txt1-1 type="text" minor="0">SNMP v3 &#x3C;b&#x3E;Initial&#x3C;/b&#x3E; user's password - Enter the SNMP password here.</password_v3_Txt1-1>
		<password_v3_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; The SNMP v3 password can only be set once, and only when HTTPS is enabled.</password_v3_Txt2>
		<password_v3_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">Once the password has been set, the password field will no longer be displayed. To set the password again, the product must be reset to the</password_v3_Txt3>
		<facdef_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">factory default settings</facdef_Txt1>
		<facdef_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">See also</facdef_Txt2>
		<https_linkTxt type="text" minor="0">Security - HTTPS</https_linkTxt>
	</snmp_h>
</language_xml>
