<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<onvif_user_setup_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/ONVIF User Setup</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">ONVIF User Setup</titleTxt>
		<addTxt1 type="text" minor="0">Provide the following information for each new ONVIF user:</addTxt1>
		<addTxt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;User name -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Enter a user name.</addTxt2>
		<addTxt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Password -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Enter a password.</addTxt3>
		<addTxt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Confirm Password -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Re-enter the password to confirm.</addTxt4>
		<addTxt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;User group&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Click the appropriate radio button to define the access rights for the user. The level of access can be described as follows:</addTxt5>
		<addTxt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Media user&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Allows access to the video stream only.</addTxt6>
		<addTxt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Operator&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - An Operator can view the video stream, create and modify event types, and also modify all the settings not included in the System options</addTxt7>
		<addTxt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Administrator&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - An Administrator has unrestricted access to the whole product and its setup Tools, and can determine the registration of all other users.</addTxt8>
	</onvif_user_setup_h>





	<onvif_users_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/ONVIF</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">ONVIF</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">ONVIF (Open Network Video Interface Forum) is a global interface standard that makes it easier for end users, integrators, consultants, and manufacturers to take advantage of the possibilities offered by network video technology. ONVIF enables interoperablity between different vendor products, increased flexibility, reduced cost and future-proof systems.</intro_Txt1>
		<intro_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">By creating a user you automatically enable ONVIF communication. Use the user name and password with all ONVIF communication with the product. For more information see the Developer pages at www.axis.com</intro_Txt2>
		<Subtitle type="text" minor="0">Users list</Subtitle>
		<list_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Users list&#x3C;/b&#x3E; shows the user name and user group of all the ONVIF users currently configured in the product.</list_Txt1>
		<list_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">To create a new user, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. To change an existing user, select the user in the list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Modify...&#x3C;/b&#x3E; To delete a user, select it and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</list_Txt2>
	</onvif_users_h>
</language_xml>
