<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<action_rule_setup_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Action Rule Setup</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Action Rule Setup</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">Action Rule setup enables setting up of rules to define how and when the Axis product will perform certain actions. Action Rule can be setup as scheduled, recurring or for example, trigged by motion detection.</intro_Txt>
		<title1_Txt type="text" minor="0">General</title1_Txt>
		<general_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable rule&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This box must be checked for the rule to be active.</general_Txt1>
		<general_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Name&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Provide a descriptive name for the Action Rule. This name will be displayed in the &#x3C;a href='action_rules_h.shtml'&#x3E;Action Rules List&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</general_Txt2>
		<title2_Txt type="text" minor="0">Condition</title2_Txt>
		<trigger_Txt type="text" minor="0">A &#x3C;b&#x3E;Trigger&#x3C;/b&#x3E; initiates the Action Rule which in turn starts certain &#x3C;b&#x3E;actions&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Listed below are the triggers available in this product. Select a group from the drop-down list and a second drop-down list will appear from which the desired trigger can be selected.</trigger_Txt>
		<trigger_appTrigger_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Applications&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule through an application installed in Axis product. The use of this trigger depends on the purpose or function of the installed application. For more information on available applications, please see &#x3C;a href='packages_h.shtml'&#x3E;Application Packages&#x3C;/a&#x3E; or the Axis web site at &#x3C;a href='http://www.axis.com' target='_blank'&#x3E;www.axis.com&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</trigger_appTrigger_Txt>
		<triggergroup_Detectors type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Detectors&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</triggergroup_Detectors>
		<audioDetect_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio Detection&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when sound level rises above or falls below the alarm level. It can be used to start/stop recording or to notify operator in case of detection.</audioDetect_Txt>
		<audioDetect_Txt_multisource type="text" minor="0">From the third drop-down list select the audio channel to be used.</audioDetect_Txt_multisource>
		<audioDetect_more_info1_Txt type="text" minor="0">For more information, see &#x3C;a href='audioDetection_h.shtml'&#x3E;Audio Detection&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</audioDetect_more_info1_Txt>
		<audioDetect_more_info2_Txt type="text" minor="0">For more information, see &#x3C;a href='audio_settings_h.shtml'&#x3E;Audio Settings&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</audioDetect_more_info2_Txt>
		<trigger_onfilter_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Day/Night Mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the camera switches between day and night mode (e.g. automatic IR Cut filter). It can be used to control an external infrared (IR) light through the output port.</trigger_onfilter_Txt1>
		<trigger_onfilter_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the camera is in day mode or switches to day mode.</trigger_onfilter_Txt2>
		<trigger_onfilter_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;No&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the camera is in night mode or switches to night mode.</trigger_onfilter_Txt3>
		<trigger_enterExit_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enter-Exit Detection&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action rule when the Axis product detects that an object has entered or exited the area. It can be used to, for example, send a notification to the operator when an object enters or exits a defined area. Enter-Exit detection must first be enabled through Setup &#x3E; Detectors.</trigger_enterExit_Txt>
		<trigger_fenceDetection_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fence Detection&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action rule when the Axis product detects that an object has crossed a virtual line. It can be used to, for example, send a notification to the operator when someone enters unauthorized area. Fence detector must first be enabled through Setup &#x3E; Detectors.</trigger_fenceDetection_Txt>
		<trigger_objectRemoved_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Object Removed&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action rule when the Axis product detects that an object has been removed from a scene.  It can be used to, for example, send a notification to the operator when someone has removed an object of interest from where it was placed. Object removed detector must first be enabled through Setup &#x3E; Detectors.</trigger_objectRemoved_Txt>
		<live_view_accessed_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Live Stream Accessed&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when a client accesses the live stream. The stream can be of any media type such as video, audio etc. The Action Rule can make use of status LED or an external light to notify persons that someone is actively monitoring.</live_view_accessed_Txt>
		<trigger_motion_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Motion Detection&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the Axis product built-in motion detection detects movement in a motion detection window.  It is used mostly to control when to start recording and when not to with respect to motion detection window. Select the motion detection window from the drop-down list and specify whether to trigger Action Rule when there is movement or when there is no movement (Yes/No). A motion detection window needs to be created for the Motion detection trigger to be enabled. More about &#x3C;a href='motion_h.shtml'&#x3E;Motion Detection&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</trigger_motion_Txt>
		<trigger_PIR type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;PIR&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the PIR sensor detects motion. The passive infrared sensor is an electronic device that measures infrared (IR) light radiating from objects in its field of view. It is typically used to detect motion in dark areas and trigger the rule to perform actions such as record video, send notification etc. For more help see &#x3C;a href='pirport_h.shtml'&#x3E;PIR Sensor&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</trigger_PIR>
		<trigger_tamper_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Tampering&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when someone has tampered with the camera. It can be used to notify operator if for example the camera has been repositioned or if the lens has been covered. For more help see &#x3C;a href='cameraTampering_h.shtml'&#x3E;Camera Tampering.&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</trigger_tamper_Txt>
		<tamper_Txt_multisource_video_Txt type="msgAsText" minor="0">From the third drop-down list select the video channel to be used.</tamper_Txt_multisource_video_Txt>
		<trigger_shockDetection_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Shock Detection&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action rule when the Axis product detects it has been tilted or hit. It can be used to, for example, send a notification to the operator when someone has hit or rotated the product. Shock detection must first be enabled through Setup &#x3E; Detectors &#x3E; Camera Tampering &#x3E; Enable shock detection.</trigger_shockDetection_Txt>
		<triggergroup_Hardware type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Hardware&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</triggergroup_Hardware>
		<triggerCasingOpen_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Casing Open&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule if the casing of a connected external device, such as a junction box is removed or opened. It can be used to send a notification to an operator if for example the casing has been opened for maintenance purposes or when someone has tampered with the casing.</triggerCasingOpen_Txt>
		<trigger_fan_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fan&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule if the fan fails.</trigger_fan_Txt>
		<trigger_network_lost1_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Network&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when Axis product looses network connection. Select one of the following options depending on the type of network connection used.</trigger_network_lost1_Txt1>
		<trigger_network_lost1_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Any&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule if any of the network connection (cable or wireless) is lost.</trigger_network_lost1_Txt2>
		<trigger_network_lost1_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;eth0&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule if network cable connection is lost.</trigger_network_lost1_Txt3>
		<trigger_network_lost1_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;eth1&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule if wireless network connection is lost.</trigger_network_lost1_Txt4>
		<trigger_network_lost1_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button to trigger the Action Rule if the network connection is &#x3C;b&#x3E;lost&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;No&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button to trigger the Action Rule when the network connection is &#x3C;b&#x3E;restored&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</trigger_network_lost1_Txt5>
		<trigger_network_lost2_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Network&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when network connection is lost. Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button to trigger the Action Rule if the network connection is &#x3C;b&#x3E;lost&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;No&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button to trigger the Action Rule when the network connection is &#x3C;b&#x3E;restored&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</trigger_network_lost2_Txt>
		<trigger_temp_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Temperature&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when temperature is above, below, inside or outside the operating range of the Axis product. In this scenario, the product can be set to notify operator.</trigger_temp_Txt>
		<triggerAudioConnector_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio Connector&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when audio cable is connected or disconnected from the Axis product. It can be used to notify an operator that audio cable has been disconnected for example when someone has tampered with the product.</triggerAudioConnector_Txt>
		<triggerRackFan_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fan&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule if the rack's fan fails. It can be used to send maintenance notifications to an operator.</triggerRackFan_Txt>
		<triggerPowerSupplyFail_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Power Supply Failure&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule if the rack's power supply fails. It can be used to send maintenance notifications to an operator.</triggerPowerSupplyFail_Txt>
		<triggerTemperatureCritical_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Temperature Critical&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the rack's temperature is above the maximum operating range, in this case the trigger may be used to send a notification to an operator.</triggerTemperatureCritical_Txt>
		<RackTriggersNote_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Fan, Power Supply Failure and Temperature Critical triggers are only available in channel 1 of the first blade in a rack.</RackTriggersNote_Txt>
		<trigger_videoloss_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Video Signal&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule if video signal to Axis product is lost. This trigger can be used in conjunction with pretrigger recording to allow viewing of the recording up to the point when video signal was lost. It can also be used to notify operator that a server has lost video signal.</trigger_videoloss_Txt>
		<videoloss_note_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; When using this trigger, the video source to detect video loss on does not have to be the same source as otherwise used by the trigger type. This means that it is possible to configure the trigger so that losing the video signal on one input will trigger an upload from another video source.</videoloss_note_Txt1>
		<videoloss_note_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">However, if the same video source is used in both cases, this will disable post-trigger upload and continued image upload (see below).</videoloss_note_Txt2>
		<trigger_inputs_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Input Signal&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Below are the types of input ports supported by this Axis product.</trigger_inputs_Txt1>
		<trigger_inputs_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">Configure I/O ports under &#x3C;b&#x3E;System Options&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Ports &#x26; Devices&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</trigger_inputs_Txt5>
		<trigger_inputs_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Digital Input Port&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when digital input port changes state. It can be used to initiate various actions such as send notification, send images, record video etc. In third drop-down list, select an input port to trigger the Action Rule when that specific input port is active. Or select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Any&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to trigger Action Rule when any input port is active.</trigger_inputs_Txt2>
		<trigger_inputs_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Manual Trigger&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when manual trigger button changes state. It can be used to start or stop the Action Rule manually through &#x3C;b&#x3E;Live View&#x3C;/b&#x3E; page. For this trigger to work, manual trigger button must be enabled in &#x3C;a href='layout_h.shtml'&#x3E;Live View Layout&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</trigger_inputs_Txt3>
		<select_view_area_Txt type="text" minor="0">Select the desired view area from the drop-down list.</select_view_area_Txt>
		<trigger_inputs_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Virtual Inputs&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when any of the virtual inputs changes states. It can be used by external client such as Video Management Systems to initiate various actions. In the third drop-down list, select an input port to trigger the Action Rule when that specific input port is active.</trigger_inputs_Txt4>
		<triggergroup_PTZ type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;PTZ&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</triggergroup_PTZ>
		<ptzAutoTrack_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Autotracking&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when PTZ autotracking starts, that is, autotracking has detected a moving object in the camera's field of view. It can be used to trigger the Action Rule to send a notification when autotracking starts to operate due to movement in the monitored area.</ptzAutoTrack_Txt>
		<ptzError_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;PTZ Error&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when Axis product encounters a serious PTZ error, for example it cannot tilt, zoom etc. This trigger can be used to notify operator that there is a problem with PTZ.</ptzError_Txt>
		<ptzError_view_area_Txt type="text" minor="0">Select the desired view area from the drop-down list.</ptzError_view_area_Txt>
		<ptzMove_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Moving&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when Axis product moves or not due to a PTZ operation. It can be used as an Additional Condition to stop other actions such as motion detection when PTZ is moving.</ptzMove_Txt>
		<ptzMove_view_area_Txt type="text" minor="0">Select the desired view area from the drop-down list.</ptzMove_view_area_Txt>
		<trigger_preset_reached_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Preset Reached &#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the view reaches at a preset position. This is useful for saving images from a guard tour, without saving images from when the Axis product is moving between presets or it can be used to upload an image at each preset position.</trigger_preset_reached_Txt1>
		<trigger_preset_reached_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">In the next drop-down list, select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Any&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to trigger the Action Rule when any preset position is reached.</trigger_preset_reached_Txt2>
		<ptzPreset_view_area_Txt type="text" minor="0">Select the desired view area from the drop-down list.</ptzPreset_view_area_Txt>
		<trigger_preset_reached_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: for the option &#x3C;b&#x3E; Preset reached &#x3C;/b&#x3E; - choose &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to trigger the Action Rule when preset position is reached (Axis product is stationary) or choose &#x3C;b&#x3E;No&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to trigger the Action Rule when preset position is left (Axis product start moving).</trigger_preset_reached_Txt3>
		<ptzReady_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Ready&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when PTZ is in ready status, for example Axis product can detect and send a notification when PTZ is ready to be used after restart. This trigger can be used to move Axis product to a specific preset position after restart.</ptzReady_Txt>
		<ptzReady_view_area_Txt type="text" minor="0">Select the desired view area from the drop-down list.</ptzReady_view_area_Txt>
		<trigger_disk2full_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Storage&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Notifies operator that there exists storage related issues that need to be responded to.</trigger_disk2full_Txt1>
		<trigger_disk2full_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Available&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when storage device is unmounted or removed.</trigger_disk2full_Txt2>
		<trigger_disk2full_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Full&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when storage device is full. Under normal conditions Axis product will cleanup old recordings before the storage is full.</trigger_disk2full_Txt3>
		<trigger_disk2full_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Locked&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when storage device has been locked (write protected).</trigger_disk2full_Txt4>
		<trigger_StorageDisruption_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Storage Disruption&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when storage problems are detected. This trigger may be used to send a notification to an operator if the storage device is unavailable, removed, full, locked or if there is a read or write problem. The operator may need to check the logs under &#x3C;b&#x3E;System Options &#x3E; Support &#x3E; Logs &#x26; Reports&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to identify the problem and take necessary measures to fix them e.g. unmount and re-mount the storage device etc.</trigger_StorageDisruption_Txt>
		<trigger_disk2full_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">Select the storage device from the drop-down list and select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for notification to be sent for example when the storage device is unmounted or removed, full, locked or if storage disruption is detected.</trigger_disk2full_Txt6>
		<trigger_recStatus_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Recording&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the Axis product records to the storage device. The recording status trigger can be used to notify the operator e.g by flashing LED lights, if the product has started or stopped to record to the storage device. Note that, this trigger can be used only for edge storage recording status.</trigger_recStatus_Txt>
		<triggergroup_System type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;System&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</triggergroup_System>
		<trigger_ready_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;System Ready&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the system is in ready status, for example Axis product can detect and send a notification to operator after it has started.</trigger_ready_Txt1>
		<trigger_ready_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button to trigger the Action Rule when the product is in Ready state. Note that the rule will only trigger when all necessary services such as event system have started.</trigger_ready_Txt2>
		<trigger_ready_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Action Rule will not be triggered when the &#x3C;b&#x3E;No&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button is selected.</trigger_ready_Txt3>
		<triggergroup_Time type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Time&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</triggergroup_Time>
		<recur_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Recurrence&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule by monitoring predefined recurrences.  It can be used to initiate recurring actions for example upload image every 30 minutes etc.  Select name of a recurrence pattern from the drop-down list. For more information about setting up a recurrence pattern, see  &#x3C;a href='recurrences_h.shtml'&#x3E;Recurrences&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</recur_Txt>
		<time_schedule_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Use Schedule&#x3C;/b&#x3E; -Triggers the Action Rule by monitoring state of predefined schedules. It can be used to record video in specific time period example office hours, weekends etc. select a schedule in the Schedule drop-down list. Select a schedule in the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Schedule&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list.</time_schedule_Txt>
		<sched_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Schedule&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</sched_Txt1>
		<sched_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Triggers the Action Rule at predefined times for example weekends, after certain hours etc. Schedule can also be used to initiate actions such as record video, send images etc. at a certain defined time.  Select a schedule to be used from the drop-down list. To add a new schedule, click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;New Schedule&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button and enter the required details.  For more information about setting up schedules, see &#x3C;a href='schedules_h.shtml'&#x3E;Schedules&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</sched_Txt2>
		<addlConditions_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Additional conditions&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</addlConditions_Txt1>
		<addlConditions_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Check this box if there is more than one criterion that should be met before the Action Rule is triggered. Description of the conditions is the same as for those under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Condition&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Trigger&#x3C;/b&#x3E; above. Note that for the Action Rule to be triggered, all triggers selected under Trigger or Schedule and Additional conditions must be active.</addlConditions_Txt2>
		<addlConditions_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">To add a new condition, Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add...&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and select a condition from the drop-down list, to change an existing condition, select condition in the list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Modify...&#x3C;/b&#x3E; To delete a condition, select it and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Set a waiting time in &#x3C;b&#x3E;Wait at least&#x3C;/b&#x3E; field to prevent Action Rule from running too often. The Action Rule needs to be re-triggered after the set waiting time in order to execute the action again.</addlConditions_Txt3>
		<actions_title type="text" minor="0">Actions</actions_title>
		<actions_intro type="text" minor="0">From the drop-down list choose an action. If for whatever reason the action fails to take place, for example an error with an email server, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Fail over action&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to enter an alternate action.</actions_intro>
		<night_vision_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Day/Night Vision Mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sets Auto mode, day mode  or night mode. When this mode is selected, the Action Rule will switch the IR cut filter to Auto mode (depending on lighting conditions), to Day mode (IR cut filter on) or to Night mode (IR cut filter off). Note that the IR cut filter setting in &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Audio&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Camera Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; page &#x3C;b&#x3E;must not&#x3C;/b&#x3E; be set to Auto.</night_vision_Txt>
		<ir_light_txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;IR Light&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Turns on the built-in Infrared (IR) light illuminator. It can be used in an Action Rule to turn on the IR light illuminator so that the camera can perform video surveillance in areas with low light, without requiring addition of external lighting.</ir_light_txt>
		<ir_light_txt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;IR Illumination&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Turns on the built-in Infrared (IR) light illuminator. It can be used in an Action Rule to turn on the IR light illuminator so that the camera can perform video surveillance in areas with low light, without requiring addition of external lighting.</ir_light_txt-1>
		<ir_light_active_txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Activate IR light while trigger is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The light will be activated while the trigger is active.</ir_light_active_txt>
		<ir_light_active_txt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Activate IR illumination while trigger is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The light will be activated while the trigger is active.</ir_light_active_txt-1>
		<ir_light_deactive_txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Deactivate IR light while trigger is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The light will be deactivated while the trigger is active.</ir_light_deactive_txt>
		<ir_light_deactive_txt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Deactivate IR illumination while trigger is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The light will be deactivated while the trigger is active.</ir_light_deactive_txt-1>
		<ir_light_deactive_oneshot_txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Deactivate IR light&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The light will be deactivated.</ir_light_deactive_oneshot_txt>
		<ir_light_deactive_oneshot_txt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Deactivate IR illumination&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The light will be deactivated.</ir_light_deactive_oneshot_txt-1>
		<ir_light_remain_active_txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Remain active as long as trigger is active (duration)&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The light will be activated as long as the trigger is active.</ir_light_remain_active_txt>
		<ir_light_active_oneshot_txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Activate IR light &#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The light will be activated.</ir_light_active_oneshot_txt>
		<ir_light_active_oneshot_txt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Activate IR illumination &#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The light will be activated.</ir_light_active_oneshot_txt-1>
		<ir_illumination_txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;IR Illumination&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Turns on the Infrared (IR) illumination. It can be used in an Action Rule to turn on IR illumination so that the camera can perform video surveillance in areas with low light, without requiring addition of external lighting.</ir_illumination_txt1>
		<ir_illumination_txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Activate IR illumination while trigger is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - IR illumination will be activated while the trigger is active.</ir_illumination_txt2>
		<ir_illumination_txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Deactivate IR illumination&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - IR illumination will be deactivated.</ir_illumination_txt3>
		<overlaytext_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Overlay Text&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Displays a text on top of a video stream image when the Action Rule is triggered. The text can be used to provide information for forensic video analysis, notify operators or validate triggers and actions during product installation and configuration.</overlaytext_Txt1>
		<overlayText_view_area_Txt type="text" minor="0">Select the desired view area from the drop-down list.</overlayText_view_area_Txt>
		<overlaytext_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: To display the overlay text when the Action Rule is triggered, the modifier &#x3C;b&#x3E;#D must&#x3C;/b&#x3E; be used in  &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Audio&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video Stream&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Image&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Overlay Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Include text&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</overlaytext_Txt2>
		<output_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Output Port&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Controls external equipment connected to a port on Axis product. Select the port and set the port to trigger when it is active or inactive. Configure I/O ports under &#x3C;b&#x3E;System Options&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Ports &#x26; Devices&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</output_Txt1>
		<output_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Duration&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set when the output port should be put in opposite state. Choose between when the Action Rule is no longer active or after a set time.</output_Txt2>
		<activatelight_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Activate Light&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Turns on the built-in light illuminator so that the camera can take clear images in dark environments. For example, if the PIR sensor detects motion in a dark environment, this action can be used to illuminate the scene while the camera records video or saves snapshot images.</activatelight_Txt1>
		<activatelight_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Keep active during rule&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The light will be activated as long as the rule is active.</activatelight_Txt2>
		<activatelight_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Keep active for (duration)&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the number of seconds/minutes the light should be activated.</activatelight_Txt3>
		<activatelight_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">It is also possible to control the Activate and Inactivate behavior according to special requirements.</activatelight_Txt4>
		<audioclip_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Play Audio Clip&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Plays a recorded audio clip when the Action Rule is triggered. It can be used to automatically notify operator that Axis product has detected movement.  From the Play drop-down list, select an audio clip to play when the Action Rule is triggered. To add new audio clips go to  &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Audio&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio Clips&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</audioclip_Txt>
		<pTZcontrol_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;PTZ Control&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Moves Axis product to a specified position when the Action Rule is triggered.</pTZcontrol_Txt>
		<pTZcontrol_view_areas_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">This action is available only if view area is enabled in &#x3C;b&#x3E;Camera Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</pTZcontrol_view_areas_Txt1>
		<pTZcontrol_view_areas_Txt1-1 type="text" minor="0">This action is available only if view area is enabled in &#x3C;b&#x3E;Camera Settings&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and if PTZ is enabled in View Areas.</pTZcontrol_view_areas_Txt1-1>
		<pTZcontrol_view_areas_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Select view area - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Select the desired view area from the drop-down list.</pTZcontrol_view_areas_Txt2>
		<control_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Control&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select from the drop-down list.</control_Txt>
		<preSet_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Preset Position&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Moves the Axis product to a specified position when the Action Rule is triggered. Use the option go to Home for Axis product to return to home preset position. It is also possible to set number of seconds for the product to wait before returning to home preset, this is done by checking the box return home when rule is no longer active and entering the number of seconds to wait before returning to home preset.</preSet_Txt>
		<runtourTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Guard Tour&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - When this option is selected, the Action Rule will start the tour selected in &#x3C;b&#x3E;guard tour&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list. Check the box if you want the tour to stop when Action Rule is no longer active. Check &#x3C;b&#x3E;Return to home position&#x3C;/b&#x3E; if you would like the tour to return to the preset home position.</runtourTxt>
		<action_AT_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Autotracking&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This action is used to start autotracking from a preset position, that is, to go to the preset position and from that position follow a moving object within the camera's field of view. Check the box &#x3C;b&#x3E;Return to home position&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for Axis product to return to home preset when Autotracking is inactive or enter number of seconds for the product to delay before returning to home preset.</action_AT_Txt>
		<select_recordVideo_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Record Video&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Records video to a selected storage.</select_recordVideo_Txt1>
		<select_recordVideo_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Select view area&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Choose view area from which to record video when the rule is active.</select_recordVideo_Txt2>
		<select_recordVideo_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream profile&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the type of stream profile. Listed below are default stream profiles as well as any created under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream Profiles&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</select_recordVideo_Txt3>
		<select_recordVideo_Txt3-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream profile&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the type of stream profile. Listed below are default stream profiles as well as any created under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream Profiles&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Note that, if no stream profile is selected, the default stream that is shown in the Live View page will be used.</select_recordVideo_Txt3-1>
		<select_recordVideo_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Duration&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set the length of the video to record.</select_recordVideo_Txt4>
		<select_recordVideo_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Pre-trigger time&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the number of seconds to include in the recording from time immediately before the rule was triggered.</select_recordVideo_Txt5>
		<select_recordVideo_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;While the rule is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Records only while the rule is active.</select_recordVideo_Txt6>
		<select_recordVideo_Txt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Post-trigger time&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the number of seconds to include immediately after the rule is no longer active. If &#x3C;b&#x3E;While the rule is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is enabled, the time entered here will be added to the recording time after the rule is no longer active.</select_recordVideo_Txt7>
		<select_recordVideo_Txt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Storage&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select where to save the recorded video from the drop-down list.</select_recordVideo_Txt8>
		<sendImages_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Send Images&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sends images to recipients such as HTTP, Email, FTP server etc.</sendImages_Txt1>
		<sendImages_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Select view area&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Choose view area from which to send images when the rule is active.</sendImages_Txt2>
		<sendImages_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream profile&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select JPEG stream profile to save the images. Listed are the stream profiles that have been created under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream Profiles&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. The default JPEG stream profile uses default image settings defined under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video Stream&#x3C;/b&#x3E; in &#x3C;b&#x3E;Video &#x26; Audio&#x3C;/b&#x3E; menu.</sendImages_Txt3>
		<sendImages_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Image frequency&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set the desired image frequency in number of frames per second, minute or hour.</sendImages_Txt4>
		<sendImages_Txt4-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Image frequency&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set the desired image frequency in number of frames per second, minute or hour. The default value 0 (zero) implies that maximum framerate from the stream profile will be used. To limit the image frequency, enter a different value. Note that, framerate is dependent on the capture mode and stream profile settings.</sendImages_Txt4-1>
		<sendImages_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Duration&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set the length of time for the images.</sendImages_Txt5>
		<sendImages_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Pre-trigger time&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the number of seconds to include in the sent images from time immediately before the rule was triggered.</sendImages_Txt6>
		<sendImages_Txt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;While the rule is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sends the images only while the rule is active.</sendImages_Txt7>
		<sendImages_Txt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Post-trigger time&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the number of seconds to include immediately after the rule is no longer active. If &#x3C;b&#x3E;While the rule is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is enabled, the time entered here will be added to the sent images time after the rule is no longer active.</sendImages_Txt8>
		<sendImages_Txt9 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Limit&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</sendImages_Txt9>
		<sendImages_Txt10 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Send only the first&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the maximum number of images to be sent.</sendImages_Txt10>
		<sendImages_Txt11 type="text" minor="1">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Recipient&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Recipients FTP, HTTP, HTTPS, Network share and email address (SMTP) are used to receive uploaded media files and notification messages. Select a recipient from the drop-down list or add a new one by clicking &#x3C;b&#x3E;New Recipient&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</sendImages_Txt11>
		<sendImagesNotes_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Notes&#x3C;/b&#x3E;:</sendImagesNotes_Txt>
		<emailSendLimit_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Some email providers have security filters that prevent users from receiving or viewing large amount of attachments, from receiving scheduled emails and similar. Check the email provider's security policy to avoid your email account being locked or missing on your expected emails.</emailSendLimit_Txt>
		<emailSendLimit_Txt-1 type="text" minor="0">Some email providers have security filters that prevent users from receiving or viewing large amount of attachments, from receiving scheduled emails and similar. Check the email provider's security policy to avoid your email account being locked or missing on your expected emails.</emailSendLimit_Txt-1>
		<sendImages_Txt12 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Select view area&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the desired view area from the drop-down list.</sendImages_Txt12>
		<sendNotific_Txt1 type="text" minor="1">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Send Notification&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sends notification to recipients HTTP, HTTPS, Email and TCP. Select a recipient from the drop-down list or add a new one by clicking &#x3C;b&#x3E;New Recipient&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</sendNotific_Txt1>
		<sendNotific_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;HTTP&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</sendNotific_Txt2>
		<sendNotific_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Message parameter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This message will be received in a CGI-variable called 'Message' on the target HTTP server. Note that including more than the maximum of 255 characters in this field will exclude some or all of the contents of &#x3C;b&#x3E;Custom parameter&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Spaces are allowed. For a list of modifiers that can be used in notifications, see &#x3C;a href='filenames_h.shtml'&#x3E;modifiers&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</sendNotific_Txt3>
		<sendNotific_Txt3-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Message parameter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the message or leave it empty. Message parameter is used when you have a CGI, that is, a HTTP server that can receive a CGI-variable called 'Message'.</sendNotific_Txt3-1>
		<sendNotific_Txt3-2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Example:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; If the complete syntax is &#x3C;i&#x3E;http://servername/axis-cgi/restart.cgi&#x3C;/i&#x3E;, then add the message 'restart' in the Message parameter field.</sendNotific_Txt3-2> 
		<sendNotific_Txt3-3 type="text" minor="0">Note that, including more than the maximum of 255 characters in this field will exclude some or all of the contents of &#x3C;b&#x3E;Custom parameter&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Spaces are allowed. For a list of modifiers that can be used in notifications, see &#x3C;a href='filenames_h.shtml'&#x3E;modifiers&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</sendNotific_Txt3-3>
		<sendNotific_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Custom parameter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Add any extra parameters here. Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and enter the name and parameter value. Note that it is allowed to use spaces in the value field but not in the name field.</sendNotific_Txt4>
		<sendNotific_Txt4-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Custom parameter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Add any extra parameters here. Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and enter the name and parameter value.</sendNotific_Txt4-1>
		<sendNotific_Txt4-2 type="text" minor="0">In the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Name&#x3C;/b&#x3E; field, enter the name of the VAPIX® command argument, for example, &#x3C;i&#x3E;gotoserverpresetname&#x3C;/i&#x3E;.</sendNotific_Txt4-2>
		<sendNotific_Txt4-3 type="text" minor="0">In the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Value&#x3C;/b&#x3E; field, enter the parameter's value. This can be, for example, a PTZ preset position number or name.</sendNotific_Txt4-3>
		<sendNotific_Txt4-4 type="text" minor="0">Note that, it is allowed to use spaces in the value field but not in the name field.</sendNotific_Txt4-4>
		<sendNotific_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Email&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</sendNotific_Txt5>
		<sendNotific_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Subject&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the subject for email</sendNotific_Txt6>
		<sendNotific_Txt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Message&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the message for email</sendNotific_Txt7>
		<sendNotific_Txt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;TCP&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</sendNotific_Txt8>
		<sendNotific_Txt9 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Message parameter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Same as HTTP Message parameter</sendNotific_Txt9>
		<sendNotific_Txt10 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Send notifications continuously while rule is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Check this box and enter the seconds interval for notifications to be sent while the rule is active.</sendNotific_Txt10>
		<sendNotific_Txt11 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;HTTPS&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</sendNotific_Txt11>
		<sendNotific_Txt12 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Message parameter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - This message will be received in a CGI-variable called 'Message' on the target HTTPS server. Note that including more than the maximum of 255 characters in this field will exclude some or all of the contents of &#x3C;b&#x3E;Custom parameter&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Spaces are allowed. For a list of modifiers that can be used in notifications, see &#x3C;a href='filenames_h.shtml'&#x3E;modifiers&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</sendNotific_Txt12>
		<sendNotific_Txt13 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Custom parameter&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Add any extra parameters here. Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and enter the name and parameter value. Note that it is allowed to use spaces in the value field but not in the name field.</sendNotific_Txt13>
		<sendVideoclip_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Send Video Clip&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sends video clip to recipients such as HTTP, FTP, Network Share, Email etc.</sendVideoclip_Txt1>
		<sendVideoclip_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Select view area&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Choose view area from which to record and send a video clip when the rule is active.</sendVideoclip_Txt2>
		<sendVideoclip_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream profile&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select the type of stream profile. Listed are the default stream profiles as well as any created under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Stream Profiles&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</sendVideoclip_Txt3>
		<sendVideoclip_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Duration&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set the length of the video to record.</sendVideoclip_Txt4>
		<sendVideoclip_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Pre-trigger time&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the number of seconds to include in the recording from time immediately before the rule was triggered.</sendVideoclip_Txt5>
		<sendVideoclip_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;While the rule is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sends video clip only while the rule is active.</sendVideoclip_Txt6>
		<sendVideoclip_Txt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: It is not possible to use &#x3C;b&#x3E;While the rule is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to send video clip to Email because some email providers may have a limit on attachments, if this limit is reached for example through receiving and viewing a huge amount of images, it can result into an email account being locked for a specific time.</sendVideoclip_Txt7>
		<sendVideoclip_Txt7-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: It is not possible to use &#x3C;b&#x3E;While the rule is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to send video clip to Email because some email providers have security filters that prevent users from receiving or viewing large amount of attachments, from receiving scheduled emails and similar. Check the email provider's security policy to avoid your email account being locked or missing on your expected emails.</sendVideoclip_Txt7-1>
		<sendVideoclip_Txt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Post-trigger time&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter the number of seconds to include immediately after the rule was triggered. If &#x3C;b&#x3E;While the rule is active&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is enabled, the time entered here will be added to the recording time after the rule is no longer active.</sendVideoclip_Txt8>
		<sendVideoclip_Txt9 type="text" minor="1">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Recipient&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Recipients FTP, HTTP, HTTPS, Network share and email address (SMTP) are used to receive uploaded media files and notification messages. Select a recipient from the drop-down list or add a new one by clicking &#x3C;b&#x3E;New Recipient&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</sendVideoclip_Txt9>
		<folderNameLimit_Txt type="text" minor="0">Time modifiers used in the field &#x3C;b&#x3E;Create folder&#x3C;/b&#x3E; are only used when an Action rule is triggered, hence no new folders are created with the current time during an active rule. To have new folders created with time modifiers during an active rule, add the modifiers in the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Base filename&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</folderNameLimit_Txt>
		<folderNameLimitVid_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Time modifiers used in the field &#x3C;b&#x3E;Create folder&#x3C;/b&#x3E; are only used when an Action rule is triggered, hence no new folders are created with the current time during an active rule. To have new folders created with time modifiers during an active rule, add the modifiers in the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Base filename&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</folderNameLimitVid_Txt>
		<sendSNMP_trap_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Send SNMP Trap&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sends an SNMP trap message to the management system when the Axis product experiences fan failure, power supply failure, when shock detection occurs or other critical issues that are of interest to the operator. Enter the message that should be sent along with the trap in the Message field.</sendSNMP_trap_Txt>
		<sendSNMP_trapNote_Txt type="text" minor="0">Make sure that SNMP is enabled and configured under &#x3C;b&#x3E;System Options > Network > SNMP&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for this action to be successful.</sendSNMP_trapNote_Txt>
		<sendSNMP_trap_Txt-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Send SNMP Trap&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sends an SNMP trap message to the management system.  This action allows the operator to send an SNMP trap message from any trigger available through the Action rule setup page. Enter the message that should be sent along with the trap in the Message field.</sendSNMP_trap_Txt-1>
		<lED_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Status LED &#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The status LED can be set to flash for the duration of the Action Rule or for a set number of seconds. Status LED can be used during installation and configuration to visually validate if trigger settings work correctly for example motion detection trigger. Choose color to flash from the &#x3C;b&#x3E;LED color&#x3C;/b&#x3E; drop-down list.</lED_Txt>
		<failOver_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fallback action&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - A fallback action is started if the primary action cannot be started, for example if connection to a recipient cannot be established. It can be used to send email notifications to operator or perform any other specified action for example upload images to a secondary recipient.</failOver_Txt>
        <wdrMode_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;WDR Mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sets WDR Mode or Lightfinder Mode when the Action Rule is triggered.  This action may be used when needed to change between the modes automatically. Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;WDR On&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;Lightfinder Mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for the product to be set to that specific mode when the Action Rule is triggered.</wdrMode_Txt>
        <wdrModeOff_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;WDR Mode&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Sets WDR Mode to On or Off when the Action Rule is triggered.  This action may be used when needed to change between the modes automatically. Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;WDR On&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;WDR Off&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for the product to be set to that specific mode when the Action Rule is triggered.</wdrModeOff_Txt>
	</action_rule_setup_h>

	<action_rules_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Action Rules</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Action Rules</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">Action rule setup allows you to set up rules to define how and when the unit will perform certain actions. Events may be set up as scheduled, recurring or triggered, for example when motion is detected, a disk is full or  audio reaches a defined level.</intro_Txt1>
		<intro_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Actions performed when an event occurs can include sending an email, a notification through FTP, HTTP or TCP, and activation of an output port.</intro_Txt2>
		<listHeaderTxt type="text" minor="0">Action Rule List</listHeaderTxt>
		<list_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">The &#x3C;b&#x3E;Action Rule List&#x3C;/b&#x3E; shows all the rules currently configured in the product, along with various information about their configuration, as listed below:</list_Txt1>
		<list_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Name&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The name entered by the user when the rule was set up.</list_Txt2>
		<list_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Trigger&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The name of the trigger that activates the rule.</list_Txt3>
		<list_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Schedule&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The name of the schedule used. The name entered by the user when the schedule was set up.</list_Txt4>
		<list_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Action&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - What action is performed for the event.</list_Txt5>
		<list_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Recipient&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The name of the recipient for email, FTP, HTTP or TCP.</list_Txt6>
		<checkbox_Txt type="text" minor="0">Select/clear the check box in the column furthest to the left to enable/disable an action rule.</checkbox_Txt>
		<button_Txt type="text" minor="1">To create a new Action rule, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add...&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. To copy a rule, select an existing rule and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Copy...&#x3C;/b&#x3E; To change an existing rule, select the rule in the list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Modify...&#x3C;/b&#x3E; To delete a rule, select it and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</button_Txt>
		<button_Txt-1 type="text" minor="1">To create a new Action rule, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add...&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. To change an existing rule, select the rule in the list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Modify...&#x3C;/b&#x3E; To delete a rule, select it and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</button_Txt-1>
		<link_Txt type="text" minor="0">See &#x3C;a href='action_rule_setup_h.shtml'&#x3E;Action Rule Setup&#x3C;/a&#x3E; for more information on how to set Action Rules.</link_Txt>
	</action_rules_h>

	<additional_condition_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Additional Condition</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Additional Condition</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">Select additional conditions that should be met before an action can take place. The selection made from the Events drop-down list and any additional events selected here would have to be active.</intro_Txt>
		<title2_Txt type="text" minor="0">Condition</title2_Txt>
		<dropdown_Txt type="text" minor="0">Select a group of events from the drop-down list. A second drop-down list will then appear from which the desired event is selected.</dropdown_Txt>
		<trigger_appTrigger_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Applications - &#x3C;/b&#x3E; Triggers the Action Rule through an application installed in Axis product. The use of this trigger depends on the purpose or function of the installed application. For more information on available applications, please see &#x3C;a href='packages_h.shtml'&#x3E;Application Packages&#x3C;/a&#x3E; or the Axis web site at &#x3C;a href='http://www.axis.com' target='_blank'&#x3E;www.axis.com&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</trigger_appTrigger_Txt>
		<triggergroup_Detectors type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Detectors&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</triggergroup_Detectors>
		<audioDetect_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio Detection - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;This is used to trigger the event every time the sound level rises above, or falls below the alarm level. See &#x3C;a href='audio_settings_h.shtml'&#x3E;Audio Settings&#x3C;/a&#x3E; for more information.</audioDetect_Txt1>
		<audioDetect_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio Detection - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;This is used to trigger the event every time the sound level rises above, or falls below the alarm level. See &#x3C;a href='audio_settings_h.shtml'&#x3E;Audio Settings&#x3C;/a&#x3E; for more information.</audioDetect_Txt2>
		<trigger_audioDetection_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Audio Detection&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when sound level rises above or falls below the alarm level. It can be used to start/stop recording or to notify operator in case of detection.</trigger_audioDetection_Txt>
		<live_view_accessed_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Live Stream Accessed&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when a client accesses the live stream. The stream can be of any media type such as video, audio etc. The Action Rule can make use of status LED or an external light to notify persons that someone is actively monitoring.</live_view_accessed_Txt>
		<trigger_onfilter_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Day/Night vision - &#x3C;/b&#x3E; Triggers the Action Rule when the camera switches between day and night mode (e.g. automatic IR Cut filter). It can be used to control an external infrared (IR) light through the output port.</trigger_onfilter_Txt1>
		<trigger_onfilter_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Day on - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Triggers the Action Rule when day/night vision is in day mode or switches to day mode.</trigger_onfilter_Txt2>
		<trigger_onfilter_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Day off - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Triggers the Action Rule when day/night vision is in night mode or switches to night mode.</trigger_onfilter_Txt3>
		<trigger_motion_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Motion Detection&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the Axis product built-in motion detection detects movement in a motion detection window.  It is used mostly to control when to start recording and when not to with respect to motion detection window. Select the motion detection window from the drop-down list and specify whether to trigger Action Rule when there is movement or when there is no movement (Yes/No). A motion detection window needs to be created for the Motion detection trigger to be enabled. More about &#x3C;a href='motion_h.shtml'&#x3E;Motion detection&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</trigger_motion_Txt>
		<trigger_PIR type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;PIR&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the PIR sensor detects motion. The passive infrared sensor is an electronic device that measures infrared (IR) light radiating from objects in its field of view. It is typically used to detect motion in dark areas and trigger the rule to perform actions such as record video, send notification etc. For more help see &#x3C;a href='pirport_h.shtml'&#x3E;PIR Sensor&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</trigger_PIR>
		<trigger_tamper_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Tampering - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;The product can trigger an alarm if it detects that someone has tampered with it, for example if the camera is repositioned or if the lens is covered. See also the help on &#x3C;a href='cameraTampering_h.shtml'&#x3E;Camera tampering.&#x3C;/a&#x3E;</trigger_tamper_Txt>
		<triggergroup_Hardware type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Hardware&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</triggergroup_Hardware>
		<trigger_fan_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Fan - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;This triggers an event if the fan fails.</trigger_fan_Txt>
		<triggerCasingOpen_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Casing Open&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule if the casing of a connected external device, such as a junction box is removed or opened. It can be used to send a notification to an operator if for example the casing has been opened for maintenance purposes or when someone has tampered with the casing.</triggerCasingOpen_Txt>
		<trigger_network_lost1_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Network - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Triggers the Action Rule when Axis product looses network connection. Select one of the following options depending on the type of network connection used.</trigger_network_lost1_Txt1>
		<trigger_network_lost1_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Any - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Triggers the Action Rule if any of the network connection (cable or wireless) is lost.</trigger_network_lost1_Txt2>
		<trigger_network_lost1_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;eth0 - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Triggers the Action Rule if network cable connection is lost.</trigger_network_lost1_Txt3>
		<trigger_network_lost1_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;eth1 - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Triggers the Action Rule if wireless network connection is lost.</trigger_network_lost1_Txt4>
		<trigger_network_lost1_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">Select the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button to trigger the Action Rule if the network connection is &#x3C;b&#x3E;lost&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;No&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button to trigger the Action Rule when the network connection is &#x3C;b&#x3E;restored&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</trigger_network_lost1_Txt5>
		<trigger_network_lost2_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Network - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Triggers the Action Rule when network connection is lost. Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button to trigger the Action Rule if the network connection is &#x3C;b&#x3E;lost&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;No&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button to trigger the Action Rule when the network connection is &#x3C;b&#x3E;restored&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</trigger_network_lost2_Txt>
		<trigger_temp_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Temperature - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;This will trigger the event if the temperature is within, rises or falls outside of the operating range of the product. Select from the drop-down list which sensor is within operating range.</trigger_temp_Txt1>
		<trigger_videoloss_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Video Signal - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;This trigger type can be used in conjunction with pre-trigger recording, to allow viewing of the recording up to the point when video was lost. It can also be used to notify users that the server has lost the video signal.</trigger_videoloss_Txt>
		<videoloss_note_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; When using this event type, the video source to detect video loss on does not have to be the same source as otherwise used by the event type. This means that it is possible to configure the event type so that losing the video signal on one input will trigger an upload from another video source.</videoloss_note_Txt1>
		<videoloss_note_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">However, if the same video source is used in both cases, this will disable post-event upload and continued image upload (see below).</videoloss_note_Txt2>
		<trigger_inputs_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Input Signal -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Below are the types of input ports supported by this Axis product. Configure I/O ports under &#x3C;b&#x3E;System Options&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Ports &#x26; Devices&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</trigger_inputs_Txt1>
		<trigger_inputs_Txt1-1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Input Signal&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Below are the types of input ports supported by this Axis product.</trigger_inputs_Txt1-1>
		<trigger_inputs_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">Configure I/O ports under &#x3C;b&#x3E;System Options&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Ports &#x26; Devices&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</trigger_inputs_Txt5>
		<trigger_inputs_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Digital Input Port&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when digital input port changes state. It can be used to initiate various actions such as send notification, send images, record video etc. In third drop-down list, select an input port to trigger the Action Rule when that specific input port is active. Or select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Any&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to trigger Action Rule when any input port is active.</trigger_inputs_Txt2>
		<trigger_inputs_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Virtual Inputs&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Triggers the Action Rule when any of the virtual inputs changes states. It can be used by external client such as Video Management Systems to initiate various actions. In the third drop-down list, select an input port to trigger the Action Rule when that specific input port is active.</trigger_inputs_Txt3>
		<trigger_inputs_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Manual Trigger&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when manual trigger button changes state. It can be used to start or stop the Action Rule manually through &#x3C;b&#x3E;Live View&#x3C;/b&#x3E; page. For this trigger to work, manual trigger button must be enabled in &#x3C;a href='layout_h.shtml'&#x3E;Live View Layout&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</trigger_inputs_Txt4>
		<triggergroup_PTZ type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;PTZ&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</triggergroup_PTZ>
		<ptzAutoTrack_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Autotracking&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when PTZ autotracking starts, that is, autotracking has detected a moving object in the camera's field of view. It can be used to trigger the Action Rule to send a notification when autotracking starts to operate due to movement in the monitored area.</ptzAutoTrack_Txt>
		<ptzReady_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Ready&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when PTZ is in ready status, for example Axis product can detect and send a notification when PTZ is ready to be used after restart. This trigger can be used to move Axis product to a specific preset position after restart.</ptzReady_Txt>
		<ptzMove_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Moving - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Triggers the Action Rule when Axis product moves or not due to a PTZ operation. It can be used as an Additional Condition to stop other actions such as motion detection when PTZ is moving.</ptzMove_Txt>
		<trigger_temp_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Preset Reached - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Triggers the Action Rule when the view reaches at a preset position. This is useful for saving images from a guard tour, without saving images from when the Axis product is moving between presets or it can be used to upload an image at each preset position.</trigger_temp_Txt2>
		<trigger_disk2full_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Storage - &#x3C;/b&#x3E; Notifies operator that there exists storage related issues that need to be responded to. It can be used to trigger the Action Rule when a storage device is available, locked or full (i.e., it has less than 10 MB of free memory). Select the storage device from the drop-down list and select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E;No&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for the desired trigger.</trigger_disk2full_Txt>
		<trigger_disk2full_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Storage&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Notifies operator that there exists storage related issues that need to be responded to.</trigger_disk2full_Txt1>
		<trigger_StorageDisruption_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Storage Disruption&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when storage problems are detected. This trigger may be used to send a notification to an operator if the storage device is unavailable, removed, full, locked or if there is a read or write problem. The operator may need to check the logs under &#x3C;b&#x3E;System Options &#x3E; Support &#x3E; Logs &#x26; Reports&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to identify the problem and take necessary measures to fix them e.g. unmount and re-mount the storage device etc.</trigger_StorageDisruption_Txt>
		<trigger_recStatus_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Recording&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the Axis product records to the storage device. The recording status trigger can be used to notify the operator e.g by flashing LED lights, if the product has started or stopped to record to the storage device. Note that, this trigger can be used only for edge storage recording status.</trigger_recStatus_Txt>
		<trigger_disk2full_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">Select the storage device from the drop-down list and select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; for notification to be sent for example when the storage device is unmounted or removed, full, locked or if storage disruption is detected.</trigger_disk2full_Txt6>
		<trigger_ready_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;System Ready&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Triggers the Action Rule when the system is in ready status, for example Axis product can detect and send a notification to operator after it has started.</trigger_ready_Txt1>
		<trigger_ready_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button to trigger the Action Rule when the product is in Ready state. Note that the rule will only trigger when all necessary services such as event system have started.</trigger_ready_Txt2>
		<trigger_ready_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E;: Action Rule will not be triggered when the &#x3C;b&#x3E;No&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button is selected.</trigger_ready_Txt3>
		<triggergroup_System type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;System&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</triggergroup_System>
		<trigger_onboot_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;System Initializing - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;Select the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Yes&#x3C;/b&#x3E; radio button to trigger the Action Rule every time the product is started.</trigger_onboot_Txt>
		<triggergroup_Time type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Time&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</triggergroup_Time>
		<recur_Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Recurrences - &#x3C;/b&#x3E;This triggers a recurring event. Select the name of a recurrency pattern from the drop-down list. For more information about setting up a recurrency pattern, see &#x3C;a href='recurrences_h.shtml'&#x3E;Recurrences&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</recur_Txt>
		<stateless_note type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Stateless events such as Tampering or Recurrences can not be used as an additional condition.</stateless_note>
	</additional_condition_h>

	<filenames_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/File Naming &#x26; Date/Time Formats</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">File Naming &#x26; Date/Time Formats</titleTxt>
		<intro_txt_1 type="text" minor="0">The Axis product supports the use of &#x3C;b&#x3E;modifier fields&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. These can be used for adding information to notification messages. The modifiers available are listed below.</intro_txt_1>
		<intro_txt_2 type="text" minor="0">The Axis product supports the use of &#x3C;b&#x3E;modifier fields&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. These can be used for modifying file names when uploading images, for formatting the date and time added to image overlays, and for adding information to notification messages. The modifiers available in each case are listed below.</intro_txt_2>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">Syntax</subTitle1Txt>
		<syntax_txt type="text" minor="0">The format string can contain normal text and/or modifier fields, the latter which always start with a &#x3C;b&#x3E;%&#x3C;/b&#x3E;  or a &#x3C;b&#x3E;#&#x3C;/b&#x3E; character, followed by another character. Anything else is considered normal text.</syntax_txt>
		<syntaxEx_txt type="text" minor="0">When for example, a new file is named, the format fields are replaced with values according to the options selected from the table below. All normal text is left as it is.</syntaxEx_txt>
		<help5txt1 type="text" minor="0">For example, the string &#x3C;b&#x3E;image-%H-%M-%S.jpg&#x3C;/b&#x3E; will cause uploaded files to be timestamped with the hour, minute and second they were created, as follows:</help5txt1>
		<help5txt2 type="text" minor="0">image-00-00-00.jpg</help5txt2>
		<help5txt3 type="text" minor="0">image-00-00-01.jpg</help5txt3>
		<help5txt4 type="text" minor="0">image-00-00-02.jpg</help5txt4>
		<help5txt5 type="text" minor="0">...</help5txt5>
		<help5txt6 type="text" minor="0">...</help5txt6>
		<help5txt7 type="text" minor="0">etc</help5txt7>
		<note1_txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; This type of formatting should not contain  blank spaces.</note1_txt>
		<subTitle2Txt type="text" minor="0">Available modifiers</subTitle2Txt>
		<modifiers_txt1 type="text" minor="0">The available modifiers can each be used in various situations. The abbreviations given in brackets for each modifier show which situations the modifier can be used in. These are:</modifiers_txt1>
		<modifiers_txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;D&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Own date formatting</modifiers_txt2>
		<modifiers_txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;T&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Own time formatting</modifiers_txt3>
		<modifiers_txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;I&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Text overlay</modifiers_txt4>
		<modifiers_txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;IP&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Notification of change of IP address</modifiers_txt5>
		<modifiers_txt6 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;EF&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Event file name</modifiers_txt6>
		<modifiers_txt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;EN&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Event notification via TCP/HTTP</modifiers_txt7>
		<modifiers_txt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;M&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Mail subject/message</modifiers_txt8>
		<modifiers_txt9 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;UF&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Folder name for uploads</modifiers_txt9>
		<generalNote_txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Some modifiers contain characters that are not supported by all filesystems. For example, modifiers that returns time or MAC address %c, #m, #M contains the colon (:) character that is not supported in Windows filesystems.</generalNote_txt>
		<help8txt type="text" minor="0">Modifier</help8txt>
		<help9txt type="text" minor="0">Description (can be used for)</help9txt>
		<help10txt type="text" minor="0">The abbreviated weekday name.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help10txt>
		<help11txt type="text" minor="0">The full weekday name.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help11txt>
		<help12txt type="text" minor="0">The abbreviated month name.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M)</help12txt>
		<help13txt type="text" minor="0">The full month name.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help13txt>
		<help14txt type="text" minor="0">The date and time.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help14txt>
		<help14txt-1 type="text" minor="0">The date and time.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;This modifier cannot be used to name folders and files in Windows operating systems as it contains the colon (:) character. For Windows, combine other modifiers to add date and time in folder and file names. For example %d.%I.%M.%S&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help14txt-1>
		<help15txt type="text" minor="0">The century number (year/100) as a 2-digit integer.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help15txt>
		<help16txt type="text" minor="0">The day of the month as a decimal number (range 01 to 31).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help16txt>
		<help18txt type="text" minor="0">As for %d, but a leading zero is replaced by a blank space.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help18txt>
		<help19txt type="text" minor="0">The 1/100 second fraction.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help19txt>
		<help19atxt type="text" minor="0">The date in the format as specified in the Date &#x26; Time settings.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help19atxt>
		<help20txt type="text" minor="0">The ISO 8601 year with century as a decimal number. The 4-digit year corresponding to the ISO week number (see &#x3C;a href='#iso_week_number'&#x3E;%V&#x3C;/a&#x3E;). This has the same format and value as %y, except that if the ISO week number belongs to the previous or next year, then that year is used instead.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help20txt>
		<help21txt type="text" minor="0">As for %G, but without the century, i.e., with a 2-digit year (00-99).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help21txt>
		<help22txt type="text" minor="0">Equivalent to %b.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help22txt>
		<help23txt type="text" minor="0">The hour as a decimal number, using the 24-hour clock (range 00 to 23).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(T,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help23txt>
		<help24txt type="text" minor="0">The hour as a decimal number, using the 12-hour clock (range 01 to 12).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(T,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help24txt>
		<help25txt type="text" minor="0">The day of the year as a decimal number (range 001 to 366).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(T,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help25txt>
		<help26txt type="text" minor="0">The hour (24-hour clock) as a decimal number (range 0 to 23); single digits are preceded by a blank space. (See also %H.)&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(T,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help26txt>
		<help27txt type="text" minor="0">The hour (12-hour clock) as a decimal number (range 1 to 12); single digits are preceded by a blank. (See also %I.)&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(T,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help27txt>
		<help28txt type="text" minor="0">The month as a decimal number (range 01 to 12).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help28txt>
		<help29txt type="text" minor="0">The minute as a decimal number (range 00 to 59).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(T,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help29txt>
		<help31txt type="text" minor="0">AM or PM, according to the given time value, or the corresponding strings for the current locale. Noon is treated as PM and midnight as AM.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(T,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help31txt>
		<help33txt type="text" minor="0">The time in a.m. or p.m. notation.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(T,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help33txt>
		<help34txt type="text" minor="0">The time in 24-hour notation (%H:%M). For a version including seconds, see &#x3C;a href='#time'&#x3E;%T&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(T,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF) &#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Will not work on all FTP servers</help34txt>
		<help35txt type="text" minor="0">The number of seconds since the Epoch, i.e., since 1970-01-01 00:00:00 UTC.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(T,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help35txt>
		<help36txt type="text" minor="0">The second as a decimal number (range 00 to 59).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(T,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help36txt>
		<help38txt type="text" minor="0">The time as specified in the Date &#x26; Time settings.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EN,M,UF) &#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Will not work on all FTP servers</help38txt>
		<help39txt type="text" minor="0">The day of the week as a decimal, range 1 to 7, Monday = 1. See also &#x3C;a href='#day_of_week_0_6'&#x3E;%w&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help39txt>
		<help40txt type="text" minor="0">The week number of the current year as a decimal number, range 00 to 53, starting with the first Sunday as the first day of week 01. See also &#x3C;a href='#iso_week_number'&#x3E;%V&#x3C;/a&#x3E; and &#x3C;a href='#week_number_monday'&#x3E;%W&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help40txt>
		<help41txt type="text" minor="0">The ISO 8601:1988 week number of the current year as a decimal number, in the range 01 to 53, where week 1 is the first week that has at least 4 days in the current year, and with Monday as the first day of the week. See also &#x3C;a href='#week_number_sunday'&#x3E;%U&#x3C;/a&#x3E; and &#x3C;a href='#week_number_monday'&#x3E;%W&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help41txt>
		<help42txt type="text" minor="0">The day of the week as a decimal, in the range 0 to 6. Sunday = 0. See also &#x3C;a href='#day_of_week_1_7'&#x3E;%u&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help42txt>
		<help43txt type="text" minor="0">The week number of the current year as a decimal number, in the range 00 to 53, starting with the first Monday as the first day of week 01.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help43txt>
		<help45txt type="text" minor="0">The time representation without the date.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EN,M,UF)</help45txt>
		<help46txt type="text" minor="0">The year as a decimal number without the century (range 00 to 99).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help46txt>
		<help47txt type="text" minor="0">The year as a decimal number, including the century.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(D,I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help47txt>
		<help50txt type="text" minor="0">The literal % character.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(All)</help50txt>
		<help60txt type="text" minor="0">The bit rate in Kbit/s (with no decimals).&#x3C;sup&#x3E;1,2&#x3C;/sup&#x3E;&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,UF)</help60txt>
		<help60txt-1 type="text" minor="0">The bit rate in Kbit/s (with no decimals). See notes 1 and 2 below.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,UF)</help60txt-1>
		<help61txt type="text" minor="0">The bit rate in Mbit/s (with two decimals).&#x3C;sup&#x3E;1,2&#x3C;/sup&#x3E;&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,UF)</help61txt>
		<help61txt-1 type="text" minor="0">The bit rate in Mbit/s (with two decimals). See notes 1 and 2 below.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,UF)</help61txt-1>
		<help76txt type="text" minor="0">The action perfomed by the Action Rule, for example Send Notification.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(EF,EN,M,UF)</help76txt>
		<help77txt type="text" minor="0">The event description.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(EF,EN,I,M)</help77txt>
		<help52txt type="text" minor="0">The IP address.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help52txt>
		<help65txt type="text" minor="0">PTZ locator zone name (OSDI).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help65txt>
		<help53txt type="text" minor="0">The short MAC address (last 6 characters).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help53txt>
		<help54txt type="text" minor="0">The long MAC address (all characters).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help54txt>
		<help55txt type="text" minor="0">The host name.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help55txt>
		<help66txt type="text" minor="0">Preset number.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help66txt>
		<help67txt type="text" minor="0">Preset name.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help67txt>
		<help58txt type="text" minor="0">The frame rate (with two decimals).&#x3C;sup&#x3E;1,2&#x3C;/sup&#x3E;&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,UF)</help58txt>
		<help58txt-1 type="text" minor="0">The frame rate (with two decimals). See notes 1 and 2 below.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,UF)</help58txt-1>
		<help59txt type="text" minor="0">The frame rate (with no decimals).&#x3C;sup&#x3E;1,2&#x3C;/sup&#x3E;&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,UF)</help59txt>
		<help59txt-1 type="text" minor="0">The frame rate (with no decimals). See notes 1 and 2 below.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,UF)</help59txt-1>
		<help51txt type="text" minor="0">The sequence number.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(EF)</help51txt>
		<help78txt type="text" minor="0">The name of the Action Rule, for example MyActionRule.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(EF,EN,M)</help78txt>		
		<help79txt type="text" minor="1">Displays a text on top of a video stream image when the Action Rule is triggered.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I)</help79txt>
		<help73txt type="text" minor="1">The fan status. &#x3C;b&#x3E;n&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is the fan number. For example, to show the status of fan number 1, enter #U1 in the text overlay field.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I)</help73txt>
		<help74txt type="text" minor="1">The sensor temperature in Celsius. &#x3C;b&#x3E;n&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is the sensor number. For example, to show the status of sensor number 1, enter #TC1 in the text overlay field.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I)</help74txt>
		<help75txt type="text" minor="1">The sensor temperature in Fahrenheit. &#x3C;b&#x3E;n&#x3C;/b&#x3E; is the sensor number. For example, to show the status of sensor number 1, enter #TF1 in the text overlay field.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I)</help75txt>
		<help56txt type="text" minor="0">The video source number.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EN,M,UF)</help56txt>
		<help56atxt type="text" minor="0">The name of the motion detection window triggering an event.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(EN,M,UF)</help56atxt>
		<help68txt type="text" minor="0">Pan coordinate (with two decimals).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help68txt>
		<help69txt type="text" minor="0">Tilt coordinate (with two decimals).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help69txt>
		<help70txt type="text" minor="0">Zoom coordinate (1-19999).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help70txt>
		<help71txt type="text" minor="0">Zoom magnification (with one decimal).&#x3C;br /&#x3E;(I,IP,EF,EN,M,UF)</help71txt>
		<help57txt type="text" minor="0">The literal # character.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; (All)</help57txt>
		<help62txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note 1:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; These values may contain spaces and should only be used in the text overlay.</help62txt>
		<help64txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note 2:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; For Motion JPEG, these values are only valid if no frame rate limit has been specified.</help64txt>
		<help63txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note 2:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; For Motion JPEG, these values are only valid if no frame rate limit and/or bandwidth limitation has been specified. For MPEG-4 the values are only valid if no bandwidth limitation has been specified.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;&#x3C;br /&#x3E;The bandwidth can be limited from &#x3C;b&#x3E;System Options &#x3C; Network &#x3C; TCP/IP &#x3C; Advanced&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</help63txt>
		<helpAudiotxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; All modifiers may not work with this product.</helpAudiotxt>
	</filenames_h>
</language_xml>
