<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<smtp_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/SMTP (email) Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">SMTP (email) Settings</titleTxt>
		<general_subTitle_smtp_Txt type="text" minor="0">SMTP Settings</general_subTitle_smtp_Txt>
		<introTxt type="text" minor="0">The Axis product can be configured to send</introTxt>
		<events_yesTxt type="text" minor="0">event and error email messages via SMTP (Simple Mail Transfer Protocol).</events_yesTxt>
		<events_noTxt type="text" minor="0">an email message via SMTP (Simple Mail Transfer Protocol) whenever the IP address changes.</events_noTxt>
		<serversTxt type="text" minor="0">Enter the host names or IP addresses for your primary and secondary mail servers in the fields provided. Note that to use host names for mail servers, a DNS server must be specified in the &#x3C;A HREF='advanced_tcpip_h.shtml'&#x3E;Advanced TCP/IP Settings&#x3C;/A&#x3E;.</serversTxt>
		<portsTxt type="text" minor="0">Enter the SMTP server port numbers for the primary and secondary SMTP servers, using values in the range 0-65535. The default value is 25.</portsTxt>
		<authenticationTxt type="text" minor="0">If your mail server requires authentication, check the box for &#x3C;b&#x3E;Use authentication to log in to this server&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</authenticationTxt>
		<userpassTxt type="text" minor="0">Enter the &#x3C;b&#x3E;User Name&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and &#x3C;b&#x3E;Password&#x3C;/b&#x3E; as provided by your network administrator or ISP (Internet Service Provider).</userpassTxt>
		<auth_methodTxt type="text" minor="0">To ensure that the login procedure is performed as securely as possible when using &#x3C;b&#x3E;SMTP&#x3C;/b&#x3E; authentication, you must define the weakest authentication method allowed. Set the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Weakest method allowed&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to the highest/safest method supported by the mail server. The most secure method is listed last. The options &#x3C;b&#x3E;Login&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and &#x3C;b&#x3E;Plain&#x3C;/b&#x3E; have the same priority.</auth_methodTxt>
		<usePOPTxt type="text" minor="0">When logging into a POP mail server, enter the host name or IP address of the POP server.</usePOPTxt>
		<noteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Action rules using SMTP (email) need to be disabled and then enabled for the new SMTP settings to be effective.</noteTxt>
		<senderTxt type="text" minor="0">The &#x3C;b&#x3E;From email address&#x3C;/b&#x3E; field will be used as the sender for all messages sent by the product.</senderTxt>
		<general_subTitle_smtp_test_Txt type="text" minor="0">Test</general_subTitle_smtp_test_Txt>
		<testTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Send test email to -&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Enter an email address and click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Send&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button to test that the mail servers are functioning and that the email address is valid.</testTxt>
	</smtp_h>
</language_xml>
