<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<recurrence_setup_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Recurrence Setup</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Recurrence Setup</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">This page allows you to set up a recurring event with a specific interval or a specific number of times in a period of time.</intro_Txt>
		<txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Name&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter a descriptive name for the recurrence.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;&#x3C;br /&#x3E; &#x3C;b&#x3E;Recurrency pattern/Repeat every&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Set up a specific pattern for the recurrency. For example, every 2 hours (starting the following hour, on the hour). When using the day(s) option the action is triggered at 00:00:00.</txt>
		<txt_extra_info type="text" minor="0">To use the recurrence in an Action Rule, first select Time from the Trigger drop-down list in the Action Rule Setup page and then select the recurrence from the second drop-down list.</txt_extra_info>
		<txt_note type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - a recurrence may not happen at the expected time set because the next  recurrence uses the last occurred recurrence as a time reference point.</txt_note>
		<txt_note_example type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Example:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;br /&#x3E;&#x3C;br /&#x3E;The Axis product uses epoch (1970-01-01T00:00:00Z ISO 8601) as a time reference in Recurrence setup, that is the time when the first recurrence occured.</txt_note_example>
		<example_setup_Txt type="text" minor="0">Go to Setup &#x3E; System Options &#x3E; Date &#x26; Time. Set manually the Axis product's time to 11:55.</example_setup_Txt>
		<example_setup_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">Go to Setup &#x3E; Events &#x3E; Schedules. Create a schedule that starts at 12:00 and ends at 12:10 (every day).</example_setup_Txt1>
		<example_setup_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">Go to Setup &#x3E; Events &#x3E; Recurrences. Create a recurrence that triggers once every 7th minute.</example_setup_Txt2>
		<example_setup_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">Go to Setup &#x3E; Events &#x3E; Action rules, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and set up an action rule that triggers on the recurrence and the schedule created in step 2 and 3.</example_setup_Txt3>
		<example_setup_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">Wait until 12:00 and note when the recurrence will trigger.</example_setup_Txt4>
		<txt_note_1example type="text" minor="0">Using epoch as a time reference, during the first hour after occurance of the first recurrence, the Action Rule will be triggered in the following minutes intervals 0 7 14 21 28 35 42 49 56.</txt_note_1example>
		<txt_note_1example-1 type="text" minor="0">Based on the above setup and the product using epoch as a time reference, during the first hour, the Action rule will be triggered in the following minutes intervals 0 7 14 21 28 35 42 49 56.</txt_note_1example-1>
		<txt_note_2example type="text" minor="0">During the second hour, recurrence will occur in the following minutes intervals 3 10 17 24 31 38 45 53 because the product uses the last occurred recurrence as a time reference.</txt_note_2example> 
		<txt_note_3example type="text" minor="0">If for example a recurrence is set to occur at 13:00, the Action Rule will be triggered before 13:00hr. Therefore recurrences may not happen at the exact specified time.</txt_note_3example>
	</recurrence_setup_h>



	<recurrences_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Recurrences</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Recurrences</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt type="text" minor="0">This page allows you to set up an recurring event with a specific interval or a specific number of times in a period of time.</intro_Txt>
		<listSubTitle type="text" minor="0">Recurrences List</listSubTitle>
		<list_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">Listed here are the recurrences that have already been set up:</list_Txt1>
		<list_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Name&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - The name entered by the user when the recurrence was set up.</list_Txt2>
		<list_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Recurrency pattern&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Shows the specific pattern the recurrency was set up for. For example, if it was set up to run every 2 hours or specific time period for example 1 hour and 15 minutes.</list_Txt3>
		<button_Txt type="text" minor="0">To create a new recurrence, click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add...&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. To change an existing recurrence, select it in the list and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Modify...&#x3C;/b&#x3E; To delete a recurrence, select it and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</button_Txt>
		<link_Txt type="text" minor="0">See &#x3C;a href='recurrence_setup_h.shtml'&#x3E;Recurrence Setup&#x3C;/a&#x3E; for more information on how to set Recurrences.</link_Txt>
	</recurrences_h>
</language_xml>
