<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<qos_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/QoS Settings</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">QoS Settings</titleTxt>
		<intro_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Quality of Service&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (QoS) provides the means to guarantee a certain level of a specified resource to selected traffic on an IP network. Quality can be defined as e.g. a maintained level of bandwidth, low latency, no packet losses, etc.</intro_Txt1>
		<intro_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">The main benefits of a QoS-aware network can be summarized as:</intro_Txt2>
		<intro_Txt3 type="text" minor="0">The ability to prioritize traffic and thus allow critical flows to be served before flows with lesser priority.</intro_Txt3>
		<intro_Txt4 type="text" minor="0">Greater reliability in the network, thanks to the control of the amount of bandwidth an application may use, and thus control over bandwidth races between applications.</intro_Txt4>
		<intro_Txt5 type="text" minor="0">The QoS in the Axis product marks the data packets belonging to various types of network traffic originating from the unit. QoS-enabled network routers and switches then use these markings to apply particular treatment to these types of traffic, for example, to reserve a fixed amount of bandwidth.</intro_Txt5>
		<intro_Txt6 type="text" minor="0">The types of traffic that can be marked are</intro_Txt6>
		<video_support_Txt type="text" minor="0">video,</video_support_Txt>
		<audio_support_Txt type="text" minor="0">audio,</audio_support_Txt>
		<event_support_Txt type="text" minor="0">event/alarm traffic,</event_support_Txt>
		<management_Txt1 type="text" minor="0">and management network traffic.</management_Txt1>
		<management_Txt2 type="text" minor="0">For more information on QoS, please visit the &#x3C;a href='http://www.axis.com/techsup' target='_blank'&#x3E;Axis Support web&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.</management_Txt2>
		<subTitle1Txt type="text" minor="0">QoS Settings</subTitle1Txt>
		<help2Txt1 type="text" minor="0">For each of the supported types of network traffic, enter a value for the &#x3C;b&#x3E;DSCP&#x3C;/b&#x3E; (Differentiated Services Codepoint) field in the data packet's IP header.</help2Txt1>
		<help2Txt2 type="text" minor="0">This value marks the network traffic so that network routers know which service(s) to apply to the packet, for example, the amount of bandwidth reserved for the type of traffic.</help2Txt2>
		<help2Txt3 type="text" minor="0">The DSCP value can be entered in decimal or hexadecimal format, but saved values are always shown in decimal format.</help2Txt3>
		<h264m4Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Live Audio DSCP will be equal to Live Video DSCP if H.264 or MPEG-4 over RTSP is used.</h264m4Txt>
		<h264Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note1:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Live Audio DSCP will be equal to Live Video DSCP if H.264 over RTSP is used.</h264Txt>
		<m4Txt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note1:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Live Audio DSCP will be equal to Live Video DSCP if MPEG-4 over RTSP is used.</m4Txt>
		<eventNoteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note2:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Changing the Event/Alarm DSCP value will not affect the DSCP value that has already been set to previous recipients. The newly set DSCP value will be used for new recipients and the old recipients will keep using the old DSCP value.</eventNoteTxt>
		<eventDSCPNoteTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E; Changing the Event/Alarm DSCP value will not affect the DSCP value that has already been set to previous recipients. The newly set DSCP value will be used for new recipients and the old recipients will keep using the old DSCP value.</eventDSCPNoteTxt>
	</qos_h>
</language_xml>
