<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language_xml>
	<autotracking_ExAr_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Exclude Areas</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Exclude Areas</titleTxt>
		<txt1 type="text" minor="0">Create an 'Exclude Window' to configure an area where movement is to be ignored. To prevent camera movement during the configuration of 'Exclude Areas', enable the Control Queue under &#x3C;b&#x3E;Dome Configuration &#x3E; Advanced &#x3E; Control Queue&#x3C;/b&#x3E;. Once enabled, request control of the camera by clicking in the image whereby autotracking and Guard Tour will be temporarily disabled.</txt1>
		<subTitle1 type="text" minor="0">Add/Edit Exclude Area</subTitle1>
		<txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Add area&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</txt2>
		<txt3 type="text" minor="0">Click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Add area&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and a blue rectangle will appear in the video stream. Click the top bar to move the rectangle and click and pull the bottom right hand corner to resize the rectangle.</txt3>
		<txt4 type="text" minor="0">Enter a descriptive name for the exclude window and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Save&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to save the settings in the list of Exclude Areas.</txt4>
		<txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Note:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</txt5>
		<txt6 type="text" minor="0">The blue rectangles will not be visible on the Live View page.</txt6>
		<txt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</txt7>
		<txt8 type="text" minor="0">Click the name of the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Exclude Area&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to be removed and click &#x3C;b&#x3E;Remove&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</txt8>
		<txt9 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable/Disable&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</txt9>
		<txt10 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable/Disable&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to enable or disable the configured Exclude Area.</txt10>
	</autotracking_ExAr_h>





	<autotracking_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Autotracking</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Autotracking</titleTxt>
		<txt1 type="text" minor="0">Autotracking detects movement in the camera's field of view and will follow the motion, e.g. a person or vehicle, until it disappears from the monitored area. The camera will automatically pan and tilt to follow the motion and, if there is a lot of movement simultaneously in the view, the area with the most amount of motion will be monitored.</txt1>
		<txt2 type="text" minor="0">When there are no moving objects in the field of view, the camera will return to the 'home' position, if this feature is enabled under &#x3C;b&#x3E;PTZ  &#x3E; Preset positions&#x3C;/b&#x3E;.</txt2>
		<txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Notes:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;</txt3>
		<txt4 type="text" minor="0">The autotracking feature is designed for areas where there is a limited amount of movement.</txt4>
		<txt5 type="text" minor="0">If autotracking and Guard Tour are both enabled, it is strongly recommended that the PTZ Control Queue is enabled. The PTZ Control Queue will make sure that the Guard Tour will have lower priority than autotracking, preventing the camera from abandoning autotracking in order to maintain a Guard Tour.</txt5>
		<txt6 type="text" minor="0">Autotracking will not trigger on movement within an area blocked by a Privacy Mask or Exclude Area nor will it follow movement beyond the limits of a Privacy Mask or autotracking Max Limits.</txt6>
		<subTitle1 type="text" minor="0">Start and Stop Autotracking</subTitle1>
		<txt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Start/Stop Autotracking&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Start&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button to manually start autotracking and click the &#x3C;b&#x3E;Stop&#x3C;/b&#x3E; button to manually stop autotracking.</txt7>
		<subTitle2 type="text" minor="0">Settings</subTitle2>
		<settingTxt type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Movement trigger sensitivity&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Select &#x3C;b&#x3E;High, Medium,&#x3C;/b&#x3E; or &#x3C;b&#x3E; Low&#x3C;/b&#x3E; to define the sensitivity level for autotracking. Medium sensitivity is the recommended setting but high or low may suit certain areas better depending on the image contrast and size of the moving objects in the monitored area.</settingTxt>
	</autotracking_h>





	<autotracking_MaLi_h>
		<pageTitle type="title" minor="0">Help/Max Limits</pageTitle>
		<titleTxt type="msgAsText" minor="0">Max Limits</titleTxt>
		<txt1 type="text" minor="0">Set the values (in degrees) to define the pan and tilt limits for the area where autotracking is allowed. Any movement in the field of view beyond the set limits will be ignored, for example in outdoor surveillance; birds in the sky may not be of interest and could be excluded using this function. In the preview window, the max limits will be highlighted by blue horizontal and vertical bars. Click on these bars in order to move them to the desired position.</txt1>
		<txt2 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable tilt limit&#x3C;/b&#x3E; -Click the checkbox to enable the tilt limits.</txt2>
		<txt3 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Lower tilt angle&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter a value (in degrees) to set the bottom limit or click on the blue &#x3C;b&#x3E;Lower tilt angle&#x3C;/b&#x3E; link to activate the blue horizontal bar that represents the lower limit.</txt3>
		<txt4 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Upper tilt angle&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter a value (in degrees) to set the top limit or click on the blue &#x3C;b&#x3E;Upper tilt angle&#x3C;/b&#x3E; link to activate the blue horizontal bar that represents the upper limit.</txt4>
		<txt5 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Enable pan limit&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Click the checkbox to enable the pan limits.</txt5>
		<txt6 type="text" minor="0">The area between &#x3C;b&#x3E;Start&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and &#x3C;b&#x3E;Stop&#x3C;/b&#x3E; will be permitted for &#x3C;b&#x3E;autotracking&#x3C;/b&#x3E; and the field of view beyond the set limits will be ignored.</txt6>
		<txt7 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Pan limit start&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter a value (in degrees) to set the limit starts in the current view or click on the blue &#x3C;b&#x3E;Pan limit start&#x3C;/b&#x3E; link to activate the blue vertical bar that represents where the limit starts.</txt7>
		<txt8 type="text" minor="0">&#x3C;b&#x3E;Pan limit end&#x3C;/b&#x3E; - Enter a value (in degrees) to set where the limit stops in the current view or click on the blue &#x3C;b&#x3E;Pan limit end&#x3C;/b&#x3E; link to activate the blue vertical bar that represents where the limit stops.</txt8>
	</autotracking_MaLi_h>
</language_xml>
